Welcome back to
Notes about Nothing.
As veteran viewers will explain to
rookies, this f eature will guide you. . .
. . .through each episode's
many historical, cultural. . .
. . .and series-related ref erences.
And here's our first fact
of the season:
Chess originated
in 6th century India. . .
. . .although it could date back
to 2nd century China.
''Checkmate'' originates from
the Persian phrase shah mat. . .
. . . meaning ''the king is dead.''
There are no moves
the player can make. . .
. . .to save the king,
hence the game is over.
We also keep track of each of the
main f our's girlfriends /boyfriends. . .
. . . Kramer's entrances
into Jerry's apartment. . .
. . .and every time Jerry says
''Hello, Newman.''
And our first counter:
GEORGE GIRLFRIEND COUNTER:
#43 - Alice, who beat him in chess
Renee Phillips also appeared in
The American Presifent. . .
. . .and played Cher in Anf the Beat
Goes On: The Sonny anf Cher Story.
She also worked in
the Art Department on films
like City Slickers and Chaplin.
The word ''emasculated'' derives
from the Latin. . .
. . . meaning ''deprived of
male role or identity.''
Actress Heidi Swedberg had used
the phrase ''Happy, Pappy?''. . .
. . .in off-screen conversations
with Larry David.
Swedberg had played George's
girlfriend Susan Ross. . .
. . .during the 1 992-93 season.
JERRY GIRLFRIEND COUNTER:
#44 - Melanie, the shusher
Susan Ross worked f or NBC
during the f ourth season.
George met her when they were
pitching a television pilot
to the network.
Susan became a lesbian and was
seen with her partner. . .
. . . late in season f our. . .
. . .in ''The Smelly Car'' episode.
In deleted dialogue. . .
. . .George shared that Susan really
understood and accepted him.
This episode was filmed
in front of a studio audience. . .
. . .on Wednesday, August 1 6, 1 995.
The 1 995-96 season
you 're now watching. . .
. . .was the final one to be
executive produced. . .
. . . by series co-creator Larry David.
Check out Jerry
and the gang's thoughts. . .
. . .on Larry's decision
to leave the show. . .
. . .in an extra located
elsewhere in this collection.
KRAMER ENTRANCE COUNTER: #240
Look f or this classic scene. . .
. . . reimagined in Sein-Imation
elsewhere on this disc.
In some deleted jokes,
Kramer continued his rant:
''And everywhere you go,
you have to call.
'I 'm going to be a little late.'
'I 'm sorry, I can 't be
home f or another half-hour.
Is that okay? Can I stay out
another half-hour? Please!'''
While the characters shied away
from marriage and family. . .
. . .the actors playing them
have taken diff erent routes. . .
. . .in their own lives.
As of 2006, Julia Louis-Dreyfus and
husband Brad Hall have two boys.
So do Jason Alexander
and his wif e Daena.
Michael Richards has one daughter.
And Jerry Seinf eld and his wif e
Jessica have three young children.
If this spot looks familiar. . .
. . .you must have seen
season five's finale, ''The Opposite.''
This bench is located
on the Santa Monica Pier
above the Pacific Ocean.
Seinfelf crew members played
the couples in this scene.
That's 2nd assistant director
Jim Lansbury. . .
. . .and script supervisor
Christine Nyhart.
And that's producer Tim Kaiser
with the woman and infant.
Notice Elaine's hoarse voice?
Julia's not acting.
She really did lose her voice.
It happened while filming
the scenes screaming at the dog. . .
. . .which took place the day
bef ore shooting this apartment scene.
Overnight, her voice
became hoarse. . .
. . .so the laryngitis
was written into the script.
Laryngitis is an inflammation
of the voice box or larynx.
It often comes on quickly
and can last up to two weeks.
Common causes include overuse
of the voice, as in Julia's case. . .
. . .upper respiratory inf ections. . .
. . .irritants like smoke or chemicals
and allergies.
Elaine considered hiring a hit man
f or her boyfriend 's cats. . .
. . .in the first season episode
''The Stock Tip.''
As many of you know,
Newman is Jerry's mailman neighbor.
Wayne Knight played him
in over 40 episodes. . .
. . .throughout the series.
By the end of this season. . .
. . . Knight was also starring on another
NBC sitcom, 3rf Rock from the Sun.
And bef ore becoming Newman,
the Georgia-born Knight. . .
. . .worked as a private detective
in New York City. . .
. . .in between early acting jobs.
He honed his craft on the stage. . .
. . .and began working in film
and television in the mid- 1 980s.
Early credits include Dirty Dancing. . .
. . . Born on the Fourth of July
and Deaf Again.
He played Numa Bertel
in Oliver Stone's JFK. . .
. . .which Seinfelf parodied
in season three's ''The Boyfriend.''
And a dinosaur famously gobbled him
right out of his jeep in Jurassic Park.
There are over 1 . 5 million dogs
living in New York City.
In deleted dialogue. . .
. . . Newman mentioned that more than
a f ew of the dogs on his route. . .
. . . had taken a bite of his flesh home
as a souvenir.
Recognize these memories from
previous seasons?
You shouldn 't.
This flashback montage was filmed
specifically f or this episode.
In the fall of 1 995,
NBC's Seinfelf. . .
. . .was the only half-hour comedy
on network TV at 9 o'clock.
Its time-slot competition
was ABC's The Monroes. . .
. . .a soap opera
about a political family.
CBS aired New York News. . .
. . .a newspaper drama
starring Mary Tyler Moore.
And Fox's crime drama
New York Unfercover. . .
. . . returned f or its second
of five seasons.
Athena Massey
plays Melanie in this episode.
She appeared in Eddie Murphy's
remake of The Nutty Professor. . .
. . .and has had recurring roles
on Nash Brifges and Black Scorpion.
Massey has also parlayed her talents
into the gaming world. . .
. . .voicing characters on the Commanf
& Conquer video game series.
Hawaiian-born Heidi Swedberg's
pre-Susan acting career. . .
. . .includes TV jobs. . .
. . . ranging from Matlock
to Brooklyn Brifge to Sisters.
Among her early film credits
are the films In Country. . .
. . . Hot Shots! and Kinfergarten Cop.
Since Seinfelf, Heidi has continued
to work in television. . .
. . .guest-starring on
Touchef by an Angel, Provifence. . .
. . . ER and G ilmore G irls.
From this conversation. . .
. . .it's clear that George never
introduced Susan to his parents. . .
. . .during their previous relationship.
Estelle Harris memorably
appeared f or the first time. . .
. . .in season f our's ''The Contest.''
Jerry Stiller first appeared
as Frank Costanza. . .
. . .in season f our's
''The Handicap Spot.''
Technically, his first appearance. . .
. . .was in season five's
''The Puffy Shirt''. . .
. . .since he replaced
the original Frank, John Randolph. . .
. . . between seasons f our and five.
When the show went into
syndication. . .
. . .Stiller re-recorded Randolph 's
scenes from ''The Handicap Spot''. . .
. . .so that he would always appear
as George's curmudgeonly dad.
You can still see
John Randolph 's perf ormance. . .
. . .on Season 4, Volume 3
of Seinfelf on DVD.
The tradition of getting engaged
began in 1 21 5. . .
. . .when Pope Innocent III established
a waiting period. . .
. . . between betrothal
and marriage.
The diamond ring was first used
as an engagement present. . .
. . .when the Holy Roman Emperor,
Maximilian I . . .
. . . proposed to Mary of Burgundy
in 1 477.
Jerry and George discussed the
merits of a ''pinkish hue''. . .
. . .in the third season 's
''The Fix-Up.''
A low-budget science-fiction film
called Firestorm. . .
. . .was released in 1 995.
Three years later. . .
. . .another movie with that title
hit the big screens. . .
. . .starring f ormer NFL sensation
Howie Long as a firefighter.
Champagne comes from grapes
grown in the Champagne region. . .
. . .in northern France. Tended by
monks in the Reims region. . .
. . .the wine was always
considered sacred.
It became a celebration libation
beginning in the 9th century. . .
. . .as it was poured during the
coronations of French royalty.
Champagne was a wine
until the 1 7 th century. . .
. . .when Dom Pérignon
accidentally discovered. . .
. . .that adding sugar caused a second
f ermentation and voilà: bubbles.
''How Much Is That Doggie
in the Window''. . .
. . .is a popular 1 950s tune
penned by Bob Merrill.
Deleted dialogue reveals that Newman
sings it to get him ''in the mood.''
The ''singing rage'' Patti Page
recorded the song to much acclaim.
Hers is the most famous rendition.
Bob Merrill is also known
f or penning a song. . .
. . .that we bet will make you
think of Barbra Streisand: ''People.''
Elaine, Kramer and Newman are
breaking all sorts of New York laws. . .
. . . by lifting this pooch.
For starters, larceny.
They are taking possession
of her neighbor's dog. . .
. . .without authorization
or notification.
They're also looking at
abandonment charges. . .
. . .f or leaving the dog
on a stranger's doorstep.
That's a misdemeanor
in New York. . .
. . .and they could face a year
in the slammer and / or a $1 , 000 fine.
In the shooting script. . .
. . . Kramer explains that Newman
wouldn 't take money. . .
. . .to kidnap the dog because
''it's the hate that drives him.''
The names of real movie stars
Glenn Close and Sally Field. . .
. . . lend credence to another fake
movie name, The Mutef Heart.
Timepieces became portable
in the 1 5th century. . .
. . .when sailors used them
f or navigation and mapping.
Patek Phillippe
invented the wristwatch. . .
. . .at the end of the 1 9th century.
Originally the accessory
was made just f or women. . .
. . . but by World War I ,
the trend caught on with men. . .
. . . namely soldiers in the field.
Kramer may tell time
by the sun here. . .
. . . but by the eighth season, he seems
to be carrying a pocket watch.
In fact, he sets that watch
an hour ahead in ''The Susie.''
It seems the dog that has been
haunting Elaine is a silky terrier.
Terriers tend to be alert
and energetic.
The silky terrier is known to bark,
especially if left unattended.
That's stand-up comedian
Mario Joyner walking
out of the theater with Jerry.
The two are good friends
in real lif e too.
Joyner also appears in
''The Puerto Rican Day.''
He's in the Chris Rock films
Down to Earth and Heaf of State.
In a deleted scene, Jerry asked Mario
to do a Jesse Jackson impersonation.
Monticello is about 1 00 miles
northwest of Manhattan.
This scene was originally
much longer. . .
. . .and involved a close call
with the police. . .
. . .which explains how Kramer,
Elaine and Newman. . .
. . .were tracked down so quickly.
Check out this episode's ''In the Vault''
section of deleted material. . .
. . .elsewhere on this DVD.
Rudy's was established
as a used clothing store. . .
. . .in season five's ''The Raincoats.''
MSG is the MSG Network,
a New York area cable station. . .
. . .that broadcasts
New York sports team games.
It also stands f or monosodium
glutamate, a flavor enhancer.
Maf About You ran on NBC from
1 992 to 1 999.
The sitcom about
a Manhattan married couple. . .
. . .starred Paul Reiser
and Helen Hunt.
Mattingly is Yankee star
first baseman Don Mattingly.
Donnie Baseball wore the pinstripes
from 1 983 to 1 995. . .
. . . but never made it
to the World Series.
This scene was also shot
on the CBS Radf ord lot. . .
. . .on the road to the lagoon that
runs alongside the Los Angeles River.
The lagoon was also used
on G illigan 's Islanf.
Jerry was scripted to be
sprawled out on his bed.
''Visible on bed is a car magazine,
Sports Illustratef and Playboy.''
Roxy was the name of one of
Larry David 's dogs at the time.
His other dog was named Mortimer.
Janni Brenn plays Roxy's owner.
Brenn has had a recurring role. . .
. . .on NBC's long-running
hospital drama ER.
She also appeared
in the animated flick Cool Worlf. . .
. . .and the Sandra Bullock thriller
Murfer by Numbers.
''Pearl Harbor'' ref ers to the Japanese
attack of the Hawaiian Navy base. . .
. . .on December 7, 1 941 , sparking
the U.S. entry into World War II .
President John F. Kennedy was
assassinated on November 22, 1 963
in Dallas, Texas.
Theories still abound,
but the official analysis concluded. . .
. . .that Lee Harvey Oswald
shot the president from the
Texas School Book Depository.
This program parodied
the magic-bullet theory
espoused in Oliver Stone's film JFK.
See ''The Boyfriend,'' Volume 2,
Season 3 of Seinfelf on DVD.
Here comes one of
the all-time great ''get outs.''
Julia took this reaction from
her own lif e and ramped it up
f or the show.
Ed O'Ross, who plays the cop,
boasts an extensive resume.
His big-screen credits include
Dick Tracy, Full Metal Jacket. . .
. . .and Universal Solfier.
O'Ross' television roles include
Curb Your Enthusiasm. . .
. . .and the recurring role of Nikolai
on Six Feet Unfer.
Look f or him to return once more
in season nine's ''The Finale.''
Deleted dialogue explained
that the trio was arrested. . .
. . .under ''Article 26, Section 353,
Cruelty to Animals.''
Season seven premiered with this
episode on September 21 , 1 995.
''The Engagement'' scored a season
high 24.6 rating with a 37 share.
In TV terms, a ratings point represents
the proportion of homes. . .
. . .that own televisions that are
watching a particular show.
The share ref ers to the proportion of
homes actually watching television. . .
. . .that are watching
a particular show.
The script f or this episode
was 83 pages long.
By comparison, most television
sitcom scripts average about 50 pages.
Do you know who composed the
Maf About You theme music?
None other than the show's star
and college music-major Paul Reiser.
Musician and producer Don Was
perf ormed the song. . .
. . .titled ''Final Frontier.''