A rabbi is the title
f or a spiritual Jewish leader.
Some insight into
Elaine's neighbor was cut.
Elaine was scripted to say,
''Very nice man. . .
. . .although not the world's
greatest dresser.''
Jerry then said, ''Rabbis generally
aren't on the cutting edge of fashion.''
Elaine replied, ''It's 80 degrees out,
he's walking around with a wool suit.''
The ''dog'' is a ref erence to the
previous episode, ''The Engagement.''
As in earlier years...
. . . Larry David and Jerry Seinf eld. . .
. . . began making plans
f or season seven. . .
. . .during the preproduction period.
That's when they decided
to have George get engaged.
Larry David wrote the opening
three episodes of the season. . .
. . .to help set the tone
f or the storylines that would f ollow.
The cast gathered f or the table
reading of ''The Postponement''. . .
. . .on Friday, August 1 8, 1 995.
The episode was filmed
in front of a studio audience. . .
. . .the next Wednesday, August 23rd.
George off ers
his bathroom stall suggestion. . .
. . .to his boss, Mr. Steinbrenner,
later in the season in ''The Calzone.''
Check out disc f our to see how
''Big Stein'' reacted to the idea.
KRAMER ENTRANCE COUNTER: #241
Rabbi Kirschbaum is named
after Bruce Kirschbaum. . .
. . .a Seinfelf writer
f or several seasons.
The character's name inexplicably
changes to Rabbi Glickman. . .
. . .in his return appearances
in season nine.
Jerry's odd delivery of this line is
an homage to comedian Jackie Mason.
March 21 is the spring,
or vernal equinox.
It marks the moment when the sun
crosses the celestial equator. . .
. . . moving northward.
While March 21 st is the first day of
spring in the Northern Hemisphere. . .
. . .it's the first day of autumn f or our
friends in the Southern Hemisphere.
KRAMER ENTRANCE COUNTER: #242
Nabisco introduced SnackWells® line
of reduced-fat. . .
. . .and fat-free cookies
and crackers in 1 992.
Bruce Mahler, who plays the rabbi,
climbed the Police Acafemy ranks...
. . .from cadet to sergeant
as Douglas Fackler. . .
. . .in f our of the cop comedy flicks.
He also worked with Michael Richards,
Larry David and Bruce Kirschbaum. . .
. . .as both a writer and actor
on Frifays.
It's no surprise that Larry David
selected his old colleague. . .
. . .to play the rabbi.
David and Mahler prayed together
during their years on Frifays...
. . . playing rabbis hosting a TV show. . .
. . .in a recurring sketch called
''Live and Be Well.''
The word rabbi translates
from Hebrew as ''teacher'' or ''master.''
Rabbis train f or years,
studying the Torah. . .
. . .and work as religious officials
in synagogues. . .
. . .teaching congregants Jewish
religion and law.
Caf é lattes are made with a single
shot of espresso and steamed milk.
The ratio is three parts milk
to one part coff ee.
Notice the way Michael Richards
says ''caf é latte.''
His mispronunciations
of certain words. . .
. . .often had the rest of the cast
in stitches.
To this day, only Michael knows
if it was an actor's choice. . .
. . .or just his way of speaking.
Plan 9 from Outer Space
is a callback to the second season.
Jerry, Elaine and George
had planned to see that film. . .
. . .in the episode,
''The Chinese Restaurant.''
Kramer wasn't with them when they
stopped at a Chinese restaurant. . .
. . . bef ore trying to catch
this classically-bad horror 1 959 movie.
Jerry calls it
''the worst movie ever made.''
There are 25, 000 wire-mesh
litter baskets in New York City.
The city council has a detailed system
of penalties in place. . .
. . .f or litterbugs like Jerry.
Fines range from $1 0 to $450
f or serious, repeat off enders.
The Lauers are the names
of real friends of Larry David.
The next coff ee shop scene
originally opened. . .
. . .with Jerry returning from
the bathroom.
Jerry says the door should be lowered
to the floor unless it's f or ventilation.
George replies, ''I'd take privacy
over ventilation any day.''
To which Jerry opines:
''That, my friend,
is a very personal choice. . .
. . .the need f or privacy versus
the need f or ventilation.
Those are the two greatest needs that
a human being has in a bathroom.''
More cut dialogue had Jerry
and George discussing the fact. . .
. . .that women are much more
comf ortable crying than men.
Jerry: ''They go to movies sometimes
specifically to cry.
Sometimes it'll be advertised.
'It's a good crying movie.'
And they go, 'Let's go.'
They bring their handkerchief,
they love it.''
George then says, ''It's too bad
they're not like babies. . .
. . .where you make funny faces
and they stop.''
George faces the possibility
of make-up sex in ''The Sponge.''
And conjugal-visit sex takes on
a whole new meaning f or George. . .
. . .when he dates a prisoner
in season eight's ''The Little Jerry.''
John Rubano is best known to fans
of Accorfing to Jim as ''John''. . .
. . .on that ABC sitcom.
Evie Peck has also appeared
on Frienfs, G ilmore G irls. . .
. . .and The Young anf the Restless.
Moses was the first rabbi.
The process of rabbinic ordination
is known as semicha.
Once ordained, a rabbi is authorized
to advise and give judgments...
. . . based on his or her understanding
of Jewish law.
We tell you this
so you'll understand why. . .
. . .some viewers
f ound it necessary. . .
. . .to write letters complaining
about Seinfelf's portrayal. . .
. . .of the gossiping rabbi.
The script shows that Jerry
had come to Elaine's apartment. . .
. . . because she was coming along
to see Plan 9.
After explaining
the rabbi 's actions. . .
. . . Jerry then says that the rabbi
was so interesting. . .
. . . he's thinking of joining
his temple.
Elaine then bags the movie because
she no longer f eels like going.
Kasha varnishkas is a Jewish dish
made from raw buckwheat. . .
. . .and thick bowtie egg noodles
cooked with onions and butter.
In a memorable scene
from season six's ''The Doorman''. . .
. . . Frank Costanza climbs into bed
with his son and a bowl of kasha.
That scene also provided
some of the series' best bloopers.
The original script opened
with the rabbi on the phone saying:
''No, I never said that. Yes, I did say
the part about having sex in the car.
But I never mentioned
stealing the CD.
I don't know where
you got that from.''
The scene ends with Elaine
pleading with him. . .
. . . not to mention
what she told him. . .
. . .about illegally deducting
her apartment rent as an office. . .
. . .on her tax return.
The rabbi replies,
''Well, here's the thing. . .
. . .it just so happens an old friend
of mine works f or the IRS.''
Elaine then buries her face
in her hands.
Note the fine acting job
of the pained woman next to Kramer.
It's not acting.
She really was hurt
during this scene.
Of course, this was the funniest take
so her anguish was immortalized.
Kelly Perine (usher) played ''Reggie''
on Provifence. . .
. . .and ''Chuck'' on
The Drew Carey Show.
KRAMER ENTRANCE COUNTER: #243
This storyline parodies
the McDonald 's®. . .
. . .''hot coff ee'' case of 1 992.
A 7 9-year-old retiree,
Stella Liebeck. . .
. . . had third-degree burns when
hot coff ee spilled in her lap.
After eight days in the hospital,
she sued McDonald's® f or damages.
The story made headlines after a jury
awarded the plaintiff $2.7 million.
During appeals,
the case was settled out of court.
It is unlikely she settled
f or free coff ee f or lif e.
McDonald's® typically serves its coff ee
between 1 80° F and 1 90° F.
The coff ee from the location
in question was only 1 58° F.
Home brewers typically heat their joe
between 1 35 ° and 1 40° F.
''The Postponement'' premiered on NBC
on September 28, 1 995.
It scored a 22.7 rating and a 35 share.
Bef ore we go,
here's a little more coff ee trivia:
More than 500 billion cups of coff ee
are guzzled each year.
Did you know that Scandinavia
holds the record. . .
. . .f or highest per capita coff ee
consumption in the world?
Finnish people
drink more than f our cups a day.
Over half of adult Americans drink
at least three and a half cups daily.