This marks the first standup
of season seven.
Monologues were filmed
f or the previous episodes. . .
. . . but not used
due to time constraints.
Check out the ''Master of His Domain''
f eature on this collection. . .
. . .to view Jerry's never-bef ore-seen
standup material.
Mr. Coff ee® began percolating
in American kitchens in 1 972.
It was the first automatic
drip coff eemaker. . .
. . .and quickly became
a bestseller.
The table reading
of ''The Maestro'' took place. . .
. . .on Sunday, August 27, 1 995.
A studio audience was treated
to a live taping. . .
. . .on Wednesday, August 30th.
The history of canning began
with a contest in 1 7 95.
Napoleon off ered a cash prize
f or the invention of a process. . .
. . .that would prevent
his military's f ood from spoiling.
Airtight glass containers
initially took the cake. . .
. . . but were soon replaced
by more durable metal cans.
The first American canning factory
opened in New York in 1 81 2.
Ross is Susan's last name.
The Rosses clothing store
has nothing to do with. . .
. . .the Ross Dress For Less chain
of bargain garments and housewares.
Jackie Chiles is based
on Johnnie Cochran.
Cochran is best known as one
of the key members. . .
. . .of O. J. Simpson's def ense team.
The Louisiana-born Cochran
( 1 937-2005 ) grew up in Los Angeles. . .
. . .and worked as a lawyer
f or over 40 years.
In 1 964, he worked
as district attorney. . .
. . .to prosecute comedian
Lenny Bruce on obscenity charges.
He represented well-known clients
such as Reginald Denny. . .
. . .who was beaten
during the Los Angeles riots. . .
. . .and Haitian immigrant
Abner Louima. . .
. . .the victim of brutality at the hands
of New York policemen.
Phil Morris played Jackie Chiles
in five episodes.
Morris had previously played
a chauff eur on Marbleheaf Manor. . .
. . .a sitcom that also starred
Michael Richards.
Other early television credits
include The Young anf the Restless. . .
. . .and Mission: Impossible
in the 1 980s.
Kramer is describing events from
the last episode, ''The Postponement.''
Morris channeled Cochran
when playing Chiles.
Check out this episode's ''Inside Look''
to learn about Morris' process. . .
. . .and real-lif e encounters
with Cochran.
James Noah plays Susan's Uncle Ned.
His credits include roles
on The Practice. . .
. . .NYPD Blue and Bonanza.
Sitting and staring is a trait
that Elaine shares. . .
. . .with her sometime boyfriend
David Puddy.
KRAMER ENTRANCE COUNTER: #244
''Litigious'' is an adjective
that describes someone. . .
. . .who is ''unreasonably prone
to go to law to settle disputes.''
Whether you call him
the Maestro or Bob Cobb. . .
. . .Mark Metcalf is best known
as Neidermeyer. . .
. . .in the college comedy
Animal House.
He's also appeared in
One Crazy Summer. . .
. . .and The Heavenly Kif.
Fans of hair-metal rock band
Twisted Sister probably remember. . .
. . . his appearance in their video
f or ''We're Not Gonna Take It.''
Tuscany is a region
in west central Italy.
Its capital is Florence,
and it lies on the Ligurian Sea.
If trying to impress your
Italian friends, call it Toscana.
Kramer never completely left the
apartment, so this is not an entrance.
''Flight Of The Bumblebee'' is Nikolai
Rimsky-Korsakov's fast masterpiece.
The piece is the prelude to Act III . . .
. . .of Rimsky-Korsakov's
The Tale of Tsar Saltan.
The retina is the layer
in the back of the eyeball. . .
. . .that contains cells
that react to light. . .
. . .and communicate with the brain
to f orm visual images.
A burned retina would not be good.
Though ''java'' has come to be
synonymous with any kind of coff ee. . .
. . .the word's origins come
from the specific gourmet coff ee. . .
. . .grown on the island of Java
in Indonesia.
Elaine and the Maestro are dining
at New York's Trattoria Dell'Arte.
Located near Carnegie Hall
on Seventh Avenue. . .
. . . between 56th and 57 th Streets. . .
. . .the restaurant is designed
like a Tuscan artist's studio. . .
. . .and f eatures a gallery
of giant noses.
Leonard Bernstein ( 1 91 8- 1 990 ). . .
. . .is perhaps the best-known American
conductor of the 20th century.
He led the prestigious New York
Philharmonic from 1 958 to 1 969.
Bernstein also composed
well-known works. . .
. . .including the scores
f or West Sife Story. . .
. . . On the Town
and On the Waterfront.
A maestro is defined
as a distinguished musician. . .
. . . most often
a classical-music conductor.
The word originates from
1 8th century Italy, meaning ''master.''
It derives from
the Latin word ''magister.''
KRAMER ENTRANCE COUNTER: #245
As you'd expect, Jerry seems to lock
his apartment door overnight. . .
. . . but keeps it unlocked
during the day.
This is not the first appearance of
a Chinese healing product on Seinfelf.
Remember George's
Chinese baldness cure?
You can watch George try to grow hair
in season three's ''The Tape''. . .
. . .available on Volume 4 /Season 3
of Seinfelf on DVD.
WHERE'S NORMAN?
There's Kramer's stand-in,
Norman Brenner, entering the store.
Gary Yates (Security Guard ). . .
. . .is a versatile Canadian-born
writer, director and actor.
You may recognize him from episodes
of In the Heat of the Night. . .
. . .or the f eature film Drumline.
A balm is a fragrant ointment
used to soothe the skin.
''Balm'' is also the name of a tree
that produces a substance. . .
. . .useful f or medicinal purposes.
Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart
( 1 756- 1 7 91 ). . .
. . .did indeed die
while writing the ''Requiem.''
Jerry is ref erring to the 1 984
Oscar®-winning biopic Amafeus. . .
. . .directed by Milos Forman. . .
. . .and starring Tom Hulce
in the title role.
Jerry is likening himself
to Alexander the Great.
The Macedonian king
lived from 356 to 323 BC. . .
. . .and conquered much
of the ancient world.
Richard McGonagle (Mr. Star). . .
. . . has appeared on the NBC
soap opera Days of Our Lives. . .
. . .and the film
Rules of Engagement. . .
. . .with Tommy Lee Jones
and Samuel L. Jackson.
He recently f ound success
doing video game voice-overs. . .
. . .including a lead voice on
Spirit: Stallion of the Cimarron.
Kenneth Ryan (Mr. Burns ) has
also appeared on Kate & Allie. . .
. . .Becker and Law & Orfer.
Kymberly S. Newberry's (Ms. Jordan )
other credits include. . .
. . . The American Presifent, Traffic
and a recurring role on Martin.
The receptionist's voice emanates
from Peggy Lane O'Rourke.
Super fans will recognize her name.
She was Julia Louis-Dreyfus' stand-in
f or all nine seasons of Seinfelf.
Phil Morris is the son
of respected actor Greg Morris.
The elder Morris is perhaps
best known as Barney Collier. . .
. . .on the 1 960s
Mission: Impossible TV series.
It's worth noting that Phil Morris
played Barney Collier's son. . .
. . .Grant Collier, in the late '80s
revival of that series.
Ludwig van Beethoven ( 1 770- 1 827 )
composed his ''Seventh Symphony''. . .
. . .in 1 81 1 in the Czech
spa town of Teplice. . .
. . .while hoping
to improve his health.
The Maestro probably knows
that the piece was also the last. . .
. . .to be conducted
by Leonard Bernstein. . .
. . . less than two months
bef ore his death.
Giuseppe Verdi ( 1 81 3- 1 901 )
was the influential Italian composer. . .
. . .of such masterpieces as
Rigoletto, La Traviata and Aifa.
Elaine is singing the famous ''La donna
é mobile'' from Verdi's Rigoletto.
Another Bob Cobb
invented the Cobb Salad.
One late night in 1 937, Cobb. . .
. . . manager of the famed Brown Derby
restaurant in Hollywood. . .
. . .threw together the contents
of his icebox. . .
. . .and a salad sensation was born.
Tuscany measures
8,877 square miles.
North Dakota measures
70,704 square miles.
Jerry's right: not quite the same.
North Dakota
became a state in 1 889.
The state's capital is Bismarck,
largest city is Fargo. . .
. . .and statewide area code is 701 .
It is bordered by Montana,
South Dakota, Minnesota. . .
. . .and Canadian provinces
Saskatchewan and Manitoba.
See the woman sitting behind Jerry?
That's Carol Brown, Jerry's assistant
during production of the series.
Some material was deleted
from the end of this scene.
In it, George told the waitress
that Jerry would pay their bill. . .
. . .and then left the coff ee shop.
Poppie was last seen
in season six's ''The Doorman.''
In season six,
Jerry uttered the famous line:
''Poppie peed on my sofa!''
In season five,
the health department busted him. . .
. . .f or not washing his hands
in his restaurant, Poppie's.
Elaine and the Maestro are jamming
to Luigi Denza's ''Funiculi Funicula.''
The popular Neapolitan song
is about the excitement. . .
. . .of riding the Mt. Vesuvius funicular,
or inclined railway.
Little Italy runs along
Mulberry Street. . .
. . . between Canal and Spring Streets
in Lower Manhattan.
The neighborhood f eatures about
40 Italian caf és and restaurants. . .
. . .and a famous San Gennaro Festival
each September.
As any coff ee, tea or soda junkie
will tell you. . .
. . .caff eine is a central nervous system
stimulant. . .
. . .that keeps its addicts
awake and alert.
ELAINE BO YFRIEND COUNTER:
#30 - Bob Cobb, the Maestro
Tim Bagley plays Evan Fane,
the store manager.
Fans of Will & Grace
will recognize him as Larry.
He also recurs as Tim
on Accorfing to Jim. . .
. . .and played a memorable Barneys
salesman on Curb Your Enthusiasm.
Paul Michael ( Ciccio )
has recurred on General Hospital. . .
. . .and also appeared on
Hill Street Blues and Kojak.
Around this time
of this episode. . .
. . .about 1 600 Italian lira
equaled one American dollar.
In early 2006,
American tourists visiting Italy. . .
. . .would convert a buck
into .84 Euros.
That's Deck McKenzie
holding his hands up.
He's not only Jerry's stand-in. . .
. . . but has also appeared
in numerous episodes.
We last saw him as a FedEx®
delivery guy in ''The Doorman.''
Julia's stand-in, Peggy Lane,
is also visible in this scene.
''The Maestro'' first aired
on NBC on October 5, 1 995.
The show scored the network
a 22. 5 rating and a 35 share.