A new Seinf eld entered the world
in the summer of 2005.
Shepherd Kellen Seinf eld
joined his big siblings. . .
. . .Sascha and Julian,
on August 22, 2005.
Snooze alarms actually play
a bigger role. . .
. . .in the next episode,
''The Hot Tub.''
But we won't give that away here.
Tom Gammill and Max Pross
penned 1 3 episodes. . .
. . .as one of the show's
most prolific writing teams.
The two joined the staff in
the fifth season after clocking time. . .
. . .in the writing rooms
at Saturfay Night Live. . .
. . .and It's Garry Shanfling's Show.
Among their earlier hits:
''The Glasses,'' ''The Pie,''
and ''The Diplomat's Club.''
The cast first read ''The Wink'' on
Wednesday, September 6, 1 995. . .
. . .after enjoying
Labor Day weekend.
They perf ormed the show in front
of a live studio audience. . .
. . .the next Tuesday, September 1 2th.
The term ''blind date''
originated in the 1 920s.
It was common among students who
would attend a dance or show. . .
. . .with someone previously unknown,
usually the friend of a friend.
Jerry actually did date a deaf woman
in ''The Lip Reader.''
Oscar® winner Marlee Matlin played
Laura, the U.S. Open ball girl. . .
. . .with a knack f or reading lips,
in that fifth-season episode.
It doesn't appear that George
dated a blind woman. . .
. . .during the run of the series, but
we won't rule out the possibility. . .
. . .that it could have happened.
Richard Herd last played Wilhelm
in season six's ''The Jimmy.''
This is his second of 1 1 appearances
as George's Yankee boss.
Herd has amassed quite a credit list
in over 35 years in the business.
He's appeared in dozens of films
and television shows. . .
. . . ranging from The China Synfrome
to T.J. Hooker.
He served as National Vice President
of the Screen Actors Guild.
We find no medical research
backing George's claim that. . .
. . .the grapefruit juice squirted in his
eye caused his involuntary winking.
However, we can off er
the f ollowing medical advice:
If you have a f oreign object in your
eye, start by washing your hands.
Then try to flush the object out. . .
. . . by gently pulling the upper eyelid
over the lower eyelid.
This should cause your eye to tear
and should flush the object out.
Seek medical attention if
this procedure does not work.
Lepers are people inf ected with
the disease known as leprosy.
They reside in leper colonies in
order to prevent the spreading. . .
. . .of the highly contagious disease,
which was originally thought. . .
. . .to be associated with a curse.
Leprosy aff ects the skin,
mucous membranes and nerves. . .
. . .and in severe cases,
causes disfigurement and def ormities.
KRAMER ENTRANCE COUNTER #246
Comic fans will delight
in Kramer's ref erences to Archie.
Archibald Andrews
emerged as a hero in 1 941 .
''Jughead'' is his best friend, Veronica
is the girl with a crush on Archie,
and Mr. Weatherbee is the principal.
Don Mattingly is the award-winning
Yankee first baseman. . .
. . .who wore pinstripes
from 1 982 to 1 995.
Buck Showalter served as Yankee
manager from 1 992 to 1 995.
There really is a Collectors Universe
on 46th Street. . .
. . . between 5th and 6th Avenues
in Manhattan.
Ian Patrick Williams plays Stubs
in this episode.
Williams has appeared on numerous
TV shows, including hits like. . .
. . . Hill Street Blues,
Marrief. . . with Chilfren. . .
. . .and even had a role on
Jason Alexander's early sitcom E / R.
Tom Wright also appeared as Morgan
in the season-six episodes. . .
. . .''The Pledge Drive,''
''The Mom and Pop Store''. . .
. . .and ''The Diplomat's Club.''
ELAINE BO YFRIEND COUNTER:
#3 1 - James, the wake-up-call guy
The Old Homestead Steak House
is known to Manhattan meat-eaters.
The restaurant has been serving up
prime steaks and sides since 1 868.
JERRY GIRLFRIEND COUNTER:
#45 - Holly, Elaine's cousin
Stacey Travis (Holly ) played
Suzanne Zimmerman. . .
. . .cruise director on
The Love Boat: The Next Wave.
Seinfelf was well-represented
aboard the ship: Phil Morris. . .
. . . best known as Jackie Chiles,
played Chief Purser Will Sanders.
Fans of the ''The Switch'' may
remember Clive Rosengren (Waiter).
He played Mr. Clotworthy in
that sixth-season episode.
A frequent TV guest star,
his credits range from. . .
. . . The A-Team
to Beverly Hills, 902 10.
Rosengren's also worked
with bigtime film directors. . .
. . .Tim Burton in Ef Woof
and Barry Levinson in Bugsy.
Additional dialogue was written
to end this scene.
In it, Elaine asks James if
he wants to get together again.
He replies: ''Uh, I'll call you in the
morning. It's my job. Remember?''
The ''quiche thing'' Jerry
mentions here is a ref erence. . .
. . .to a 1 982 best-selling book
by Bruce Feirstein called
Real Men Don't Eat Quiche.
The book was a satirical guide to
living lif e as a macho manly man.
Feirstein knows what makes
a ''real man.'' He went on to write. . .
. . .three screenplays f or the ultimate
masculine character, James Bond.
Elaine originally added grapefruit to
the list of sub-manly f ood choices.
It's not a big surprise that Kramer
pegged George as Mr. Weatherbee.
''The Bee'' shared George's stocky,
bald, bespectacled f eatures. . .
. . .as well as his shorter height.
Stacey Travis also has
quite a list of films to her credit.
They include: The Muse,
Traffic and Ghost Worlf.
Thomas Dekker has worked steadily
since his appearance as Bobby
in this episode.
Actually, his Seinfelf career
began in season five. . .
. . .when he appeared in
''The Stand-In.''
Since then he's appeared on TV shows
ranging from Star Tre k: Voyager. . .
. . .to Grosse Pointe
and CSI to 7 th Heaven.
Dekker's also logged many hours
in sound studios. . .
. . . lending his voice to animated hits
like The Lanf Before Time. . .
. . .and An American Tail series.
Mutton, lamb and hogget
all ref er to sheep meat.
The terms have taken on diff erent
meanings in various cultures. . .
. . . but lamb meat typically comes
from young animals. . .
. . .while mutton and hogget
come from older, fattier sheep.
Mutton tends to be more flavorful
than lamb and is often used in stews.
Julia was scripted to say ''thanks
f or the mutton'' bef ore she exits.
She dropped the ''the,''
and a new joke was born.
Comedy writers ref er to the last joke
in a sitcom scene as ''the blow.''
Brian McNamara (James )
costarred in the NBC sitcom
that bumped Seinfelf. . .
. . .to make it on the network's
1 989 calendar, The Nutt House.
For more on Seinfelf's
unusual start, check out. . .
. . .the ''How It Began'' documentary
on Volume 1 of Seinfelf on DVD.
McNamara has worked consistently
on both the big and small screens.
He's played leads in Short Circuit. . .
. . . The Flamingo Kif, Caffyshack II
and Arachnophobia.
More recently he's had a recurring
role on Fox's smash hit The O. C.
He also guest-starred on an episode
of It's Like, You Know. . .
. . .created by Seinfelf writer
Peter Mehlman.
Foot f etishists have
earmarked this scene. . .
. . .as one of their favorites
of the season.
KL5 is another name f or 555, the
standard prefix f or made-up numbers.
This abbreviation is known
as a telephone exchange.
Most Americans recited their numbers
using the letter/ number combo. . .
. . .from the 1 930s to the 1 950s.
The practice was quite common
in Manhattan. . .
. . .and it seems New Yorker habits
die hard.
In India and other Eastern nations,
the term mutton often ref ers. . .
. . .to goat meat
rather than sheep meat.
Mutton curries are
specialties of Indian cuisine.
Paul O'Neill took over first base
from Don Mattingly.
He played f or the Yankees
from 1 993 to 2001 .
A five-time All-Star, f our of his
fingers wear World Series rings.
The actors and crew shot this scene
ahead of the rest of the season. . .
. . .on Saturday, August 1 9, 1 995.
They did so to take advantage of
a Yankee visit to nearby Anaheim. . .
. . .and utilized
the stadium's locker room.
The Yankees played the Angels
that night, losing 5 to 3.
Paul O'Neill played
but went 0 f or 4.
As he did in season six's
''The Chaperone''. . .
. . .Yankee announcer Bob Sheppard
recorded this voiceover.
Deleted dialogue reveals that Jerry
was drinking ginger ale in this scene.
Thomas Dekker had roles on
The Young anf the Restless
and Star Tre k: Generations.
He starred in the TV series based on
the film Honey, I Shrunk the Kifs.
He even played young Donny Osmond
in Insife the Osmonfs.
The Yankees didn't play
when this aired.
The Mariners won the pennant.
But O'Neill homered in game five.
As many schoolchildren could
tell you, 503 years prior. . .
. . .to the day that this episode aired,
October 1 2, 1 995. . .
. . .Christopher Columbus
reached the New World.
On the same day in 1 960,
Russian leader Nikita Khrushchev. . .
. . .threw his infamous tantrum
at the United Nations. . .
. . . pounding his shoe on the table.
Civil war buffs probably already know
that Conf ederate army commander. . .
. . . Robert E. Lee passed away on
the same day in 1 870.
Now you know too.
History off ers a f ew
compelling stories. . .
. . .of pro ball players
promising home runs to sick kids.
In 1 926, Babe Ruth promised an ailing
1 1 -year-old, Johnny Sylvester. . .
. . .a home run during an
October World Series game. . .
. . .against the St. Louis Cardinals.
The Bambino smacked not one,
not two, but three homers that day.
He even sent one ball soaring out
of the park and right through. . .
. . .the window of a car dealership
behind the stadium.
Film history also off ers
a similar tale.
In the 1 942 biopic
The Prife of the Yankees. . .
. . . Lou Gehrig (played by Gary Cooper)
promises a hospitalized boy. . .
. . .that he'll hit two home runs
in a World Series game.
Gehrig makes good
and little Billy walks again.
Inside-the-park home runs
are rare in the majors.
The ball does not clear
the outfield f ence and the batter. . .
. . . makes it home without
any errors committed in the field.
Major League Baseball
defines an error as f ollows:
''An error shall be charged
f or each misplay
( fumble, muff or wild throw ). . .
. . .which prolongs
the time at bat of a batter. . .
. . .or which prolongs
the lif e of a runner. . .
. . .or which permits a runner
to advance one or more bases.''
Angioplasty is a medical procedure
in which surgeons. . .
. . .open a narrow coronary artery
using a balloon.
A stent, or wire-mesh tube,
is placed at the narrowed section. . .
. . .during the procedure.
If timed correctly, angioplasty is
a pref erred treatment. . .
. . .f or heart-attack patients.
Major League Baseball defines
a catch as ''the act of a fielder. . .
. . .of getting secure possession in
his hand or glove of a ball in flight. . .
. . .and firmly holding it, providing he
does not use his cap, protector. . .
. . . pocket or any other part of
his unif orm in getting possession.''
So the hat catch requested
wouldn't exactly count.
This episode winked at NBC audiences
f or the first time at 9 p. m. . .
. . .on Thursday, October 1 2, 1 995.
''The Wink'' scored a 22. 3 rating
with a 34 share.
Here's some industry
insider inf o f or you:
The scene broadcast over a show's
closing credits is called ''the tag.''
The tag f or this episode f eatures
George and Mr. Steinbrenner.
Steinbrenner's ramble includes a list
of the many baseball managers. . .
. . . he's fired since becoming
the team owner in 1 972.
It ends with a mention
of Buck Showalter. . .
. . .who would be fired on
November 2, 1 995. . .
. . . less than three weeks
after this episode debuted.
Joe Torre replaced Showalter
the next season.
It was a good move.
Torre went on to lead the Yanks
to f our World Series titles.