1
00:00:09,927 --> 00:00:14,805
NARRATOR: £G£o£t£h£a£m £C£i£t£y£,
<i>Woodrow Roosevelt High School.</i>

2
00:00:17,559 --> 00:00:19,769
<i>Three-oh-nine p.m.</i>

3
00:00:19,937 --> 00:00:24,607
<i>Normal healthy activity</i>
<i>in the school gymnasium.</i>

4
00:00:38,330 --> 00:00:40,122
-You got it memorized?
-Think so.

5
00:00:40,290 --> 00:00:41,332
Okay, Iet's go.

6
00:00:41,500 --> 00:00:42,708
[WHISTLE BLOWS]

7
00:00:43,961 --> 00:00:48,464
ALL:
<i>And zing-boom-sis-boom-bah</i>

8
00:00:49,091 --> 00:00:52,552
<i>We're from Woodrow Roosevelt</i>
<i>That's who we are</i>

9
00:00:52,761 --> 00:00:56,556
<i>Does anybody scare us?</i>
<i>The answer is nix</i>

10
00:00:56,765 --> 00:01:00,434
<i>Come on, team</i>
<i>Let's make it six</i>

11
00:01:00,602 --> 00:01:02,478
[CHEERLEADERS AND
AUDIENCE CHEERING]

12
00:01:02,646 --> 00:01:04,855
MAN 1 : That was great. Great.
MAN 2: Okay.

13
00:01:06,358 --> 00:01:07,942
Gosh, Susie, terrific.

14
00:01:08,110 --> 00:01:10,027
-Did you write it yourseIf?
-Oh, heck, no.

15
00:01:10,195 --> 00:01:11,821
Ms. Browning, our poetry professor.

16
00:01:11,989 --> 00:01:16,158
-Let's take a break, gang. Anyone for a drink?
-Me.

17
00:01:23,584 --> 00:01:24,709
[VENDING MACHINE CLANGING]

18
00:01:27,963 --> 00:01:31,507
HoIy cow. Look, siIver dolIars.

19
00:01:31,675 --> 00:01:33,926
Let me try.

20
00:01:36,221 --> 00:01:37,888
[COINS CLANGING]

21
00:01:39,891 --> 00:01:43,561
Hey, kids, everyone. Come on.
It's Christmas. Look, heh.

22
00:01:50,777 --> 00:01:52,737
GORDON:
SiIver doIIars.

23
00:01:53,030 --> 00:01:57,325
A strange, disturbing bonanza
from a gimmick milk machine.

24
00:01:57,618 --> 00:02:00,745
Either of you men fear what I fear?

25
00:02:01,913 --> 00:02:04,915
-The Joker?
-Exactly, Chief O'Hara, the Joker.

26
00:02:05,083 --> 00:02:10,129
That most pestiIent of predators,
the CIown Prince of Crime.

27
00:02:10,339 --> 00:02:13,090
This smeIIs Iike an opening gambit of his.

28
00:02:13,258 --> 00:02:14,634
That devil.

29
00:02:14,843 --> 00:02:18,137
-But how can we be sure?
-We can't. Not yet.

30
00:02:18,347 --> 00:02:20,056
But if it's the Joker we're facing...

31
00:02:20,265 --> 00:02:24,226
...and his pIot is aimed at Gotham City youth,
we can't wait to be sure.

32
00:02:24,686 --> 00:02:30,983
This, if there ever was one, is a case
for our unknown friend behind the mask.

33
00:02:40,786 --> 00:02:41,827
[BEEPING]

34
00:02:41,995 --> 00:02:43,496
NARRATOR:
<i>And in Wayne Manor...</i>

35
00:02:43,664 --> 00:02:46,874
<i>...stately residence</i>
<i>of millionaire socialite Bruce Wayne...</i>

36
00:02:47,042 --> 00:02:52,254
<i>...and his young ward, Dick Grayson,</i>
<i>whom we just saw at school:</i>

37
00:02:58,053 --> 00:03:03,349
Please, Bruce, I beg you.
Accept the proposaI. Run for mayor.

38
00:03:03,558 --> 00:03:08,104
It's funny. They come to you
with the same offer every two years.

39
00:03:08,271 --> 00:03:11,482
You'd think they'd get it through their heads
you're not interested.

40
00:03:12,109 --> 00:03:14,318
I'm afraid she's right, Mr. VandergiIt.

41
00:03:14,528 --> 00:03:16,862
You see, the good works
of my Wayne Foundation...

42
00:03:17,030 --> 00:03:20,032
...require that I stay above
the brawI of politics.

43
00:03:20,200 --> 00:03:22,743
But Gotham City needs you.

44
00:03:22,911 --> 00:03:24,578
Think of our problems.

45
00:03:24,746 --> 00:03:31,043
The snarl of traffic, a water shortage,
and now these recurrent power failures.

46
00:03:31,628 --> 00:03:33,003
How can you turn us down?

47
00:03:33,171 --> 00:03:34,714
[ALFRED CLEARS THROAT]

48
00:03:34,881 --> 00:03:36,006
HARRIET:
What is it, AIfred?

49
00:03:36,675 --> 00:03:39,260
Nothing of importance, madam.

50
00:03:40,804 --> 00:03:45,683
-It's the Batphone, sir.
-Thank you, AIfred, for reminding me.

51
00:03:45,892 --> 00:03:48,018
I'II teIl you what, Mr. VandergiIt.

52
00:03:48,186 --> 00:03:52,231
I'II ponder it
and give you my answer tomorrow.

53
00:03:52,566 --> 00:03:56,652
Aunt Harriet, give Mr. VandergiIt
some more tea, wiII you?

54
00:03:58,530 --> 00:04:03,117
He'II ponder it? That's strange.
What's he got to ponder?

55
00:04:03,702 --> 00:04:05,953
-Yes, commissioner.
<i>£G£O£R£D£O£N£: Prepare yourself for a blow.</i>

56
00:04:06,455 --> 00:04:08,581
Someone has struck
at Woodrow Roosevelt High.

57
00:04:08,749 --> 00:04:10,207
We think it's the Joker.

58
00:04:10,625 --> 00:04:13,753
Good grief. I'm on my way.

59
00:04:15,172 --> 00:04:18,883
Dick's in the thick of this aIready.
If he phones in, teII him to stay where he is.

60
00:04:19,050 --> 00:04:21,051
-Very good, sir.
-The switch, AIfred.

61
00:04:22,929 --> 00:04:24,722
Good Iuck, sir.

62
00:05:17,442 --> 00:05:19,193
[ENGINE ROARS AND TIRES SCREECH]

63
00:05:54,604 --> 00:05:57,022
Looks sinister, doesn't it?

64
00:05:57,232 --> 00:06:00,150
"Joker reIeased from jaiI one week ago...

65
00:06:00,360 --> 00:06:04,655
...immediately buys controI
of One-Armed Bandit NoveIty Company."

66
00:06:04,865 --> 00:06:06,782
Makers of coin-operated gadgets.

67
00:06:06,950 --> 00:06:09,910
Gum machines, pin baIls,
that sort of harmIess junk.

68
00:06:10,078 --> 00:06:13,414
There's nothing harmIess about the Joker.
We alI know that.

69
00:06:13,665 --> 00:06:18,460
Or about a machine which returns
20 siIver dolIars for a dime.

70
00:06:18,670 --> 00:06:21,547
What about the men who instalI the machine
and service it?

71
00:06:21,715 --> 00:06:25,134
CIean as driven snow, Batman.
And they're even more surprised than we are.

72
00:06:25,302 --> 00:06:30,055
It's open-and-shut. Somebody got to that
poor innocent machine and gimmicked it.

73
00:06:30,223 --> 00:06:34,018
But why? In the deviI's name, why?

74
00:06:34,269 --> 00:06:36,312
I can make a guess.

75
00:06:36,521 --> 00:06:37,688
[PHONE BUZZES]

76
00:06:37,856 --> 00:06:39,440
Yes?

77
00:06:39,608 --> 00:06:42,443
Oh, thank you, Bonnie.
Put him on the conference phone.

78
00:06:42,611 --> 00:06:46,196
It's PrincipaI SchooIfieId,
Woodrow Roosevelt High.

79
00:06:48,116 --> 00:06:49,867
SCHOOLFIELD: £C£o£m£m£i£s£s£i£o£n£e£r £G£o£r£d£o£n£?
-Speaking.

80
00:06:50,076 --> 00:06:53,996
Another machine has gone mad,
in the Iibrary.

81
00:06:54,205 --> 00:06:58,542
Instead of candy bars,
it's dispensing negotiabIe stocks and bonds.

82
00:06:59,210 --> 00:07:02,087
<i>To put it mildly,</i>
<i>student morale is cracking up.</i>

83
00:07:02,255 --> 00:07:05,758
SchooIfield. This is Batman here.
Do you hear me?

84
00:07:05,926 --> 00:07:07,885
SCHOOLFIELD:
<i>Ah, yes. Hello, Batman.</i>

85
00:07:08,053 --> 00:07:10,054
Who's the president
of your student counciI?

86
00:07:10,221 --> 00:07:13,140
A boy named Grayson, a Richard Grayson.

87
00:07:13,350 --> 00:07:16,435
<i>-A fine lad.</i>
-I'm gIad to hear it.

88
00:07:16,645 --> 00:07:19,980
Have him caIl a meeting in your office.
I'II be right there.

89
00:07:20,231 --> 00:07:23,859
I'II have him waiting for you. Goodbye.

90
00:07:24,069 --> 00:07:26,904
-I think my guess was right.
-What, Batman?

91
00:07:27,072 --> 00:07:28,113
No time to Iose.

92
00:07:28,281 --> 00:07:30,699
Chief O'Hara,
get me a visuaI ID fiIe on the Joker.

93
00:07:30,867 --> 00:07:33,619
-Meet me at the BatmobiIe.
-Yes, sir.

94
00:07:39,751 --> 00:07:42,920
I mean, like Iook, Dickie.
So everyone's goofing off.

95
00:07:43,129 --> 00:07:45,506
-So why shouIdn't they?
-It's quite true.

96
00:07:45,757 --> 00:07:49,218
The purpose of our studies is to equip us
to make our way in Iife.

97
00:07:49,386 --> 00:07:53,555
If, on the other hand, one has mereIy
to insert a dime in a machine--

98
00:07:53,765 --> 00:07:56,850
He's right. Why go through alI that study?

99
00:07:57,018 --> 00:07:59,603
For crying out Ioud.
I'm surprised at you guys.

100
00:07:59,813 --> 00:08:01,981
We're meant to be student Ieaders.

101
00:08:02,190 --> 00:08:03,899
Susie, what do you say?

102
00:08:04,109 --> 00:08:09,279
I say, has anyone tried
Mr. SchooIfieId's coffee machine?

103
00:08:11,783 --> 00:08:13,367
[COINS CLANGING]

104
00:08:14,995 --> 00:08:16,036
[CHUCKLES]

105
00:08:16,204 --> 00:08:21,125
Hey, not bad for oId SchoolfieId.
Quarters. Look.

106
00:08:21,334 --> 00:08:24,086
-Hey, not bad, eh?
-How about that?

107
00:08:24,295 --> 00:08:26,714
Wise up, you guys. Life isn't this easy.

108
00:08:26,881 --> 00:08:29,591
That's easy for you to say.
You're the ward of that rich miIlionaire.

109
00:08:29,759 --> 00:08:30,801
[BATMOBILE APPROACHES]

110
00:08:30,969 --> 00:08:35,097
-That has nothing to do with it.
-Hey, gang, cut it out. Here comes Batman.

111
00:08:43,023 --> 00:08:45,399
[SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]

112
00:08:46,443 --> 00:08:48,485
GIRL 1 : Robin. He's here.
GIRL 2: It's Batman.

113
00:08:48,653 --> 00:08:50,195
Sorry, kids. Stay back.

114
00:08:50,363 --> 00:08:51,739
Sorry, Robin isn't with me.

115
00:08:51,906 --> 00:08:55,701
This BatmobiIe is fiIled
with deIicate anti-crime equipment.

116
00:08:55,910 --> 00:08:58,871
You might set off
the automatic antitheft system.

117
00:08:59,039 --> 00:09:01,165
Nobody cIoser than 50 feet, pIease.

118
00:09:01,332 --> 00:09:03,167
Hey, Batman, where's Robin?

119
00:09:03,376 --> 00:09:05,836
BATMAN: Attending school just as you are.
-What school?

120
00:09:06,004 --> 00:09:09,757
I can't teII you that.
It might reveaI his secret true identity.

121
00:09:09,966 --> 00:09:13,969
And Iisten, if anyone hears a sharp beep,
let me know at once.

122
00:09:14,179 --> 00:09:18,223
It'lI be the Batphone ringing
with an important message.

123
00:09:26,775 --> 00:09:29,985
NARRATOR:
<i>And even as Batman races into the school...</i>

124
00:09:30,195 --> 00:09:34,490
<i>...across town in a fashionable little bistro:</i>

125
00:09:54,052 --> 00:09:55,636
[JOKER LAUGHS ON RECORDING]

126
00:09:55,804 --> 00:10:01,183
JOKER [ON RECORDING]: £T£h£e£j£o£k£e£'£s £o£n £y£o£u£,
<i>my cheery boozehounds. It's a stickup.</i>

127
00:10:03,061 --> 00:10:05,395
<i>Hands up. You're covered.</i>

128
00:10:05,563 --> 00:10:07,481
[CLICKING]

129
00:10:22,288 --> 00:10:26,917
<i>Thanks, folks. The party will now resume.</i>

130
00:10:31,673 --> 00:10:34,675
BeIieve me, this may Iook Iike a party,
but it's not.

131
00:10:34,926 --> 00:10:36,677
There's a crook behind these handouts.

132
00:10:36,928 --> 00:10:39,221
-What's his angle?
-He may have severaI.

133
00:10:39,430 --> 00:10:42,558
One is to lure you into a deceptive pattern
of easy Iiving.

134
00:10:42,725 --> 00:10:45,435
You'II quit your studies, become dropouts.

135
00:10:45,645 --> 00:10:49,064
You'II have no other recourse
but to join criminaI groups.

136
00:10:49,274 --> 00:10:52,151
Batman's right. It's sort of recruiting drive.

137
00:10:52,318 --> 00:10:53,986
Sure, he's right. What'd I teIl you?

138
00:10:54,154 --> 00:10:58,740
-Can you corroborate this odd hypothesis?
-Yeah, Batman. Like, what's the crook's name?

139
00:10:58,950 --> 00:11:01,702
I can do better than that.
I can show you his picture.

140
00:11:01,870 --> 00:11:03,954
-What's your name, son?
-Richard Grayson, sir.

141
00:11:04,122 --> 00:11:07,082
Thank you, Richard. You darken the room.
I'II man the projector.

142
00:11:07,250 --> 00:11:08,792
Roger.

143
00:11:12,046 --> 00:11:15,799
Here it is, everybody. The Joker.

144
00:11:16,634 --> 00:11:20,095
Don't be deceived by that grin, anyone.

145
00:11:20,305 --> 00:11:24,016
He's one of the most malevolent malefactors
we've ever met.

146
00:11:24,225 --> 00:11:28,145
-I'II bet he's a master of makeup too.
-You're right, he is.

147
00:11:28,354 --> 00:11:33,358
He might be skuIking around here
in any one of 50 outrageous outfits.

148
00:11:33,568 --> 00:11:36,820
For example, here's another one.

149
00:11:37,697 --> 00:11:39,406
Get a IittIe closer, kids.

150
00:11:39,574 --> 00:11:43,035
I want you to see that phony fIower
in his button hoIe.

151
00:11:47,290 --> 00:11:51,251
Sometimes, it shoots out water,
sometimes powder...

152
00:11:52,503 --> 00:11:54,838
...other times knockout gas.

153
00:11:55,423 --> 00:11:58,675
-Hey.
-HoIy magician.

154
00:11:59,636 --> 00:12:01,178
[LAUGHING]

155
00:12:01,638 --> 00:12:05,807
HeIlo, kiddies. Meet the Joker.

156
00:12:06,017 --> 00:12:07,351
No hard feeIings.

157
00:12:07,518 --> 00:12:09,686
[BUZZING AND HERBIE YELLS]
[JOKER LAUGHING]

158
00:12:09,854 --> 00:12:13,023
-Corny, aren't I?
-Joker, what are you doing here?

159
00:12:13,191 --> 00:12:15,150
Oh, just passing by. I heard my name...

160
00:12:15,360 --> 00:12:19,863
...and I couIdn't resist shooting a joIly jet
through the tiny perforation in that screen.

161
00:12:20,031 --> 00:12:22,324
Just passing by, huh? To do what?

162
00:12:22,533 --> 00:12:24,743
Gimmick another innocent
vending machine?

163
00:12:25,078 --> 00:12:27,871
Oh, there must be bats in your beIfry,
Batman.

164
00:12:28,039 --> 00:12:31,083
Has anyone found fingerprints
or other evidence?

165
00:12:31,251 --> 00:12:32,793
You're too smart for that, Joker.

166
00:12:33,086 --> 00:12:34,628
Hey, Batman, nab him anyway.

167
00:12:34,796 --> 00:12:36,838
Loitering on schooI property.

168
00:12:37,048 --> 00:12:40,384
Right. Five-thousand doIIars fine
and five years imprisonment.

169
00:12:40,551 --> 00:12:43,428
Ha, ha. No. Wrong, kiddies.

170
00:12:43,638 --> 00:12:46,682
Look up the statute.
In Gotham City, the crime of Ioitering...

171
00:12:46,849 --> 00:12:51,895
...requires the loiterer to remain
in the same spot for over two minutes.

172
00:12:52,313 --> 00:12:55,816
You.... You jaiIhouse Iawyer.

173
00:12:55,984 --> 00:12:57,943
The tricky trickster, he's outwitting us.

174
00:12:59,112 --> 00:13:04,157
Ooh, dear me.
The court jester must run, jest in time.

175
00:13:04,325 --> 00:13:05,450
[LAUGHS]

176
00:13:05,618 --> 00:13:09,663
WelI, goodbye, kiddies.
And remember, I was here, eh?

177
00:13:09,831 --> 00:13:11,748
[LAUGHING]

178
00:13:13,167 --> 00:13:14,710
What an odd parting remark.

179
00:13:14,877 --> 00:13:17,212
Yeah. Why'd he want us to remember
he was here?

180
00:13:18,506 --> 00:13:23,260
From the lips of a crook,
it can mean only one thing.

181
00:13:23,469 --> 00:13:25,429
-EstabIishing an aIibi.
-Right.

182
00:13:25,888 --> 00:13:28,473
Gee whiz. AIibi for what?

183
00:13:38,192 --> 00:13:39,234
[BEEPING]

184
00:13:40,194 --> 00:13:42,487
The Batphone signaI. Batman!

185
00:13:42,655 --> 00:13:45,115
Hey, Batman, it's your Batphone.

186
00:13:45,283 --> 00:13:47,951
The Batphone, Batman.

187
00:13:59,672 --> 00:14:01,715
-What now, commissioner?
GORDON: £A£n£o£t£h£e£r £s£t£r£i£k£e£.

188
00:14:01,883 --> 00:14:05,719
A cocktaiI Iounge. A gimmick jukebox.
It must be the Joker.

189
00:14:05,928 --> 00:14:08,138
We'II never make it stick. He has an alibi.

190
00:14:08,348 --> 00:14:11,433
<i>£G£O£R£D£O£N£: Maybe we can break it.</i>
-ImpossibIe. The alibi is me.

191
00:14:11,642 --> 00:14:13,101
What? You?

192
00:14:13,269 --> 00:14:17,147
Forget it. Give me the address.
I'II race to the scene of the crime.

193
00:14:17,565 --> 00:14:19,274
Right. Goodbye.

194
00:14:19,442 --> 00:14:20,901
DICK:
Batman, sir.

195
00:14:22,362 --> 00:14:23,779
You forgot your box of sIides.

196
00:14:23,946 --> 00:14:25,155
Good Iad. Bring it over.

197
00:14:30,495 --> 00:14:33,497
Fake a headache. Speed home.
Wait for me in the Batcave.

198
00:14:33,706 --> 00:14:35,207
You're welcome, sir.

199
00:14:39,170 --> 00:14:44,174
Boys and girIs, go back to your studies.
BeIieve me, nothing in Iife is free.

200
00:15:06,572 --> 00:15:12,369
<i>£N£A£R£R£A£T£O£R£: Scarcely 500 yards away,</i>
<i>behind this innocent-seeming candy store...</i>

201
00:15:12,578 --> 00:15:15,664
<i>...an abandoned garage,</i>
<i>now headquarters of the Joker...</i>

202
00:15:15,832 --> 00:15:19,251
<i>...and his current gang the Bad Pennies,</i>
<i>high-school dropouts most of them.</i>

203
00:15:19,419 --> 00:15:20,752
[JOKER LAUGHING]

204
00:15:20,920 --> 00:15:24,881
-It's a pretty good haul, isn't it?
-Peanuts, my boy. Mere peanuts.

205
00:15:25,049 --> 00:15:29,094
That bar job was just a pot-boiIing appetizer
for the reaI feast.

206
00:15:29,303 --> 00:15:32,013
Ho, ho! What an inspired stroke of mine...

207
00:15:32,181 --> 00:15:36,351
...buying up the One-Armed Bandit
Novelty Company. Ah.

208
00:15:36,519 --> 00:15:38,353
Plunder by remote controI.

209
00:15:38,521 --> 00:15:39,563
[BOTH LAUGHING]

210
00:15:39,730 --> 00:15:42,816
Hey, Joker. I think I got this one rigged.
Come and have a Iook.

211
00:15:43,234 --> 00:15:46,027
-Put it alI away.
-Right.

212
00:15:47,947 --> 00:15:49,614
Set to go off on the third strike?

213
00:15:49,824 --> 00:15:51,658
Yeah, and I got two strikes rung up already.

214
00:15:51,826 --> 00:15:55,203
Ho, ho! Here we go.

215
00:15:59,333 --> 00:16:01,168
SensationaI. It's a gas.

216
00:16:01,335 --> 00:16:04,337
It won't be colored smoke in a bar,
it'II be your knockout stuff.

217
00:16:04,505 --> 00:16:06,339
-You've done it again, Two Bits.
-Thanks.

218
00:16:06,507 --> 00:16:07,757
[BUZZING AND TWO BITS YELLS]

219
00:16:07,925 --> 00:16:08,967
[JOKER LAUGHS]

220
00:16:09,135 --> 00:16:12,804
A timely reminder. Crime can be shocking.

221
00:16:12,972 --> 00:16:14,848
[JOKER LAUGHS THEN HORN HONKS]

222
00:16:15,433 --> 00:16:18,185
Someone's trying the bubbIe-gum machine.

223
00:16:23,691 --> 00:16:24,774
Hi, gang.

224
00:16:24,942 --> 00:16:29,488
Ah, sweet Sue, shiniest of my Bad Pennies.

225
00:16:29,655 --> 00:16:33,658
Boy, Joker, you sure are some card,
popping out at schooI Iike that at Batman.

226
00:16:33,868 --> 00:16:36,495
WondrousIy whimsicaI, wasn't it?

227
00:16:36,662 --> 00:16:38,914
It was reaI crazy, if you asked me.

228
00:16:39,081 --> 00:16:41,500
I might have fainted
and given the whoIe game away.

229
00:16:41,667 --> 00:16:42,834
However, you didn't.

230
00:16:43,002 --> 00:16:45,629
-Ah! I see you have the stuff.
-Of course.

231
00:16:45,796 --> 00:16:47,839
-Any trouble getting it?
-Heck, no.

232
00:16:48,007 --> 00:16:51,426
Like I toId you, being chief cheerIeader
puts me on the student counciI.

233
00:16:51,594 --> 00:16:53,595
Once you're on that,
you can get away with anything.

234
00:16:53,763 --> 00:16:55,430
Ho, ho! Let's see.

235
00:16:55,598 --> 00:16:58,391
Hands off. Not untiI I get paid.

236
00:16:58,559 --> 00:17:01,811
Trusting IittIe wench, aren't you?

237
00:17:02,021 --> 00:17:04,523
I'm a crook, Joker, just Iike you.

238
00:17:04,690 --> 00:17:05,815
Now, where's the payoff?

239
00:17:05,983 --> 00:17:07,317
[JOKER GRUMBLES]

240
00:17:09,904 --> 00:17:13,990
-Hi there, Iamb chop. You busy tonight?
-You IowIife, get away from me.

241
00:17:14,158 --> 00:17:17,786
-Now, Iook here, baby. I have plans--
-Are you stupid or something?

242
00:17:17,995 --> 00:17:22,082
The reason I've taken up crime
is so I can get a taste of the finer things in life.

243
00:17:22,291 --> 00:17:23,333
-Yeah--
-Now, beat it.

244
00:17:23,501 --> 00:17:24,543
[GRUNTS]

245
00:17:24,710 --> 00:17:27,837
Ha, ha. Shut your eyes, sweet Susie.

246
00:17:28,005 --> 00:17:31,925
Oh, yeah? And get an expIoding cigar
in my ear? No thanks.

247
00:17:32,093 --> 00:17:35,929
You mischievous bobette.
Shut your eyes, I said.

248
00:17:38,808 --> 00:17:41,017
A rhinestone bracelet...

249
00:17:41,602 --> 00:17:43,520
...a fox-fur stoIe...

250
00:17:43,688 --> 00:17:48,400
...and one fulI quart
of imported Mexican perfume.

251
00:17:48,568 --> 00:17:51,861
Oh. Oh, gee, Joker.

252
00:17:52,071 --> 00:17:55,323
I'm sorry I sassed you.

253
00:17:58,160 --> 00:18:01,705
Why, this is Iike some IoveIy dream.

254
00:18:03,457 --> 00:18:08,003
Ah, perfect.
Stolen right from SchooIfield's safe...

255
00:18:08,170 --> 00:18:10,922
...the keycard
to my malevolent machinations.

256
00:18:11,090 --> 00:18:15,302
-WelI, what is it, Joker?
-Look, you boobs. Look and laugh.

257
00:18:15,511 --> 00:18:17,554
Examination papers.

258
00:18:17,722 --> 00:18:19,764
[ALL LAUGHING]

259
00:18:22,518 --> 00:18:27,188
X plus Y times X pIus Y.

260
00:18:27,356 --> 00:18:29,399
HoIy alphabet. What is it?

261
00:18:29,567 --> 00:18:32,277
ALFRED: If you'II excuse me, Master Robin.
-Yes, AIfred?

262
00:18:32,486 --> 00:18:37,157
The soIution is, uh,
X squared pIus 2XY pIus Y squared.

263
00:18:37,325 --> 00:18:39,909
Gee, sure. Why didn't I know that?

264
00:18:40,077 --> 00:18:43,663
And with nationwide pre-coIlege exams
coming up in just three days.

265
00:18:55,217 --> 00:18:57,385
ALFRED:
Good to have you home, sir.

266
00:18:57,553 --> 00:18:59,512
-What'd you find out, Batman?
-Nothing.

267
00:18:59,722 --> 00:19:01,181
HoIy vacuum. Not a singIe clue?

268
00:19:01,349 --> 00:19:04,184
We don't need clues, Robin.
We know our man is the Joker.

269
00:19:04,393 --> 00:19:06,186
What we need is evidence.

270
00:19:06,395 --> 00:19:09,189
I went over that Iooted Iounge
with a fine-tooth comb.

271
00:19:09,398 --> 00:19:11,566
I didn't even find a singIe hair to anaIyze.

272
00:19:12,068 --> 00:19:14,736
Gosh, and school moraIe in a tailspin.

273
00:19:14,904 --> 00:19:17,364
A month from now
there'II be dropouts by the busheI.

274
00:19:17,531 --> 00:19:19,366
BATMAN: If he waits that Iong.
-Huh?

275
00:19:19,533 --> 00:19:22,702
I didn't want to cause panic
at that student meeting...

276
00:19:22,870 --> 00:19:26,915
...but I think the Joker has
some other dirty pIan afoot as weII.

277
00:19:27,083 --> 00:19:28,708
-Like what?
-I don't know.

278
00:19:29,377 --> 00:19:33,254
But I think it invoIves gimmicked machines
and Woodrow Roosevelt High.

279
00:19:33,798 --> 00:19:36,424
Gee, if we just knew
how he gets in to fix them.

280
00:19:36,592 --> 00:19:38,885
You've guessed it, Robin. Our next move.

281
00:19:39,053 --> 00:19:42,263
-Stake out the schooI.
-Right again. Let's go.

282
00:19:58,614 --> 00:20:01,950
[BATMOBILE APPROACHING]

283
00:20:18,759 --> 00:20:19,884
[CHUCKLES]

284
00:20:20,052 --> 00:20:21,386
[PHONE RINGS]

285
00:20:21,554 --> 00:20:23,888
HeIlo, helIo? Give me the sign.

286
00:20:24,056 --> 00:20:26,266
How do you stop a dog
from barking in JuIy?

287
00:20:26,851 --> 00:20:31,271
Countersign: Shoot him in June. Very good.
Ha-ha-ha.

288
00:20:31,522 --> 00:20:34,899
Joker, Iisten. Batman and Robin
just drove into the parking Iot.

289
00:20:35,151 --> 00:20:37,861
What? The Dynamic Duo at the schooI?

290
00:20:38,028 --> 00:20:40,572
That's right, Joker.
What'Il I do? Take it on the Iam?

291
00:20:40,740 --> 00:20:43,408
No, no, no, Iisten. Oh, ha-ha-ha.

292
00:20:43,576 --> 00:20:46,578
Thank heavens
for my deIicious sense of humor.

293
00:20:46,746 --> 00:20:48,747
You have your crooked keys, don't you?

294
00:20:48,914 --> 00:20:51,416
-Natch.
<i>£J£O£K£E£R£: All right, sweet Sue.</i>

295
00:20:51,584 --> 00:20:57,088
<i>Find Key 17. Do exactly as I tell you.</i>

296
00:21:02,553 --> 00:21:05,305
-Gain IeveI set.
-Okay.

297
00:21:05,723 --> 00:21:08,808
Set the antitheft systems. Let's go.

298
00:21:16,484 --> 00:21:18,943
BATMAN: Susie.
-Oh. Wow, am I ever gIad to see you two.

299
00:21:19,111 --> 00:21:20,153
BATMAN:
Oh?

300
00:21:20,321 --> 00:21:22,280
Just now,
I saw a suspicious character in the gym.

301
00:21:22,448 --> 00:21:25,492
-Quick, run to safety.
-We'II take care of him.

302
00:21:26,494 --> 00:21:29,954
Wait, Batman.
Look, that machine, it's been tampered with.

303
00:21:30,206 --> 00:21:32,916
This might be tricky.

304
00:21:33,125 --> 00:21:37,212
Get out your Batarang. I'II sIip in a dime.

305
00:21:42,635 --> 00:21:44,093
[LOUD CLICKING]

306
00:21:44,845 --> 00:21:47,222
ROBIN:
HoIy baII and chain.

307
00:21:47,598 --> 00:21:49,140
[BOTH GRUNTING]

308
00:21:51,644 --> 00:21:53,770
Quick, Iet's get out our cutting tooIs.

309
00:21:53,938 --> 00:21:55,480
[HISSING]

310
00:21:56,232 --> 00:21:59,108
Oh. Knockout gas.

311
00:22:04,448 --> 00:22:06,741
[ALL LAUGHING]

312
00:22:09,620 --> 00:22:13,873
<i>£N£A£R£R£A£T£O£R£: Twelve-and-one-half minutes later</i>
<i>inside this curious vehicle:</i>

313
00:22:20,548 --> 00:22:21,881
It's alI hooked up, boss.

314
00:22:22,049 --> 00:22:24,676
-Fifty-thousand voIts from the city main.
-Good.

315
00:22:24,844 --> 00:22:26,344
[BOTH LAUGH]

316
00:22:27,680 --> 00:22:30,515
Gosh, Joker.
This sure is some crazy mixed-up moving van.

317
00:22:30,683 --> 00:22:34,394
One of the assets of the One-Armed Bandit
Novelty Company, my dear.

318
00:22:34,562 --> 00:22:37,522
BuiIt for a whimsical Caribbean dictator.

319
00:22:37,690 --> 00:22:43,194
HappiIy for us, if not for the Dynamic Duo,
deposed before delivery.

320
00:22:43,362 --> 00:22:44,863
[BATMAN GROANS]

321
00:22:50,536 --> 00:22:53,538
-Oh, they're waking up.
-CarefuI now, my dimpIed darling.

322
00:22:53,706 --> 00:22:56,833
No names. I'II speak to them
through this trick microphone...

323
00:22:57,001 --> 00:22:59,544
...that disguises our voices.

324
00:23:01,005 --> 00:23:03,214
SUSIE [DISTORTED]:
<i>Oh, what a ball.</i>

325
00:23:03,424 --> 00:23:04,924
HoIy Las Vegas. Where are we?

326
00:23:05,092 --> 00:23:09,554
JOKER [OVER SPEAKER]: £I£n £a £s£t£r£a£n£g£e
<i>kind of game room, Boy Blunder.</i>

327
00:23:09,722 --> 00:23:12,223
-Do you see the machine next to you?
BATMAN: Right.

328
00:23:12,391 --> 00:23:15,852
JOKER:
<i>It's going to spin around merrily and merrily.</i>

329
00:23:16,061 --> 00:23:17,520
What's the payoff?

330
00:23:17,688 --> 00:23:23,401
Three Liberty BelIs:
Your freedom, and $50,000 cash.

331
00:23:24,069 --> 00:23:27,071
<i>Three oranges: Your freedom only.</i>

332
00:23:27,323 --> 00:23:30,867
And if it's three lemons?
Which the percentages say is the more IikeIy.

333
00:23:31,076 --> 00:23:37,081
Fifty-thousand voIts of eIectrifying electricity,
my fettered fatman.

334
00:23:37,625 --> 00:23:40,209
<i>Automatically on the third lemon.</i>

335
00:23:40,377 --> 00:23:43,922
-HoIy fruit salad.
-Sorry, I don't approve of gambling.

336
00:23:44,089 --> 00:23:46,341
JOKER:
<i>Enough, my captured Caped Crusaders.</i>

337
00:23:46,550 --> 00:23:51,262
I guarantee this machine is fair.
So let the game commence.

338
00:23:51,430 --> 00:23:52,931
[BOTH CHUCKLING]

339
00:24:01,065 --> 00:24:02,774
[NARRATOR READING ON-SCREEN TEXT]

340
00:25:12,011 --> 00:25:14,012
[EngIish - US - SDH]

