NARRATOR:
We have previously seen a day at school...
...a glass of milk.
Not milk, but money.
Holy cow juice. It's easy living.
Sounds like the Joker.
Watch out, kids, the Joker's back of this.
How true.
What's he up to?
An innocent jukebox?
Oh, yeah?
Plunder by remote control.
And in the Joker's workshop....
Cheerleader Susie...
...a secret member of the gang?
But what's the Joker's plan?
And that night at school....
Watch out!
Ouch!
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
NARRATOR:
Knockout gas.
And inside this van, a ghastly game.
Three lemons win 50,000 volts.
One lemon.
Two lemons.
[READING ON-SCREEN TEXT]
-Hey, boss, Iook.
-What, what, what?
-The whoIe town, dark.
-Street lights, everything.
Oh, curses and criminy,
what confounded luck.
Gotham City is having a power faiIure,
just like New York.
[SIRENS IN DISTANCE]
The cops.
I don't Iike the twist this joke is taking.
Let us away. Cheese it, everyone.
Let's go. Let's go.
Strange, an abandoned truck.
Let's have a Iook inside.
HoIy smoke.
Quick, cut us out of here before
the power comes on.
Or that's what we wiII be,
just holy smokes.
A mobiIe sIot-machine torture van.
Being in possession of such a vehicle
vioIates 1 7 separate statutes.
And not a shred of evidence tying it
to the devilish Joker.
No fingerprints, stolen Iicense pIates.
You overIooked this, Chief O'Hara.
A reeI of tape?
Right, the tape from our anti-crime recorder.
Before setting out, I equipped my utiIity
beIt with a microphone and transmitter.
ROBIN: Every word those criminaIs said
was recorded in the Batmobile.
But what good wiII that do,
Boy Wonder?
I thought you told us they spoke
to you through a trick, uh, voice distorter.
Tricky, commissioner. Tricky but vain.
They didn't reaIize that every human voice
has its own private wave pattern.
-Private as a fingerprint.
-Astounding.
Is it evidence?
Can it be used by the district attorney?
True. The court won't accept it as yet.
However, I'II take this tape to the Batcave...
...run it through the anti-crime voice analyzer,
check it against the voice fiIe.
We'II be able to Iearn the identity
of the Joker's henchmen.
We might be abIe to foIlow one of them
to the Joker's hideout.
Robin's right.
It's our only card.
Let's hope it's a trump.
I'm afraid the Joker may stiIl hoId
the winning hand, Batman.
WilI the anti-crime voice anaIyzer
operate without power?
Fortunately, the Batcave is equipped
with an anti-crime auxiIiary generator...
...which automaticalIy compensates
for any power failure.
Saints be praised.
And the Caped Crusader's
advanced technoIogy.
To the Batcave.
NARRATOR:
Morning. Hallelujah.
The mighty power grid serving Gotham City
is back in action.
And in the Batcave,
deep below stately Wayne Manor....
Master scope circuit, A-okay.
-Let's check the beginning of the tape.
-Right.
That'Il be Susie when we ran into her
in the haII.
SUSIE: Wow, am I ever glad to see you two.
-Perfect.
-What'Il I do? Jump the tape ahead?
-Roger.
Pick it up at 1 2.7.
That'Il be when we were tied inside
that grisIy torture van.
TweIve point seven, here it goes.
SUSIE:
Oh, what a ball.
-The same voice.
-I don't beIieve it. Susie?
Quick, both tapes.
Let's run them again, back to back.
SUSIE:
Wow, am I ever glad to see you two.
Oh, what a ball.
HoIy Benedict ArnoId.
Susie, our chief cheerIeader,
a member of the Joker's criminaI gang.
Is it possibIe, Batman?
Steady, Robin. Steady, oId chum.
But how can it be?
It's an oId story I'm afraid,
oId as Eve and the appIe.
That snake, the Joker must have
promised her some baubIes, Ied her astray.
But what are we gonna do, Batman?
It's bitter, but it's a break,
the first one we've had.
-We'II have to use it.
-You're right. OnIy how?
Let's see. Today is a schooI hoIiday, isn't it?
Where is that cute IittIe trickster apt
to be hanging out?
I know. The Easy Living candy store.
It's on East 3rd, two bIocks from school.
Get set, Robin. Get set for an ugIy job.
-No, correction.
-What?
Not Robin, Dick.
Dick Grayson, undercover agent.
His job is to get inside that gang.
[GULPS]
Dog George to Batman, do you read me?
-Do you read me, Batman?
-Loud and cIear, over.
I'm about to go in.
How's that micro TV camera working?
-Push button for test pattern.
-Roger.
Batscope, A-okay, Dog George.
Rendezvous in Batcave at end of mission.
Good luck, over and out.
Good gravy. It's Dick Grayson,
president of the student council.
A goodnik Iike that coming in here?
Hi, Sue baby.
How's tricks?
I must be seeing things. I thought you spent
aII your spare time studying.
Ah, sure. I used to, maybe,
but, uh, who needs it anymore.
You're Iooking at a guy
who's seen the Iight, Sue baby.
-Who's the boyfriend?
-Oh, my friends caII me Nick.
DICK: No kidding?
What do your enemies call you?
NICK: My enemies ain't in no condition
to call nobody nothing.
Heh, some joker, isn't he?
[CLEARING THROAT]
Uh....
You Iooking for something, Dicky boy?
Heh, same as everyone eIse, Sue baby.
Some way of making an easy buck,
that's aIl.
You, the ward of that rich miIlionaire,
Bruce Wayne?
What a skinflint. If I didn't swipe dimes from
the butIer, I wouIdn't have cigarette money.
WelI, here. Have one on me, buster.
-Oh, thanks, paI.
NICK: Right.
[COUGHING]
I better pass this round.
I already had two packs today.
So how's the easy buck setup?
Got any leads?
You know, he might be abIe to heIp us, Nick.
He's a reaI super athIete.
-Oh, is that so?
-You ought to see him cIimb and stuff.
-Maybe I shouId introduce him to--
-Zip your Iip, baby.
Introduce me to who, Susie?
-Hey, you want a tip, buster?
-Yeah.
Oh, there was a cocktaiI Iounge stuck up
recently. These guys used a trick jukebox.
-Yeah. I heard about that, some cute caper.
-Yeah.
Well, here's my tip. You go down to
that same joint at exactly 3 p.m. today.
You might pick yourself up
some nickels and dimes.
-Thanks, pal.
-That's my tip.
-I'II see you around, huh?
-Oh, yeah. You'II see me around.
So long, Sue baby.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Gee, Nick. What's the idea?
Why, you gorgeous dumb hunk of cheerIeader,
couIdn't you see?
-That guy is strictly a phony.
-What do you mean?
Already had two packs today, huh?
My blind grandmother couId see.
That guy never had a weed
in his hand in his life.
Good gravy.
How'd I do, Batman?
Good show, Robin. Darn good show.
It's 20 minutes to 3.
We'd better hurry up
if we're gonna trap them.
Right you are. Let's go.
NARRATOR:
A trap indeed, but who's the mouse?
For in the lurid lair of that criminal cat,
the Joker....
My favorite kind ofjoke,
one which ends with a bang.
-Ha-ha-ha.
-Right. And what about, uh, Susie?
Has she, uh, fiIled the miIk machine again?
She's just getting ready.
Uh, Susie, sweetie...
...a speciaI extra bonus...
...a half-pint bottIe of the most exquisite
imported Canadian perfume.
Wow, Canadian perfume.
It's caIled Un Nuit Sans Fin,
one endless night.
Gee, that's Iike poetry.
No, Susie, no.
Do not open untiI after you've loaded
the miIk machine, do you understand?
Oh, sure, Joker, anything you say.
You're just the best boss
any crook ever had.
Oh, thank you.
-Ha, ha.
-Hey, Joker. It's 3:00.
Batman's zero hour.
Watch for the green light.
[PATRONS CHATTERING]
Back. Everybody, back of the bar.
We gotta have room to throw our Batarangs
when the crooks come in for the Ioot.
Ready with the coin, Robin?
Ready.
Zero hour.
-Put it in the slot.
-Roger.
Batman's funeraI dirge begins.
I'II give him five seconds.
Now.
JOKER [ON SPEAKER]: Thejokes on you,
my cheery booze hounds. It's a stickup.
Hands up, you cowards.
Surprise, Batman.
-Quick, Robin, down behind the BatshieId.
-Surprise and good night.
HoIy haiI storm.
You knew this was gonna happen.
Or something like it.
You see, Robin,
you betrayed yourself in that candy store.
-How?
-Despite your boast...
...it was painfuIly evident
you're not a smoker.
Nick must have seen that you were working
with the poIice.
-Gee, Batman. I'm sorry.
-Don't be siIly.
It's to your credit that that charade faiIed.
The thing now is to save Susie.
-Save Susie?
-Work it out.
Why wouId an undercover agent
try to pump her?
-Because I knew she was one of the gang.
-Right.
And once they know that we know...
...that young Iady's Iife
isn't worth a pIug IolIipop.
HoIy murder. We gotta find her quick.
-Where? Back at the store?
-SchooI.
-On Saturday?
-She'II be in the gym practicing cheers.
Of course. Tonight there's a big game,
Woodrow Roosevelt against Disko Tech.
Let's hurry, Batman.
Bartender, a bit of advice.
Always inspect a jukebox carefuIIy.
These machines can be deadIy.
[RINGING]
HeIlo. Yeah. Right.
Yeah, just a sec. He's right here.
Joker. Joker, it's for you. It's Las Vegas...
-...Pete The Swede.
-Ah!
HeIlo, Pete The Swede.
What's the Iine on the big game tonight?
The odds are 20-to-1 ?
On Woodrow Roosevelt High?
Oh, what a kiIIing.
Take a whimsical wager.
Fifty thousand doIlars on Disko Tech.
Yes, Pete The Swede,
you heard me, Disko Tech.
Fifty times 20, 1 miIlion bucks.
Oh, how delicious. Ha-ha-ha!
NARRATOR:
What? Bet against these champs?
The Clown Prince of Crime
must have slipped a cog.
But wait.
GIRL:
One....
ALL [CHEERING]:
Disko Tech, hey!
Fight them, Woodrow Roosevelt
Beat them, Woodrow Roosevelt
Woodrow Roosevelt, Woodrow Roosevelt
-Fight!
Fight!
Okay, kids. Let's take a break, huh?
Gee, too bad
that magic milk machine is out of order.
Susie, stop. Give yourseIf up.
Your Iife is danger, Susie.
The Joker knows we're on to you.
He'II discard you without mercy
like an oId shoe.
Have you guys stripped your gears?
Quick, catch her.
So long, Dynamic Duo.
Poisoned.
Dead.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I saw them Ioading her on
a meat wagon from the city morgue.
The Boy Wonder was bawIing his head off.
Oh, weII.
WelI, it had to be done, my Bad Pennies.
What's the death of a greedy IittIe dupe?
This life at best
is one long impracticaI joke.
Have a memoriaI cigar.
Why, thank you, Joker.
[EXPLODES]
[LAUGHING]
The brief shadow is Iifted.
I'm my own humorous seIf again.
-What's the hour?
-5:22.
Quick. Cameras. Disguises.
It's time for my greatest strike.
[LAUGHING]
[BALL BOUNCING]
Okay....
One more.
Okay, feIlas, let's knock it off
before we go stale.
Right you are, cap.
We'II quit whiIe we stilI got
our razor-sharp edge.
We'II beat them by 50 points tonight.
We'II do it for Susie, right?
-Right.
-Come on.
The out of order sign's gone off
the miIk machine.
Oh, boy. It must be fixed.
-Hey, who's got a dime?
-Oh, here, I got one.
-What the heck?
-This machine's been fixed aII right.
Good gosh!
These are next week's
nationwide pre-colIege exam papers.
Complete with the answers written in.
[LAUGHING]
Dear me, how disiIIusioning.
The champs are cheats.
Caught red-handed with the answers
to the nationwide pre-colIege exams.
-The Joker.
-At the moment, mereIy an honest citizen.
We was passing by to inspect
this, uh, here school property...
...which we support with our taxes.
-And imagine our surprise.
-Hey, we're not cheats.
Oh, it's a typicaI fiIthy Joker's trick.
WelI, it hardly matters, boys, now, does it?
When the board of education sees this picture
with you hoIding the answer to those exams....
[LAUGHING]
Good gosh, we'II be suspended.
We won't be aIlowed
to pIay Disko Tech tonight.
Ah! WeIl, ha-ha-ha! I'm sure
the scrubs wiII do their best.
The scrubs? They'lI be creamed.
Oh, so sad, so sad. Tsk-tsk-tsk.
And after Batman's Iectures
to you about honesty. Ah!
What on earth wiII
the Caped Crusader say?
BATMAN:
BaII players. Run for cover.
Don't worry about having seen
those exam papers. They're a fake.
ROBIN: We pIanted them and
the Joker's picture doesn't mean a thing.
We saved Susie's life by using the universaI
antidote piIls in our utiIity beIts.
She repaid us by reveaIing
the whoIe criminal scheme.
Okay, Batman.
Let's deIiver the punch Iine.
[ALL GRUNTING]
-Tough luck, Bad Pennies.
-You're out of circulation.
They'lI meIt you down in a pan.
[LAUGHING]
HoIy New Year's Eve.
He's got me in his famous trick streamers.
[LAUGHING]
Have a sneeze on me, Batman.
No use, Joker.
I knew you'd empIoy your sneezing powder.
So I took an anti-aIIergy piII.
Instead of a sneeze, I've caught you coId.
That's what easy Iiving gets you, kids.
Stick to your books.
And good Iuck against Disko Tech.
WelI, I guess it's goodbye, Susie.
Goodbye, Dick.
I give you my word. I'lI mail you alI
the new cheers as soon as they're made up.
You can practice them while you're away.
Gosh.
What's the matter?
You've aIl been so nice to me.
I can hardly bear it.
Heck, Susie, it wasn't aIl your fault.
I mean, with your unhappy chiIdhood
and a broken home and everything.
No wonder you feIl for
that crook's phony promises.
It's time, Susie.
The chauffeur is waiting.
Gee, imagine being taken to jaiI
by a chauffeur.
The Wayne Foundation for deIinquent girIs
is hardIy a jaiI.
Heck, no.
There are teams and cIubs and everything.
I don't know what to say to you both.
I just....
-Thanks, Dick.
-You're welcome, Susie.
I'II have nightmares aII my Iife, Mr. Wayne.
If it hadn't been for that power failure,
where wouId Robin be?
And where wouId Batman be?
-Where wouId Dick Grayson be?
-Huh?
BRUCE:
Don't think about it, young peopIe.
Just be thankfuI that Iife is fiIled
with unanswered questions. That's aII.
-Goodbye, Susie.
-Goodbye.
NARRATOR:
Next week, Batman battles False Face.
[EngIish - US - SDH]