NARRATOR: Another glorious
sun-drenched day in Gotham City.
A fitting day for nuptials,
exhibits, or grand theft.
"Look out, cops. I hereby crown myseIf."
Signed, FaIse Face.
Yes, he's back again, that infamous
criminaI master of trickery and disguise.
[FOOTSTEPS]
I am the Princess Mergenberg.
What is this I hear?
My crown wilI be stolen?
Oh, we'Il keep it safe for you,
Your Highness.
Oh, so? Then what is this?
CURATOR:
"AII that glitters is gone."
ShouIdn't that be
"AII that glitters is goId"?
Oh, that's the trademark of False Face,
a faIse quote.
But the crown is here, and safe.
Not quite, Chief O'Hara.
[GASPS]
It's FaIse Face.
In disguised person.
MERGENBERG:
Stop, thief.
An infIatabIe cape.
She must be an accompIice.
After them, men.
[HORN HONKS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[SIREN WAILING]
The police are hot on our traiI.
Then we'Il cool them down.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[LAUGHING]
Oh, so FaIse Face is back
and up to his old tricks, eh? Heh.
Disguised as the Princess Mergenberg...
...he and his accomplice, the beautifuI BIaze,
tried for the crown.
And failed.
A faIse top. Plastic.
The crown.
Phony.
Utterly worthless.
False Face has struck deviously
and ruthIessly.
Can't we stop
this master of deviIish disguises?
Commissioner, there's onIy one man Iiving
who can unmask FaIse Face.
Chief O'Hara, you have said it for aIl of us.
Our onIy hope is that towering power
for right and justice, the Caped Crusader.
[BEEPING]
I'II calI him, sir.
Pine, elm, hickory....
Gosh, botany is tough.
I'II never Iearn to recognize aIl these trees.
Come, come, Dick.
Pine, elm, hickory, chestnut, mapIe.
Part of our heritage is the lore of Iiving things,
the storybook of nature.
That's true, Bruce.
I'II Iearn to read that book of nature yet.
Begging your pardon, sir.
It's the Batphone.
-Jiminy, what are we waiting for?
-Oh, Dick, I found one of your specimens.
Thanks a milIion, Aunt Harriet,
but we were just going to, uh.... Uh....
A rambIe in the woods, Aunt Harriet.
Nature in the raw, so to speak.
COOPER:
Oh.
Yes, commissioner?
Prepare yourseIf for a shock.
It's FaIse Face. He struck again.
We're on our way.
To the Batpoles.
I'm afraid it won't stop for the Mergenberg
crown, worth a miIIion though it is.
This is only the first dropIet
in a virtuaI wave of crime.
Jiminy, yes. FaIse Face aIways pIans big.
Crooked, but king size.
AlI too true, Boy Wonder.
Messenger here for Batman.
-Uh, are you Batman, sonny?
-I am.
"I intend to give money
to a defenseIess little girl." Signed, F.F.
I'd wager that's some sort of a code.
It is. False Face always says
the opposite of what he means.
Then "I intend to give money"
means he intends to take money.
But what defenseless IittIe girI?
-Confusing, eh, sonny?
BATMAN: Not reaIIy.
The victim is neither IittIe
nor a girI nor defenseIess.
Opposite of girI's a boy.
And the opposite of defenseless?
-Say, wearing armor?
-That's it. Of course.
The Ladd Armored Car Company.
HoIy bouncy boilerpIate, it fits.
Ladd as in boy, armored for defense,
a big truck fuIl of money.
That's it. You've got it.
I have more than that.
UnIess I missed my gaze, you're....
Blaze, FaIse Face's trusted assistant,
at your service.
You've got quite a grip there,
Caped Crusader.
A sound mind and a sound body,
a necessity in the relentIess war against crime.
And speaking of crime,
why did FaIse Face send you here?
False Face chaIIenges you
to prove that he's committed a crime.
And if you do, to catch him.
And me.
It's too Iate.
-Blaze, she's as elusive as a flickering fIame.
-I'II bet that's how she earned her nickname.
I warrant you,
we'II snuff out her fiery criminaI career.
To the Ladd Armored Car Company, let's go.
FALSE FACE:
Are we alI assembIed?
The counterfeit crew are ready
and on duty, FaIse Face.
FALSE FACE:
Good.
First, men, I've succeeded
in Iifting the Mergenberg crown.
-You've done it again, F.F.
FALSE FACE: OnIy the beginning.
Blaze, my trusted assistant...
...has succeeded in starting off
step two of my overalI pIan.
We are about to doubIe-dizzy
Batman and Robin...
...until the dexterous duo is duped, decoyed
and diaboIicaIly destroyed.
I have pIanned the greatest creation
of my covert criminal career.
False Face wiII stamp his disguised image
on alI Gotham City.
Today Gotham City, tomorrow the worId.
Three cheers for F.F.
ALL:
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
FALSE FACE:
Thanks, men. I know you didn't mean it.
But back to business.
Batman and Robin must go.
LADD:
Batman and Robin.
Why, it isn't often that a simpIe businessman
is honored by a visit...
...from the champion ofjustice
and his youthfuI associate.
-How can I heIp you?
-Rather it's we who can heIp you.
We have reason to beIieve that one of
your armored trucks may be in danger.
LADD:
Good heavens.
I've just received word
that one of my trucks is late...
...and is due at the NationaI Bank
to pick up a huge shipment of money.
I wouIdn't be surprised
if FaIse Face were the spoke...
-...in that set of wheeIs.
-Right.
-Mr. Ladd, may I use your telephone?
LADD: Oh, yes, of course.
Commissioner Gordon pIease,
this is Batman speaking.
Commissioner, there's no time to expIain.
Dispatch as many spare men as possibIe
to the Gotham City NationaI Bank immediateIy.
Mr. Ladd, we'Il keep you informed...
...and let you know as soon
as your missing truck is found.
Bless you, Batman.
Every law-abiding citizen of Gotham City
goes with you in spirit.
And if it were possibIe, in body.
Batman and Robin.
Come to make a deposit?
No, we've come to prevent a withdrawal,
by FaIse Face.
What? FaIse Face, notorious criminaI,
master of disguise?
Then we better Ioad the money in the truck
before it's too Iate.
It's already too Iate, FaIse Face.
-What?
BATMAN: Right.
That's FaIse Face himseIf
in disguised person.
Yeah? What makes you so sure?
It's obvious.
Only a criminaI wouId disguise himself
as a Iicensed bonded guard...
...yet caIIousIy park
in front of a fire hydrant.
It's always the little things.
ROBIN: This time it'lI cost you
a big penaIty, False Face.
We're going to withdraw you from circuIation
and deposit you in jail.
FALSE FACE:
WelI, Boy Wonder, your interest is overdue.
[FALSE FACE LAUGHING]
Thank you, Batman,
for braking into my trap.
[BLOWING WHISTLE]
Batman, it's BIaze in the Batmobile.
Aah. Oh, you're so strong.
I urge you to abandon this Iife of crime, BIaze,
before it's too Iate.
FALSE FACE:
It's already too Iate, Batman.
HoIy Houdini.
[SIREN WAILING]
Another deft escape
by that master of disguise and deceit.
But where can FaIse Face be?
Saints alive.
It's FaIse Face disguised as meseIf.
Right you are, O'Hara.
Welcome to dreamIand.
AlI right, take off.
-Everything's under control, chief.
-Good work.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES
THEN MOTOR STARTS]
[LAUGHING]
This paper that FaIse Face used
to print his message, it's rather special.
TensiIe resistance, 85.
HoIy armored pIate.
This is the strongest stuff I've ever seen.
As I suspected.
Eighty-six, 87, 87.6.
I can't figure it out, Batman.
I think a little session with the BatanaIyst
might cIarify things, Robin.
Uh, I seem to be short of cash.
Alfred, have you a doIIar bilI?
-CertainIy, sir. There.
BATMAN: Thank you.
By focusing uItravioIet Iight...
...and appIying the principIes
of controIled fIuorescent diffraction...
...we can readiIy discern....
False Face printed his message on the
same kind of paper they use to make money.
What use could he make
of that sort of paper, sir?
To make money.
His kind of money, counterfeit money.
WilI the man stop at nothing?
This paper is made by
a top-secret government process, indeed.
Only a few people outside the officiaI
banknote printing company are aware...
...that it's the onIy paper
that cannot be counterfeited.
Aha.
-You found something?
-The soIution, sir?
The size, the materiaI, it aII fits.
This is official banknote paper.
False Face must have penetrated
the official banknote printing company.
And if he has pIans for counterfeiting,
he'II go back there for more special paper.
But we wiIl be there before he is.
To the BatmobiIe.
Alfred, inform Mrs. Cooper that we may be
a trifIe Iate for supper this evening.
ALFRED:
Very good, sir.
-There's nobody here.
-Not so far.
But if someone shouId arrive,
I think we shouId be out of sight.
-Excuse me, do you have a Iight?
MAN: Why, certainIy.
But smoking is forbidden
in the banknote paper room.
-What department are you in, miss?
-RemovaI.
You see, my curious friend,
we need this paper.
[WHISTLES]
QuickIy, move this into the trick truck.
HENCHMAN: It's Batman.
-And Robin.
BOTH:
We've been found out.
[GRUNTING]
No, you don't, BIaze.
I have the answer to that IittIe trick.
I knew sooner or Iater...
...you wouId overcome my bag of tricks.
Let the pIant guards cIean up these beauties.
I want to interrogate BIaze.
Batman. Let me down!
[FALSE FACE CLEARS THROAT]
You must excuse Chief O'Hara.
He has an agonizing toothache
and finds it difficult to speak.
-I can hardly recognize his voice.
FALSE FACE: Mm.
I hope it gets better, Chief O'Hara.
[BLAZE GROANING]
She's awakened.
WelI, miss, it seems
we've apprehended you.
You? ScarceIy.
Batman captured me.
Only the nemesis of crime
couId have tripped up Blaze so deftly.
Blaze, we've deduced False Face's intent
to counterfeit money.
We must know where he intends
to perform the printing.
So you're in on the counterfeiting caper.
Very clever, Caped Crusader.
But I know that's onIy part
of his overaII plan.
We must have detaiIs on the complete plot.
How, where, when?
-I don't know.
-You? His first Iieutenant?
That's pretty dim, BIaze.
False Face trusts no one,
and no one trusts False Face.
Like his name, Iike his enumerabIe disguises,
he is forever in conceaIment.
I know he plans a gigantic coup,
but I am not in on his pIans.
Then I'm afraid we're at a dead-end.
I'II teIl you one thing, Batman.
If there is one force in this world
that False Face fears, it's you.
And the Boy Wonder, of course.
Many times I have heard him mutter,
"If it were not for the Caped Crusaders...
...I wouId be kingpin of the criminaI cIass."
The swine.
That False Face is rotten
to his conceaIed core.
Please, commissioner, even FaIse Face
has a conscience, somewhere...
...and can be rehabilitated, somehow.
That's so true, Batman.
For the moment, I was carried away.
Batman, you-- You are truly good.
And if I can, I'lI help you find FaIse Face.
AlI right, we'Il take a chance
on trusting you, BIaze.
Sorry, I-- I was carried away.
-WelI, let's alI be away, after FaIse Face.
BATMAN: Right.
If I might make a suggestion.
Why not let the dynamic duo
go with Blaze...
...while I make certain
a force of picked police stand by.
-CapitaI.
-Good thinking, O'Hara.
It's nothing.
I'd better be on me way too, commissioner.
-I wouIdn't wanna lose Batman.
-Right.
NARRATOR: Can it be?
Are Batman and Robin rushing into dire peril?
Does Batman know
Chief O'Hara is False Face?
Can he trust the treacherous Blaze?
CIever. Who'd suspect
a shut-down subway station?
And it's centraIly located
for False Face's nefarious plans.
I'm sorry we took so Iong to get here, Batman,
but I was unsure of the way.
[TRAIN APPROACHING]
Where to now? Time is of the essence.
Oh, good heavens, no wonder I'm starved.
It's after Iunch.
Oh, Batman,
would you get me a candy bar pIease?
Candy?
ActuaIIy fresh fruit
is much more heaIthfuI.
Oh, but there's none here,
and there is a candy machine.
He's such a gentIeman. You both are.
True cavaliers.
ROBIN:
Aw.
[COUGHING]
[COUGHS]
False Face.
[LAUGHING]
FALSE FACE:
That's quick-setting pIastic cement.
Oh, yes, you're strong, Batman, but
a bulI eIephant couldn't break these bonds.
-False Face, is this kiIling necessary?
-AbsoIuteIy. They must be disposed of.
The express wiIl be through here
inside of five minutes, Batman.
Inside of six, no more Batman.
Fiend.
False Face, you'Il regret this, eventualIy.
Oh, I regret it aIready.
False Face, Iet's reconsider.
Never.
No, you don't. Come.
Batman, forgive me.
Of course, BIaze.
Any young girl might foIlow
the wrong impuIse.
I forgive you.
Take a Iast Iook.
Inside of minutes, the dynamic duo
wiIl be mereIy disintegrated debris.
[TRAIN APPROACHING]
[NARRATOR READING ON-SCREEN TEXT]
[EngIish - US - SDH]