1
00:00:09,968 --> 00:00:13,346
NARRATOR:
<i>So far we have seen a jeweled crown...</i>

2
00:00:16,600 --> 00:00:18,142
<i>...an inflating cape...</i>

3
00:00:21,730 --> 00:00:24,774
<i>...a crown proved false...</i>

4
00:00:26,735 --> 00:00:28,653
<i>...a cry for aid...</i>

5
00:00:31,615 --> 00:00:33,449
<i>...and a ready answer.</i>

6
00:00:33,617 --> 00:00:35,618
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]

7
00:00:36,119 --> 00:00:38,704
NARRATOR:
<i>While False Face plotted...</i>

8
00:00:43,168 --> 00:00:44,293
<i>...a robbery?</i>

9
00:00:47,005 --> 00:00:48,464
<i>No, an ambush...</i>

10
00:00:51,718 --> 00:00:53,135
<i>...which backfired.</i>

11
00:00:53,595 --> 00:00:58,015
<i>False Face in chief's clothing</i>
<i>captured the chief.</i>

12
00:00:59,977 --> 00:01:01,978
<i>Deduction by the duo.</i>

13
00:01:04,356 --> 00:01:06,816
<i>A daring escape by Blaze...</i>

14
00:01:07,609 --> 00:01:10,319
<i>...later nabbed by the Caped Crusader.</i>

15
00:01:11,154 --> 00:01:13,656
<i>Interrogation and repentance.</i>

16
00:01:15,075 --> 00:01:16,325
<i>An embrace.</i>

17
00:01:17,160 --> 00:01:18,869
<i>Holy entanglement.</i>

18
00:01:21,707 --> 00:01:22,999
<i>A gasser.</i>

19
00:01:25,127 --> 00:01:26,877
<i>An escaping pair.</i>

20
00:01:30,048 --> 00:01:32,508
<i>The Dynamic Duo on the wrong track...</i>

21
00:01:35,345 --> 00:01:37,555
<i>...facing a fearsome fate.</i>

22
00:01:37,723 --> 00:01:41,183
<i>Wait. The wildest is yet to come.</i>

23
00:02:26,730 --> 00:02:28,731
[HORN BLARES]

24
00:02:51,338 --> 00:02:54,215
NARRATOR:
<i>In the Batcave deep under Wayne Manor...</i>

25
00:02:54,383 --> 00:02:57,259
<i>a faithful Alfred tends to his daily duties.</i>

26
00:03:00,097 --> 00:03:04,058
MAN [ON RADIO]: <i>A</i><i>n</i><i>d</i> <i>n</i><i>o</i><i>w</i> <i>t</i><i>h</i><i>e</i> <i>c</i><i>u</i><i>l</i><i>t</i><i>u</i><i>ra</i><i>l</i> <i>h</i><i>o</i><i>u</i><i>r</i>
<i>brings you a special message:</i>

27
00:03:04,226 --> 00:03:09,438
<i>"To the friends of Batman:</i>
<i>Many are called but two are chosen.</i>

28
00:03:09,606 --> 00:03:11,357
<i>Be receptive."</i>

29
00:03:11,525 --> 00:03:15,403
<i>Now we return to the fragile intricacies</i>
<i>of Mozart.</i>

30
00:03:21,284 --> 00:03:23,494
HoId on, oId chum. I've got an idea.

31
00:03:23,829 --> 00:03:26,580
Batman. CalIing Batman and Robin.

32
00:03:34,256 --> 00:03:35,589
[OVER RADIO]:
<i>This is the Batcave.</i>

33
00:03:35,757 --> 00:03:39,427
<i>Calling Batman.</i>

34
00:03:39,636 --> 00:03:41,971
It's AIfred. I've turned on the Batradio.

35
00:03:42,139 --> 00:03:43,973
Alfred, Batman here.

36
00:03:44,141 --> 00:03:46,392
Oh, very good, sir. I was concerned.

37
00:03:46,810 --> 00:03:50,104
Alfred, pulI the short-circuit Iever
on the Bat Transmitter.

38
00:03:50,772 --> 00:03:53,274
Short-circuit lever. But--

39
00:03:53,775 --> 00:03:57,236
But, sir, that wiIl destroy
your wrist Batradio.

40
00:03:57,571 --> 00:04:01,866
Alfred, our relationship
has always been one of mutuaI respect.

41
00:04:02,033 --> 00:04:07,496
I cannot disregard my own standards
and order you to destroy the Bat Transmitter.

42
00:04:07,664 --> 00:04:11,751
But I am urging you to comply.

43
00:04:13,003 --> 00:04:15,171
If you put it that way, sir.

44
00:04:40,906 --> 00:04:43,491
Wasn't that Batman and Robin?

45
00:04:43,658 --> 00:04:47,620
Ah, yes. Fighting crime wherever it may be.

46
00:04:47,788 --> 00:04:49,580
Good for them.

47
00:04:52,375 --> 00:04:56,337
FALSE FACE: Escaped.
The tricky twosome tore free, thanks to you.

48
00:04:56,505 --> 00:05:00,591
Why accuse me of it?
Batman's a redoubtabIy fine crime fighter.

49
00:05:00,759 --> 00:05:02,718
FALSE FACE:
Fine, huh?

50
00:05:02,886 --> 00:05:04,470
Perhaps you find him attractive.

51
00:05:04,638 --> 00:05:06,263
Intriguing, was that it?

52
00:05:06,431 --> 00:05:09,433
I? False Face,
I was mereIy according Batman...

53
00:05:09,601 --> 00:05:13,145
...the respect due an outstanding adversary.
I haven't the slightest--

54
00:05:13,313 --> 00:05:17,399
FALSE FACE: Not so much protesting, Blaze,
and I'd believe you sooner.

55
00:05:17,567 --> 00:05:19,652
I say do the deep six with her.

56
00:05:19,820 --> 00:05:21,946
FALSE FACE:
Not so fast. I make the moves in this mob.

57
00:05:22,113 --> 00:05:23,531
Yes, sir.

58
00:05:23,949 --> 00:05:27,076
FALSE FACE:
I'II decide about you in the morning, BIaze.

59
00:05:27,244 --> 00:05:28,911
MeanwhiIe...

60
00:05:29,496 --> 00:05:31,831
...I warn you...

61
00:05:31,998 --> 00:05:35,835
...one thing I wilI not aIlow
is anyone being faIse to me.

62
00:05:59,359 --> 00:06:04,113
You say the radio message said
"Many are caIled but two are chosen"?

63
00:06:04,281 --> 00:06:07,533
Yes, sir. CIearly a reference
to yourself and Master Robin.

64
00:06:07,701 --> 00:06:12,246
I therefore activated the Bat AIarm
and caIIed you on the Bat Transmitter.

65
00:06:12,414 --> 00:06:13,581
Luckily for us.

66
00:06:13,748 --> 00:06:17,126
But, gosh, why'd FaIse Face trap us
then send a warning?

67
00:06:17,294 --> 00:06:18,627
-Why?
-He wouIdn't.

68
00:06:18,795 --> 00:06:20,796
But who wouId?

69
00:06:20,964 --> 00:06:24,800
The question is, Robin,
not only why but who?

70
00:06:25,677 --> 00:06:28,345
Very neatly done, Alfred. Thank you.

71
00:06:28,513 --> 00:06:30,556
Who sent that message? Who?

72
00:06:34,185 --> 00:06:36,020
GORDON:
O'Hara, where have you been?

73
00:06:36,187 --> 00:06:38,314
On a garbage scow, commissioner.

74
00:06:38,481 --> 00:06:39,857
It's alI right.

75
00:06:40,025 --> 00:06:41,150
In a sack.

76
00:06:41,318 --> 00:06:43,110
I was wrapped up and abandoned.

77
00:06:43,278 --> 00:06:45,613
-That's criminaI.
-That it is, sir.

78
00:06:45,780 --> 00:06:48,616
That's why I'm concerned
about Batman and Robin.

79
00:06:48,783 --> 00:06:50,743
GORDON: The Caped Crusaders?
-Yes.

80
00:06:50,911 --> 00:06:54,705
For I was put into this condition
by FaIse Face.

81
00:06:56,499 --> 00:07:00,419
<i>Today all Gotham City</i>
<i>is pulsating with one question.</i>

82
00:07:00,587 --> 00:07:04,423
<i>What criminal outrage</i>
<i>will False Face perpetrate next?</i>

83
00:07:04,591 --> 00:07:08,344
<i>Meanwhile, Police Chief O'Hara,</i>
<i>shaken by his ordeal as the prisoner...</i>

84
00:07:08,511 --> 00:07:10,846
<i>...of the masked master</i>
<i>of criminal concealment...</i>

85
00:07:11,014 --> 00:07:12,431
<i>...has sworn revenge.</i>

86
00:07:12,599 --> 00:07:17,686
<i>Chief O'Hara will broadcast an appeal</i>
<i>to the citizenry of Gotham City later tonight.</i>

87
00:07:17,854 --> 00:07:19,021
Of course.

88
00:07:19,189 --> 00:07:20,689
ROBIN: What is it, Batman?
-Broadcast.

89
00:07:20,857 --> 00:07:24,318
We'II trace that mysterious radio message
back to its broadcasting source.

90
00:07:24,486 --> 00:07:26,946
-HoIy transistors.
-Let's go.

91
00:07:57,227 --> 00:07:58,769
MAN:
Who ordered that announcement?

92
00:07:58,937 --> 00:08:01,021
A compIete stranger. Anonymous.

93
00:08:01,189 --> 00:08:04,358
FrankIy, Batman, I assumed
that it was simpIy another announcement.

94
00:08:04,526 --> 00:08:09,113
If someone wishes a message broadcast
like "Many are caIIed, two are chosen"...

95
00:08:09,280 --> 00:08:12,074
...I assume it's religious and that's aII.

96
00:08:12,409 --> 00:08:14,743
I don't think we shouId treat reIigion lightIy.

97
00:08:14,911 --> 00:08:16,078
Oh, of course not.

98
00:08:16,246 --> 00:08:18,914
I mereIy meant I treated it
as part of the day's work.

99
00:08:19,708 --> 00:08:21,625
Then it's another dead end.

100
00:08:21,793 --> 00:08:22,876
Thanks to FaIse Face.

101
00:08:23,378 --> 00:08:26,547
Is that who's invoIved, FaIse Face,
the criminaI master of disguise?

102
00:08:27,090 --> 00:08:29,591
None other.
That's why we hoped you'd give us a cIue.

103
00:08:30,385 --> 00:08:32,553
I am sorry, but--

104
00:08:33,471 --> 00:08:37,307
I say, there was one little thing
that you might caII pecuIiar.

105
00:08:37,475 --> 00:08:38,559
What is it?

106
00:08:38,727 --> 00:08:40,811
The young Iady who paid
for the announcement.

107
00:08:40,979 --> 00:08:43,897
She was not only staggeringIy beautiful,
she had green hair.

108
00:08:44,065 --> 00:08:46,275
-Green hair. HoIy wigs.
-Blaze.

109
00:08:46,443 --> 00:08:48,610
GORE:
Does that mean anything to you?

110
00:08:48,778 --> 00:08:49,987
Indeed it does.

111
00:08:50,155 --> 00:08:53,532
Good observation, Gore.
Darn good observation.

112
00:08:53,700 --> 00:08:57,244
Then perhaps you can teII me
what she meant by her parting remark.

113
00:08:57,412 --> 00:09:00,205
As she handed me the check and payment,
she said...

114
00:09:00,373 --> 00:09:02,416
...I couId bank on its being faIse.

115
00:09:02,917 --> 00:09:06,336
Check, bank, faIse.

116
00:09:06,963 --> 00:09:08,756
What bank was that checked drawn on?

117
00:09:08,923 --> 00:09:10,215
GORE:
Gotham NationaI.

118
00:09:10,383 --> 00:09:11,800
Of course.

119
00:09:11,968 --> 00:09:14,678
That's the bank that FaIse Face
is pIanning to break.

120
00:09:14,846 --> 00:09:18,307
-You mean the check is no good?
-Not as a check, Mr. Gore.

121
00:09:18,475 --> 00:09:19,808
But as a message, yes.

122
00:09:20,643 --> 00:09:23,979
Send the check to Commissioner Gordon.
I'II see that you're paid.

123
00:09:38,995 --> 00:09:41,997
Blaze ordered the radio announcement?

124
00:09:42,248 --> 00:09:44,500
-And saved our lives.
-She did even more than that.

125
00:09:44,667 --> 00:09:48,003
At great personal risk, she gave us a cIue
as to False Face's next move.

126
00:09:48,171 --> 00:09:50,506
GORDON: How so?
-When she handed the man at the station...

127
00:09:50,673 --> 00:09:54,426
...a check in payment for the announcement,
she said he couId bank on it being faIse.

128
00:09:54,594 --> 00:09:56,428
Sounds rather cryptic to me.

129
00:09:56,596 --> 00:09:58,806
The check was drawn
on the Gotham City National Bank.

130
00:09:58,973 --> 00:10:02,559
It baffles me, Batman. If False Face
contempIates a counterfeiting coup...

131
00:10:02,727 --> 00:10:06,021
-...why break into a bank?
-For a doubIe dose of diaboIicaI deception.

132
00:10:06,189 --> 00:10:07,523
Think, what's in a bank?

133
00:10:08,191 --> 00:10:09,858
-Money?
-Right.

134
00:10:10,026 --> 00:10:11,777
And what has FaIse Face been forging?

135
00:10:11,945 --> 00:10:13,779
-Money. Counterfeit money.
-Right again.

136
00:10:13,947 --> 00:10:15,989
Think of the consequences if FaIse Face...

137
00:10:16,157 --> 00:10:18,867
...replaced the bank's good money
with counterfeit currency.

138
00:10:19,035 --> 00:10:21,578
GhastIy. He's gambling for biIlions.

139
00:10:21,746 --> 00:10:25,582
Gosh, nobody's money
would be worth anything except False Face's.

140
00:10:25,750 --> 00:10:28,043
And nobody wouId be able to teII true
from false.

141
00:10:28,211 --> 00:10:29,336
He must be stopped.

142
00:10:29,504 --> 00:10:33,215
No, he must be encouraged, enticed...

143
00:10:33,383 --> 00:10:36,718
...and onIy then entrapped.

144
00:10:36,886 --> 00:10:39,054
But how?

145
00:10:39,514 --> 00:10:40,848
By faIsehood.

146
00:10:42,600 --> 00:10:44,101
NARRATOR:
<i>Falsehood?</i>

147
00:10:44,269 --> 00:10:49,398
<i>Is Batman capable</i>
<i>of out-falsing False Face?</i>

148
00:11:22,765 --> 00:11:23,932
[WHISTLES]

149
00:11:26,853 --> 00:11:30,397
FALSE FACE: Perfect. No one suspected
you were hiding in here alI day.

150
00:11:31,107 --> 00:11:33,984
The bank is closed,
and we're ready to begin our attack, right?

151
00:11:34,152 --> 00:11:35,235
BOTH:
Right, FF.

152
00:11:35,403 --> 00:11:37,696
FALSE FACE:
Brinks, the bars.

153
00:11:44,037 --> 00:11:46,038
[WHIRRING]

154
00:11:57,884 --> 00:11:58,967
[BARS CLANK]

155
00:12:02,847 --> 00:12:04,348
FALSE FACE:
Very good, Brinks.

156
00:12:05,308 --> 00:12:08,268
Burns, careful, now.

157
00:12:08,436 --> 00:12:13,023
There's a very cunning eIectric eye
set just 1 8 inches above the fIoor.

158
00:12:13,191 --> 00:12:15,067
-Go.
-Right, FF.

159
00:12:39,676 --> 00:12:41,593
Electric-eye aIarm eIiminated.

160
00:12:41,761 --> 00:12:43,762
[FALSE FACE LAUGHS]

161
00:12:44,681 --> 00:12:46,848
FALSE FACE:
ExceIIent, exceIlent, excelIent.

162
00:12:47,016 --> 00:12:49,393
Pinkerton, the TNT timed torpedo.

163
00:12:49,560 --> 00:12:51,812
Yes, FF.

164
00:12:57,527 --> 00:12:59,236
Back, back.

165
00:13:04,158 --> 00:13:05,284
You did it, FF.

166
00:13:05,451 --> 00:13:07,703
We're rich, beyond the dreams of avarice.

167
00:13:07,870 --> 00:13:09,871
FALSE FACE:
Not my dreams of avarice.

168
00:13:10,039 --> 00:13:12,291
QuickIy, now, Ioot sacks out.

169
00:13:17,588 --> 00:13:19,673
Now, Iet me at that Iock. Is it cIean?

170
00:13:19,841 --> 00:13:21,758
I'II dust it, FF.

171
00:13:21,926 --> 00:13:23,218
He's so fastidious.

172
00:13:26,639 --> 00:13:28,682
FALSE FACE:
What? Is it possibIe?

173
00:13:28,850 --> 00:13:30,642
Not only possibIe but true.

174
00:13:32,061 --> 00:13:34,813
FALSE FACE:
Please. Not that word.

175
00:13:34,981 --> 00:13:39,109
We've turned your own tricky tables on you,
False Face, via a false vauIt.

176
00:13:40,194 --> 00:13:44,323
I'm never out-tricked untiI the Iast turn,
Boy Wonder.

177
00:13:50,580 --> 00:13:51,830
[BOTH GRUNTING]

178
00:13:53,791 --> 00:13:57,169
Chief O'Hara, teIl your men
to search alI these cubicles.

179
00:14:11,267 --> 00:14:13,101
-CarefuI.
O'HARA: Ow!

180
00:14:13,269 --> 00:14:14,936
I'II handle him, chief.

181
00:14:15,104 --> 00:14:17,105
O'HARA:
Good man.

182
00:14:24,030 --> 00:14:26,698
-He's been gassed.
-By that counterfeit poIiceman, FaIse Face.

183
00:14:26,866 --> 00:14:28,784
After him, Robin.

184
00:14:29,118 --> 00:14:30,786
[O'HARA MUMBLES]

185
00:14:36,751 --> 00:14:38,585
FALSE FACE:
The dogged duo is in hot pursuit.

186
00:14:38,753 --> 00:14:40,253
And they'II catch you, FaIse Face.

187
00:14:40,838 --> 00:14:41,922
FALSE FACE:
I hope so.

188
00:14:42,090 --> 00:14:45,425
I sincerely hope so, because, you little fooI...

189
00:14:45,593 --> 00:14:48,720
...I'm leading them
into a truIy torturous trap.

190
00:14:48,888 --> 00:14:50,514
[FALSE FACE LAUGHS]

191
00:14:56,062 --> 00:14:59,147
NARRATOR:
<i>What is False Face's fiendish foolery?</i>

192
00:14:59,315 --> 00:15:02,776
<i>Are the Caped Crusaders</i>
<i>heading into a cul-de-sac?</i>

193
00:15:02,944 --> 00:15:08,198
<i>Will this be the dead end</i>
<i>for the dedicated deeds of Batman and Robin?</i>

194
00:15:08,366 --> 00:15:11,493
The oId Bioscope Studios.
It's been abandoned for years.

195
00:15:11,661 --> 00:15:15,664
False Face must have his hideout here
in the crumbIing sets and faded faIse fronts.

196
00:15:15,832 --> 00:15:21,294
We'II expose his concealments to the Iight
of day and put him behind reaI bars.

197
00:15:31,431 --> 00:15:32,597
FALSE FACE:
Good.

198
00:15:32,765 --> 00:15:34,599
They're hot on my trail.

199
00:15:34,767 --> 00:15:38,145
And very soon, they may be even hotter.

200
00:15:38,312 --> 00:15:41,189
As a matter of fact, perhaps too hot.

201
00:15:41,357 --> 00:15:42,899
Oh, you monster!

202
00:16:05,590 --> 00:16:07,466
HoIy rats in a trap.

203
00:16:10,428 --> 00:16:12,721
False Face is getting away.

204
00:16:12,889 --> 00:16:15,390
No, Robin, he seems
to be coming back this way.

205
00:16:17,560 --> 00:16:19,561
What is he up to?

206
00:16:20,271 --> 00:16:21,605
Let's find out, Robin.

207
00:17:11,614 --> 00:17:12,739
Commissioner...

208
00:17:12,907 --> 00:17:15,951
...dispatch a patroI car
to the abandoned Bioscope Studios...

209
00:17:16,118 --> 00:17:18,703
...to pick up a couple of thugs
that Robin and I netted.

210
00:17:18,871 --> 00:17:23,667
And we expect to add FaIse Face himself
to the coIIection shortIy. Hmm.

211
00:17:23,834 --> 00:17:28,338
False Face may stiIl have a pIot or two
in his bag of fiendish tricks.

212
00:17:28,506 --> 00:17:32,634
It's time for a IittIe trickery of our own,
Robin.

213
00:17:52,989 --> 00:17:54,447
[CHUCKLES]

214
00:17:54,615 --> 00:17:56,992
FALSE FACE:
They're coming right at me.

215
00:18:04,500 --> 00:18:05,667
[SCREAMS]

216
00:18:09,755 --> 00:18:12,090
FALSE FACE:
I've done it. I've done it.

217
00:18:12,258 --> 00:18:14,342
I destroyed the Dynamic Duo.

218
00:18:14,510 --> 00:18:17,637
-You diaboIicaI demon!
-Uh-huh.

219
00:18:17,805 --> 00:18:20,974
WelI, your cIever Caped Crusaders
are now kaput.

220
00:18:21,142 --> 00:18:23,143
[BATMOBILE HUMMING]

221
00:18:32,695 --> 00:18:34,654
BriIIiantIy done, Batman.

222
00:18:35,031 --> 00:18:37,365
FALSE FACE:
But I bIew up the BatmobiIe.

223
00:18:37,533 --> 00:18:38,700
I saw it go.

224
00:18:38,868 --> 00:18:40,368
Not exactIy, FaIse Face.

225
00:18:40,536 --> 00:18:42,537
You destroyed a false BatmobiIe.

226
00:18:42,705 --> 00:18:46,374
An infIated dupIicate that I'd prepared
for just this kind of situation.

227
00:18:46,709 --> 00:18:48,209
ROBIN:
Face it, FaIse Face.

228
00:18:48,377 --> 00:18:50,086
You've been out-decoyed.

229
00:18:50,254 --> 00:18:52,505
You feIl for a phony target.

230
00:18:52,673 --> 00:18:55,967
Now, wilI you come quietIy?

231
00:18:57,386 --> 00:19:00,180
FALSE FACE:
Not yet, Dynamic Duo.

232
00:19:08,397 --> 00:19:11,066
Wait, it's faster on foot. Get me out of here.

233
00:19:44,600 --> 00:19:46,601
[SIREN WAILING]

234
00:20:21,303 --> 00:20:22,971
Stay here, Robin.

235
00:20:25,599 --> 00:20:27,934
Howdy, partners. What's aII the ruckus?

236
00:20:28,102 --> 00:20:29,477
O'HARA:
There's a criminaI Ioose.

237
00:20:31,647 --> 00:20:33,648
RustIers, huh?

238
00:20:34,108 --> 00:20:37,152
WelI, I'II join the posse myself.

239
00:20:38,654 --> 00:20:41,156
I'II head him off at the pass.

240
00:20:42,158 --> 00:20:44,367
Pass intercepted, FaIse Face.

241
00:21:15,357 --> 00:21:16,399
[GORDON COUGHING]

242
00:21:16,567 --> 00:21:17,942
Commissioner.

243
00:21:18,110 --> 00:21:19,319
Are you alI right?

244
00:21:19,487 --> 00:21:22,238
Yes, but the trickster got away from me,
vanished that way.

245
00:21:22,406 --> 00:21:24,699
-Let's get after him.
GORDON: I'Il send reinforcements.

246
00:21:24,867 --> 00:21:27,285
I must get back to my office.
Order me a squad car.

247
00:21:27,453 --> 00:21:29,204
O'HARA: Yes, sir.
-That's not necessary.

248
00:21:29,371 --> 00:21:32,248
False Face must be found
before he springs another scheme.

249
00:21:32,708 --> 00:21:35,752
AbsoIuteIy accurate, FaIse Face.

250
00:21:35,920 --> 00:21:37,545
[O'HARA GASPS]

251
00:21:37,713 --> 00:21:40,965
But, Caped Crusader,
that's the commissioner.

252
00:21:41,133 --> 00:21:45,553
Is it? Then why is a right-handed commissioner
hoIding his handkerchief in his left hand?

253
00:21:56,524 --> 00:21:59,484
Saints alive, it's FaIse Face.

254
00:21:59,652 --> 00:22:03,947
BLAZE: So you finalIy fumbIed, FaIse Face.
FALSE FACE: For the moment.

255
00:22:05,074 --> 00:22:06,950
I Iost him.

256
00:22:07,326 --> 00:22:10,620
Luckily, commissioner, he found us.

257
00:22:10,788 --> 00:22:12,997
Impersonating a police commissioner.

258
00:22:13,165 --> 00:22:17,418
WelI, the warden wiII be working out
a warm weIcome for you.

259
00:22:20,422 --> 00:22:23,424
FALSE FACE:
Game and set to you, Caped Crusader.

260
00:22:23,592 --> 00:22:26,970
But wait, you may yet meet your match.

261
00:22:37,898 --> 00:22:40,692
Come. Come, now. Let's not be late.

262
00:22:40,860 --> 00:22:45,029
You know how sensitive a criminaI can be
the first day of parole.

263
00:22:45,197 --> 00:22:47,824
-But which criminaI?
-And why here?

264
00:22:47,992 --> 00:22:52,620
Because the Bruce Wayne RehabiIitation Fund
arranged for it alI.

265
00:22:52,788 --> 00:22:59,168
And I must say, I think this one magnificent
success justifies the entire risk.

266
00:22:59,336 --> 00:23:05,258
Just think, a hardened criminal,
compIeteIy reformed.

267
00:23:06,927 --> 00:23:09,512
You may come in now.

268
00:23:09,680 --> 00:23:11,139
Penguin?

269
00:23:11,307 --> 00:23:12,348
Joker?

270
00:23:16,145 --> 00:23:17,645
Blaze.

271
00:23:20,566 --> 00:23:24,736
Good morning, Mr. Wayne, Mr. Grayson.

272
00:23:25,487 --> 00:23:28,406
I want to thank you personaIly, Mr. Wayne...

273
00:23:28,574 --> 00:23:33,620
...for because of your rehabiIitation fund,
I feel like a new girI.

274
00:23:33,787 --> 00:23:35,663
The pIeasure is truIy mine.

275
00:23:35,831 --> 00:23:38,750
-What are your pIans now, miss?
-I pIan to go to New Zealand...

276
00:23:38,918 --> 00:23:41,502
...to keep house
for my poor but honest brother.

277
00:23:41,670 --> 00:23:43,004
He's a sheepherder.

278
00:23:43,172 --> 00:23:44,881
An entire new Iife.

279
00:23:45,299 --> 00:23:47,508
Oh, I think that's simpIy fine.

280
00:23:47,801 --> 00:23:51,387
And you, Mr. Wayne, are one of the two men
who have made this possibIe.

281
00:23:51,555 --> 00:23:54,641
Two men? Who was the other one?

282
00:23:54,808 --> 00:23:55,850
Batman.

283
00:23:56,352 --> 00:23:58,478
HARRIET:
The scourge of crime?

284
00:23:58,979 --> 00:24:01,731
The Caped Crusader himseIf.

285
00:24:01,899 --> 00:24:04,692
I hope when I have paid my debt to society...

286
00:24:04,860 --> 00:24:08,821
...that I can in some way, somehow,
repay Batman.

287
00:24:09,073 --> 00:24:11,699
I wouId think that somehow,
he knows of your redemption.

288
00:24:11,867 --> 00:24:14,369
And somewhere, he is glad.

289
00:25:11,093 --> 00:25:13,094
[EngIish - US - SDH]

