1
00:00:10,260 --> 00:00:14,138
NARRATOR:
<i>It is midnight and Gotham City sleeps...</i>

2
00:00:14,348 --> 00:00:16,182
<i>...but not everyone...</i>

3
00:00:16,391 --> 00:00:21,354
<i>...for there is evil afoot</i>
<i>in the Gotham City Art Museum.</i>

4
00:00:23,440 --> 00:00:25,650
[CAT MEOWS]

5
00:00:26,109 --> 00:00:29,153
What's that? Who's there?

6
00:00:30,364 --> 00:00:31,697
[CAT SCREECHES]

7
00:01:10,737 --> 00:01:12,154
I know it was vaIuabIe.

8
00:01:12,364 --> 00:01:15,658
But why'd they take onIy that and
leave aIl those other magnificent treasures?

9
00:01:15,826 --> 00:01:17,577
I'm as puzzIed as you are, commissioner.

10
00:01:17,744 --> 00:01:18,786
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]

11
00:01:18,954 --> 00:01:20,580
GORDON:
Uh-- Oh, Bonnie, come in. Come in.

12
00:01:20,747 --> 00:01:24,000
The oddest-Iooking man left this for you, sir.
He said it was important.

13
00:01:24,209 --> 00:01:27,712
GORDON: Odd-looking? In what way, Bonnie?
-I'm just not sure, commissioner.

14
00:01:27,921 --> 00:01:30,298
He was as jumpy as a cat.

15
00:01:30,507 --> 00:01:32,717
GORDON:
Thank you. Thank you, Bonnie.

16
00:01:34,553 --> 00:01:36,470
A kitten.

17
00:01:36,638 --> 00:01:39,640
O'HARA:
Ah, Iook, there's a bit of paper under his coIlar.

18
00:01:39,808 --> 00:01:42,643
Yes, Iooks Iike a newspaper cIipping.
What do you make of it, O'Hara?

19
00:01:42,811 --> 00:01:43,853
[KITTEN MEOWS]

20
00:01:44,021 --> 00:01:47,773
What? Wait, that's Mark Andrews,
the muItimiIIionaire...

21
00:01:47,983 --> 00:01:52,987
...owner of the stoIen golden cat.
And, Iook, one of them has been crossed out.

22
00:01:53,196 --> 00:01:56,407
And those two cats are onIy
a smaII part of his priceIess colIection.

23
00:01:56,617 --> 00:02:02,371
Yes, one was on Ioan to the museum,
and the other is at the Gotham City Exposition.

24
00:02:02,581 --> 00:02:07,084
-I smeIl the tracks of a feline predator.
-You mean...?

25
00:02:07,294 --> 00:02:09,587
Exactly. The Catwoman.

26
00:02:09,796 --> 00:02:12,506
I'm afraid this caIIs
for more drastic methods.

27
00:02:12,674 --> 00:02:14,050
[KITTEN MEOWING]

28
00:02:21,600 --> 00:02:24,435
It's actuaIIy quite rudimentary, Dick.

29
00:02:24,645 --> 00:02:27,480
You just have to think
14 moves ahead, that's aII.

30
00:02:27,689 --> 00:02:29,899
HoIy Reshevsky.

31
00:02:30,108 --> 00:02:33,361
Gosh, Bruce, I think
I'II just stick to Latin crossword puzzles.

32
00:02:33,528 --> 00:02:35,029
[BRUCE CHUCKLES]

33
00:02:40,911 --> 00:02:42,203
[ALFRED CLEARS THROAT]

34
00:02:42,371 --> 00:02:45,623
-Yes, AIfred?
-The phone, sir.

35
00:02:46,792 --> 00:02:49,251
WelI, I didn't hear the phone.

36
00:02:49,461 --> 00:02:53,464
Oh, I, uh-- Heh.
I was just making a caIl, madam...

37
00:02:53,674 --> 00:02:55,716
...and there was someone on the Iine
for Mr. Wayne.

38
00:02:55,884 --> 00:02:58,427
Oh, yes, that's happened to me too.

39
00:02:58,637 --> 00:03:01,472
We'II finish our snack Iater, Aunt Harriet.

40
00:03:02,099 --> 00:03:03,140
[ALFRED CHUCKLES]

41
00:03:07,354 --> 00:03:09,522
-Yes, commissioner?
GORDON [OVER PHONE]: <i>D</i><i>re</i><i>a</i><i>d</i><i>fu</i><i>l</i> <i>n</i><i>e</i><i>ws</i><i>.</i>

42
00:03:09,690 --> 00:03:13,275
<i>-Catwoman is on the prowl again.</i>
-We're on our way.

43
00:03:14,277 --> 00:03:16,278
To the Batpoles.

44
00:04:42,240 --> 00:04:45,034
We beIieve that this is just
the first of the planned robberies.

45
00:04:45,202 --> 00:04:46,494
Good thinking, commissioner.

46
00:04:46,661 --> 00:04:49,747
ObviousIy, the Catwoman
would not be satisfied with onIy this.

47
00:04:49,956 --> 00:04:53,542
No, I'm certain this is mereIy the first stitch
in a Iarge tapestry of crime.

48
00:04:53,752 --> 00:04:56,086
And the cIipping?

49
00:04:56,296 --> 00:04:58,255
There is a great deaI of hidden significance...

50
00:04:58,423 --> 00:05:02,092
...in the fact that just one
of the cats is scratched out.

51
00:05:03,178 --> 00:05:06,722
Gosh, I wish Mark Andrews was here.
I'II bet he could give us some more info.

52
00:05:06,932 --> 00:05:08,641
ANDREWS:
And indeed, I can.

53
00:05:08,850 --> 00:05:11,435
GORDON: Batman and Robin, the Boy Wonder,
this is Mark Andrews.

54
00:05:11,686 --> 00:05:13,771
We calIed him
to come down to headquarters.

55
00:05:14,022 --> 00:05:16,524
-How do you do, Mr. Andrews?
-What a thriII this is, Batman.

56
00:05:16,691 --> 00:05:20,569
I've foIIowed your expIoits for years.
Nice meeting you too, Robin.

57
00:05:20,779 --> 00:05:23,280
This clipping indicates
that there are two golden cats.

58
00:05:23,532 --> 00:05:26,200
Yes, the second one
is at the Gotham City Exposition.

59
00:05:26,701 --> 00:05:30,579
I wouIdn't Iend any one institution
both cats at one time.

60
00:05:30,789 --> 00:05:32,790
-Insurance, you know.
-Yes, I understand.

61
00:05:33,041 --> 00:05:36,085
-How Iong is it on dispIay at the exposition?
-UntiI this evening.

62
00:05:36,294 --> 00:05:39,046
So if Catwoman is going to steaI that one,
she'II do it tonight.

63
00:05:39,214 --> 00:05:41,799
Correct, Robin. There's no time to lose.

64
00:05:42,050 --> 00:05:44,802
WilI you be wanting
any extra poIice protection?

65
00:05:45,053 --> 00:05:46,303
No, thank you, Chief O'Hara.

66
00:05:46,555 --> 00:05:49,932
I certainIy don't mean to cast
any aspersions on the PoIice Department.

67
00:05:50,183 --> 00:05:53,811
But this time,
I think Robin and I better go it aIone.

68
00:05:54,145 --> 00:05:58,649
Any large contingent of poIice officers
might create unnecessary confusion.

69
00:05:58,817 --> 00:06:02,319
Whatever you say, Batman.
I know it'Il be safe with you on the job.

70
00:06:03,321 --> 00:06:04,905
Let's go, Robin.

71
00:06:08,159 --> 00:06:11,036
-It just doesn't sound right.
-Too easy, is it, Robin?

72
00:06:11,288 --> 00:06:14,999
First the cat at the museum,
then the cat at the exposition.

73
00:06:15,208 --> 00:06:17,334
Then.... Then....

74
00:06:17,544 --> 00:06:21,005
-The rest of Mark Andrews' colIection.
-HoIy trickery, you're right.

75
00:06:21,172 --> 00:06:24,842
But I don't understand why Catwoman
would teIl us what she's planning.

76
00:06:25,010 --> 00:06:29,597
Maybe to give us a faIse Iead
to hide the real crime.

77
00:06:30,056 --> 00:06:31,765
[ALARM BUZZES]

78
00:06:31,933 --> 00:06:36,520
-You haven't fastened your safety Bat BeIt.
-We're onIy going a coupIe of blocks.

79
00:06:36,730 --> 00:06:40,733
It won't be Iong untiI you're oId enough
to get a driver's Iicense, Robin.

80
00:06:40,942 --> 00:06:45,195
Then you'lI be abIe to drive
the BatmobiIe and other vehicIes.

81
00:06:45,363 --> 00:06:50,367
-Remember, motorists' safety.
-Gosh, Batman, when you put it that way....

82
00:06:52,037 --> 00:06:56,957
<i></i>N<i></i>A<i></i>R<i></i>RAT<i></i>O<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> Meanwhile, in a quiet alley</i>
<i>in the heart of downtown Gotham City...</i>

83
00:06:57,208 --> 00:07:01,587
<i>...is a fur warehouse,</i>
<i>an innocent place of business.</i>

84
00:07:01,838 --> 00:07:03,213
<i>Or is it?</i>

85
00:07:07,135 --> 00:07:10,137
What a beauty.
I'II bet it's worth a smalI fortune.

86
00:07:10,347 --> 00:07:14,350
Heh. Fat lot of good that does us.
She stoIe it, but she won't seII it.

87
00:07:14,559 --> 00:07:17,102
Yeah, I wonder why.
We should get our cut.

88
00:07:17,270 --> 00:07:18,646
[WHIP CRACKS]

89
00:07:22,901 --> 00:07:25,277
CATWOMAN:
Yours is not to reason why.

90
00:07:25,487 --> 00:07:30,407
Yours is to do as I teII you to,
or you'II keep tasting my cat o' nine tails.

91
00:07:30,575 --> 00:07:32,284
[CAT MEOWS]

92
00:07:36,414 --> 00:07:39,291
-Leo, did you get the books?
LEO: Yes, Catwoman.

93
00:07:39,501 --> 00:07:43,671
I had to go alI the way down to the main library,
but I got every one of them.

94
00:07:44,923 --> 00:07:47,925
-Felix, what about the deIivery?
FELIX: Smooth as cream.

95
00:07:48,093 --> 00:07:50,761
-Made it without a hitch.
CATWOMAN: Good.

96
00:07:51,179 --> 00:07:53,597
I know that Batman and Robin
wiIl swaIlow the bait.

97
00:07:53,765 --> 00:07:58,394
And when they do, I'II be rid of that
dynamic duo once and for alI.

98
00:07:58,603 --> 00:08:00,980
Others have tried but failed.

99
00:08:01,606 --> 00:08:03,816
The Catwoman is not like the others.

100
00:08:04,025 --> 00:08:08,112
I'II show you how to cIip
Batman and Robin's wings. I wiII prevail.

101
00:08:08,279 --> 00:08:14,201
Oh, joy, success and revenge
aII wrapped up into one sweet package.

102
00:08:14,452 --> 00:08:17,287
We're sorry, Catwoman.
We didn't mean to step on your paws.

103
00:08:17,455 --> 00:08:18,872
CATWOMAN:
Hm.

104
00:08:19,040 --> 00:08:21,792
WelI, don't do it again.
Now, where are the books?

105
00:08:22,002 --> 00:08:23,627
I'II get them for you, Catwoman.

106
00:08:23,795 --> 00:08:25,212
[CAT MEOWS]

107
00:08:27,632 --> 00:08:30,843
Each of you know
what you have to do, so do it.

108
00:08:31,052 --> 00:08:32,302
And remember this...

109
00:08:32,470 --> 00:08:35,639
...once we get that other cat,
the key to untold riches wiIl be ours.

110
00:08:35,849 --> 00:08:37,474
Yes, Catwoman.

111
00:08:41,021 --> 00:08:43,480
[CATWOMAN CHUCKLING]

112
00:09:03,376 --> 00:09:04,835
Meow.

113
00:09:12,010 --> 00:09:14,178
[TIRES SCREECHING]

114
00:09:15,013 --> 00:09:17,473
Good afternoon, sir. TroubIe?

115
00:09:17,682 --> 00:09:20,267
The Catwoman
has unsheathed her cIaws again.

116
00:09:20,518 --> 00:09:22,895
Oh, wilI she never Iearn?

117
00:09:23,104 --> 00:09:25,606
WhiIe the atomic reactor
is recharging the BatmobiIe...

118
00:09:25,857 --> 00:09:29,860
...pIease heIp Robin with the auxiliary
power channeI. Time is of the essence.

119
00:09:40,121 --> 00:09:45,375
-AlI set in the auxiIiary power channeI.
-Good. The solution is ready.

120
00:09:45,543 --> 00:09:49,379
Increase the power to 1 7,000 kW.

121
00:09:49,547 --> 00:09:51,757
[WHIRRING]

122
00:10:12,570 --> 00:10:17,574
-Power to 1 7,000 kW.
-That's it. AIl power off.

123
00:10:17,784 --> 00:10:19,034
AlI power off.

124
00:10:19,244 --> 00:10:20,410
-Alfred.
-Yes, sir?

125
00:10:20,620 --> 00:10:24,456
Please attach that high-pressure can
to the outIet valve.

126
00:10:36,678 --> 00:10:39,263
[RATTLING]

127
00:10:39,430 --> 00:10:43,016
There. That wiIl neutraIize
the dangerous radioactivity...

128
00:10:43,184 --> 00:10:46,436
...and give us just the proper
amount of emission for our purposes.

129
00:10:46,604 --> 00:10:50,107
May one inquire, sir,
exactIy what are your purposes?

130
00:10:50,316 --> 00:10:51,441
Of course, AIfred.

131
00:10:51,609 --> 00:10:54,778
It's a defense mechanism
in case the Catwoman eludes us tonight...

132
00:10:54,988 --> 00:10:57,614
...and decides to make off with her prize.

133
00:10:57,824 --> 00:11:00,784
You see, we spray this radioactive mist
on an object...

134
00:11:00,952 --> 00:11:04,371
...and then we can trace it on the Bat-o-meter
within a radius of 50 miles.

135
00:11:04,622 --> 00:11:05,622
Remarkable.

136
00:11:07,125 --> 00:11:12,963
When deaIing with powerfuI criminaI eIements,
one can never be too weIl-prepared. Let's go.

137
00:11:25,018 --> 00:11:30,230
-Batman, Robin, this way, please.
BATMAN: Thank you, citizens.

138
00:11:31,441 --> 00:11:34,276
No need for you to wait in Iine.
You're on officiaI business?

139
00:11:34,444 --> 00:11:38,280
-I'd rather not say.
-There's no charge for you. Go right in.

140
00:11:38,531 --> 00:11:42,534
No, I'd rather pay
just like any other ordinary citizen.

141
00:11:51,753 --> 00:11:53,545
[PHONE MEOWS]

142
00:11:54,255 --> 00:11:56,256
-Yes?
LEO [OVER PHONE]:<i>T</i><i>h</i><i>e</i><i>y</i><i>'r</i><i>e</i> <i>h</i><i>e</i><i>re</i><i>.</i>

143
00:11:56,466 --> 00:11:59,676
-ExceIIent.
-This pIace cIoses at 6.

144
00:11:59,886 --> 00:12:01,845
One of the guards toId me
that Batman and Robin...

145
00:12:02,055 --> 00:12:04,598
...wiIl be in the Great HaIl
of CuIture and Art aIone.

146
00:12:04,766 --> 00:12:07,142
SpIendid.

147
00:12:07,602 --> 00:12:12,189
FELIX: Is everything okay?
-Perfect.

148
00:12:12,440 --> 00:12:15,108
FELIX:
WelI, I, for one, just don't Iike it, that's aIl.

149
00:12:15,276 --> 00:12:18,278
I mean, deaIing with Batman and Robin.

150
00:12:18,488 --> 00:12:21,698
WelI, I don't know,
it just makes me nervous.

151
00:12:21,950 --> 00:12:23,325
Everything makes you nervous.

152
00:12:23,576 --> 00:12:26,578
WelI, I'd feeI a lot better
if I knew who he realIy was.

153
00:12:26,788 --> 00:12:30,624
The whoIe idea of a bat bothers me.

154
00:12:30,792 --> 00:12:33,168
That's exactly what I'd expect from you.

155
00:12:33,336 --> 00:12:35,295
[NECKLACE MEOWING]

156
00:12:36,965 --> 00:12:42,344
Five-thirty, just enough time
for a catnap. FeIix, scram.

157
00:12:42,595 --> 00:12:47,182
And have the car parked catty-corner
at exactIy 1 1 sharp.

158
00:12:47,392 --> 00:12:49,017
FELIX:
Right.

159
00:13:00,530 --> 00:13:01,989
There.

160
00:13:02,156 --> 00:13:06,493
Now we'lI be abIe to trace the radioactivity
within a 50-miIe radius.

161
00:13:07,412 --> 00:13:08,495
Hm.

162
00:13:08,663 --> 00:13:11,540
Almost midnight.
Time to check the exits again.

163
00:13:11,749 --> 00:13:14,001
ROBIN: I'Il do it.
-No, Robin.

164
00:13:14,168 --> 00:13:16,003
You better Iet me do it this time.

165
00:13:16,212 --> 00:13:19,548
if you see or hear anything,
let me know via the Bat communicator.

166
00:13:19,757 --> 00:13:23,677
-I'II be back in three minutes and 20 seconds.
-Right.

167
00:13:49,287 --> 00:13:50,829
[CAT MEOWS]

168
00:13:50,997 --> 00:13:53,457
HoIy cats, a cat.

169
00:13:53,666 --> 00:13:55,709
[CAT SCREECHES]

170
00:14:01,966 --> 00:14:05,218
HeIp, Batman, help.

171
00:14:06,387 --> 00:14:07,763
What is it, Robin? Answer me.

172
00:14:08,014 --> 00:14:10,265
Ah....

173
00:14:10,433 --> 00:14:15,604
Poor IittIe Robin.
Did the itty-bitty kitty ruffIe your feathers?

174
00:14:20,735 --> 00:14:23,945
[HUMMING]

175
00:14:25,406 --> 00:14:27,282
You feIine deviI.

176
00:14:27,533 --> 00:14:29,117
What have you done with Robin?

177
00:14:29,285 --> 00:14:32,537
Oh, is that any way to greet
an old friend, Batman?

178
00:14:32,747 --> 00:14:34,706
Not even a "heIIo, how are you"?

179
00:14:34,874 --> 00:14:36,792
[HISSES]

180
00:14:36,959 --> 00:14:38,794
Meow.

181
00:14:38,961 --> 00:14:41,380
Teach him some manners, feIlas.

182
00:15:15,832 --> 00:15:18,250
BATMAN:
Robin, oId chum.

183
00:15:21,921 --> 00:15:23,922
Come on, cats, Iet's get out of here.

184
00:15:33,307 --> 00:15:35,934
What happened? The cat.

185
00:15:36,144 --> 00:15:39,146
Easy now, Robin,
you were drugged with catclaw...

186
00:15:39,355 --> 00:15:42,691
...a fiendish preparation designed to attack
the central nervous system.

187
00:15:42,859 --> 00:15:45,735
The universal drug antidote pilIs
wiIl fix you up posthaste.

188
00:15:45,945 --> 00:15:49,156
-Did she get the cat?
-Yes, Robin.

189
00:15:49,365 --> 00:15:51,366
It's just as I pIanned it.

190
00:15:51,534 --> 00:15:56,788
Now the Catwoman herseIf wilI Iead us
to her Iair and the recovery of both cats.

191
00:15:58,374 --> 00:16:01,543
[BEEPING]

192
00:16:01,794 --> 00:16:04,337
Batman, the Bat-o-meter
is functioning perfectIy.

193
00:16:04,547 --> 00:16:07,340
AlI we do is foIIow the blip
and we're on the traiI.

194
00:16:09,760 --> 00:16:11,887
CATWOMAN:
Of course I know they're on our traiI.

195
00:16:12,138 --> 00:16:14,639
They wouIdn't be Batman and Robin
if they weren't.

196
00:16:14,849 --> 00:16:16,725
Are we set to greet our two pigeons?

197
00:16:16,893 --> 00:16:19,227
Oh, they're going to get a helIo
they'lI never forget.

198
00:16:19,395 --> 00:16:23,064
Good. Just make sure
nothing goes wrong.

199
00:16:23,274 --> 00:16:26,193
I wouIdn't wanna miss this opportunity.

200
00:16:26,360 --> 00:16:29,196
FELIX:
We're ready whenever you are, Catwoman.

201
00:16:29,906 --> 00:16:31,865
-Felix.
-Yes, Catwoman?

202
00:16:32,533 --> 00:16:34,576
You can brush my pussy wiIlows
before you Ieave.

203
00:16:36,245 --> 00:16:41,374
-And don't go against the fur.
-I'II treat them Iike they was my very own.

204
00:17:24,085 --> 00:17:27,087
This is it, Robin. She's in that building.

205
00:17:29,090 --> 00:17:31,800
How can you be sure, Batman?

206
00:17:32,051 --> 00:17:34,761
BATMAN:
Look up, Robin, the sign over the door.

207
00:17:34,929 --> 00:17:36,805
ROBIN:
"Gato and Chat Fur Company."

208
00:17:36,973 --> 00:17:40,392
<i>G</i><i>a</i><i>to</i> means "cat" in Spanish,
and <i>c</i><i>h</i><i>a</i><i>t</i> means "cat" in French.

209
00:17:40,601 --> 00:17:43,270
Only the Catwoman would choose
a hideout with those names.

210
00:17:43,479 --> 00:17:47,482
I'm gIad you're up on your foreign Ianguages.
They come in handy when fighting crime.

211
00:17:47,650 --> 00:17:49,568
<i>S</i><i>í</i><i>,</i> <i>s</i><i>í,</i> Batman. What do we do now?

212
00:17:49,735 --> 00:17:52,487
There are no entrances and onIy one door.
We have no choice.

213
00:17:52,655 --> 00:17:56,116
-We'II use the Bat Beam in the BatmobiIe.
-Why don't we just walk right in?

214
00:17:56,284 --> 00:17:57,742
BATMAN:
The door may be booby-trapped.

215
00:17:57,910 --> 00:18:00,745
We won't take any chances
if we use the Bat Beam.

216
00:18:04,458 --> 00:18:06,001
Stand by for Bat Beam.

217
00:18:06,168 --> 00:18:07,502
[WHIRRING]

218
00:18:17,013 --> 00:18:19,306
You were right again, Batman.
We might have been kiIled.

219
00:18:19,515 --> 00:18:21,558
Or worse. Now, Iet's go.

220
00:18:25,855 --> 00:18:28,690
[CREAKS]

221
00:18:37,533 --> 00:18:39,159
ROBIN:
The door.

222
00:18:40,161 --> 00:18:44,581
It seems it wilI be more difficult
getting out of here than it was getting in.

223
00:18:44,790 --> 00:18:48,501
CATWOMAN [OVER PA]:
<i>Good evening, Batman and Robin. Welcome.</i>

224
00:18:49,962 --> 00:18:53,548
Good evening, Catwoman.
It seems as if you were expecting us.

225
00:18:53,716 --> 00:18:57,886
<i></i>C<i></i>ATW<i></i>O<i></i>M<i></i>A<i></i>N<i></i>:<i> I have a wonderful night</i>
<i>planned for you, and it starts right now.</i>

226
00:19:09,732 --> 00:19:11,191
Where are we?

227
00:19:11,400 --> 00:19:15,236
CATWOMAN: <i>Y</i><i>o</i><i>u</i> <i>a</i><i>re</i> <i>d</i><i>e</i><i>e</i><i>p</i>
<i>in the inner catacombs of this building.</i>

228
00:19:15,404 --> 00:19:19,658
<i>This is the last room you will ever occupy.</i>

229
00:19:20,743 --> 00:19:23,578
I've heard that song before, Catwoman.

230
00:19:23,746 --> 00:19:28,917
But the last few bars are aIways the same,
and the criminaI is always behind them.

231
00:19:30,211 --> 00:19:32,379
CATWOMAN:
This is my night to howI, Batman...

232
00:19:32,588 --> 00:19:35,882
...because tonight
you are the mice and I am the cat.

233
00:19:36,342 --> 00:19:38,593
<i>The old cat-and-mouse game, is it?</i>

234
00:19:38,761 --> 00:19:41,554
CATWOMAN:
You have a wonderfuI way with words, Batman.

235
00:19:42,390 --> 00:19:45,016
I couIdn't have put it any better.

236
00:19:45,601 --> 00:19:48,436
How does it feeI
to be the quarry for a change, hm?

237
00:19:48,604 --> 00:19:50,730
<i>Mm....</i>

238
00:19:51,774 --> 00:19:54,901
<i>What's the matter? Cat got your tongue?</i>

239
00:19:55,069 --> 00:19:57,278
[CATWOMAN LAUGHING]

240
00:19:59,031 --> 00:20:01,700
BATMAN:
<i>All right, you've had your laugh, Catwoman.</i>

241
00:20:02,410 --> 00:20:04,744
<i>-Now, what do you intend to do with us?</i>
CATWOMAN: Do?

242
00:20:05,746 --> 00:20:10,208
WelI, first, I'm gonna
give you two a few pointers.

243
00:20:13,045 --> 00:20:15,046
HoIy ice picks.

244
00:20:19,051 --> 00:20:23,430
-What are we gonna do, Batman?
<i></i>C<i></i>ATW<i></i>O<i></i>M<i></i>A<i></i>N<i></i>:<i> Ticklish situation, isn't it, Batman?</i>

245
00:20:23,639 --> 00:20:27,684
Hit the deck, Robin. I'Il get us out of this.

246
00:20:36,485 --> 00:20:39,279
[SCREECHING]

247
00:20:49,790 --> 00:20:52,625
These pointers are made
of painted rubber, Robin.

248
00:20:52,835 --> 00:20:54,836
[LAUGHING]

249
00:20:56,839 --> 00:20:59,841
<i>-The old cat-and-mouse game.</i>
<i>-Exactly.</i>

250
00:21:00,092 --> 00:21:05,096
CATWOMAN: But it was scary
for a while, wasn't it, Batman? Meow.

251
00:21:05,306 --> 00:21:08,641
<i>Your sense of humor</i>
<i>leaves me cold, Catwoman.</i>

252
00:21:08,809 --> 00:21:10,852
[LAUGHING]

253
00:21:11,020 --> 00:21:12,854
CATWOMAN:
Felix.

254
00:21:20,321 --> 00:21:25,325
Perhaps my next idea wilI warm you up,
Batman. It's quite interesting.

255
00:21:25,534 --> 00:21:30,747
-Almost catacIysmic.
-EviI is as evil does.

256
00:21:52,228 --> 00:21:53,561
[MEOWS]

257
00:21:53,729 --> 00:21:58,399
<i></i>C<i></i>ATW<i></i>O<i></i>M<i></i>A<i></i>N<i></i>:<i> Ha! Now, you have to admit</i>
<i>that was funny, Batman.</i>

258
00:21:59,360 --> 00:22:04,739
Your chiIdish antics Iead me to beIieve
you're a kitten, not a cat.

259
00:22:04,907 --> 00:22:06,199
[LAUGHING]

260
00:22:06,367 --> 00:22:07,909
CATWOMAN:
Leo?

261
00:22:13,374 --> 00:22:15,083
I'm bored with you, Batman.

262
00:22:15,251 --> 00:22:17,919
The time has come to separate
Damon from Pythias.

263
00:22:18,170 --> 00:22:22,882
The cataIog is cIosed.
Say goodbye to each other.

264
00:22:31,267 --> 00:22:34,936
<i>Say bye-bye to Robin.</i>
<i>Your little bird has flown.</i>

265
00:22:35,187 --> 00:22:36,437
What have you done with him?

266
00:22:36,605 --> 00:22:40,233
CATWOMAN:
<i>That's for me to know and you to find out.</i>

267
00:22:40,776 --> 00:22:45,446
-You feIine deviI.
-Tsk-tsk and another tsk, Batman.

268
00:22:45,614 --> 00:22:48,950
Why don't you just admit
I'm smarter than you are and Iet it go at that?

269
00:22:49,451 --> 00:22:52,787
There is more than one way
to skin a Catwoman.

270
00:22:53,122 --> 00:22:56,457
<i></i>C<i></i>ATW<i></i>O<i></i>M<i></i>A<i></i>N<i></i>:<i> You a betting man?</i>
-I never gambIe.

271
00:22:57,418 --> 00:23:02,171
WelI, this time you'II have to,
because I now have a wager you must accept.

272
00:23:02,548 --> 00:23:04,340
The stakes are your Iife.

273
00:23:04,550 --> 00:23:05,800
You Ieave me no choice.

274
00:23:05,968 --> 00:23:11,347
<i></i>C<i></i>ATW<i></i>O<i></i>M<i></i>A<i></i>N<i></i>:<i> Ah, but I do, and that is</i>
<i>the sum and substance of the bet.</i>

275
00:23:11,974 --> 00:23:17,437
<i>In front of you are two doors.</i>
<i>I'm standing behind one of them.</i>

276
00:23:17,646 --> 00:23:20,648
-And the other?
<i></i>C<i></i>ATW<i></i>O<i></i>M<i></i>A<i></i>N<i></i>:<i> Ah, there's the rub.</i>

277
00:23:20,858 --> 00:23:24,611
<i>Behind the other door</i>
<i>is a ferocious Batman-eating tiger.</i>

278
00:23:24,820 --> 00:23:27,614
-So the odds are even?
CATWOMAN: <i>C</i><i>o</i><i>rre</i><i>c</i><i>t</i><i>.</i>

279
00:23:27,823 --> 00:23:31,993
<i>If you pick the right door, l'm yours, Batman.</i>

280
00:23:32,244 --> 00:23:36,664
<i>If you pick the wrong door, you're mine.</i>

281
00:23:36,874 --> 00:23:41,878
<i>So which is it, Batman,</i>
<i>the lady or the tiger?</i>

282
00:23:45,841 --> 00:23:48,843
<i>The lady or the tiger?</i>

283
00:23:51,180 --> 00:23:52,889
[BUZZES]

284
00:23:53,432 --> 00:23:54,599
[GROWLS]

285
00:23:56,852 --> 00:24:00,480
NARRATOR:
<i>Will Batman ever see Robin alive again?</i>

286
00:24:01,357 --> 00:24:04,525
<i>Will Robin ever see Batman alive again?</i>

287
00:24:04,693 --> 00:24:07,528
[GROWLING]

288
00:24:08,656 --> 00:24:13,660
<i>Will our daring duo escape the claws</i>
<i>of the wily Catwoman?</i>

289
00:24:15,663 --> 00:24:19,707
[NARRATOR READS ON-SCREEN TEXT]

290
00:25:12,136 --> 00:25:14,137
[EngIish - US - SDH]

