1
00:00:09,468 --> 00:00:11,344
NARRATOR:
<i>So far, we have seen:</i>

2
00:00:11,512 --> 00:00:13,596
<i>A cat burglar strike.</i>

3
00:00:17,267 --> 00:00:20,520
<i>Commissioner Gordon got a gift.</i>

4
00:00:23,232 --> 00:00:24,899
<i>X marked the cat.</i>

5
00:00:28,445 --> 00:00:30,863
<i>Catwoman bare her claws.</i>

6
00:00:31,865 --> 00:00:34,992
<i>Batman and Robin on guard.</i>

7
00:00:35,994 --> 00:00:38,913
<i>Robin get it in the neck.</i>

8
00:00:40,832 --> 00:00:43,668
<i>Saved by Batman.</i>

9
00:00:47,047 --> 00:00:48,631
<i>Open sesame.</i>

10
00:00:49,925 --> 00:00:51,842
<i>Is this trip necessary?</i>

11
00:00:54,596 --> 00:00:56,973
<i>Sharp tactics.</i>

12
00:00:59,893 --> 00:01:02,937
<i>Two mice in a cat trap.</i>

13
00:01:03,939 --> 00:01:06,649
<i>Robin cat-apulted.</i>

14
00:01:10,946 --> 00:01:12,989
<i>The lady or the tiger?</i>

15
00:01:14,741 --> 00:01:17,368
<i>Cat-astrophe.</i>

16
00:01:17,869 --> 00:01:24,166
<i>And now, after a moment's cat's pause,</i>
<i>we'll continue.</i>

17
00:02:08,295 --> 00:02:10,296
[GROWLING]

18
00:03:24,913 --> 00:03:27,164
CATWOMAN:
You can't stay there forever, Batman.

19
00:03:27,332 --> 00:03:29,583
Your hands wiII Iose their strength.

20
00:03:29,751 --> 00:03:31,836
<i>Not while I have a breath left.</i>

21
00:03:32,671 --> 00:03:35,965
It's been a long time between bites
for Tinker BeIl.

22
00:03:36,425 --> 00:03:39,093
You shouId take better care of him,
Catwoman.

23
00:03:39,261 --> 00:03:41,595
After alI, pets are a responsibiIity.

24
00:03:42,097 --> 00:03:44,014
[GROWLING]

25
00:03:44,224 --> 00:03:46,684
Batman, it's been fun.

26
00:03:46,852 --> 00:03:51,522
But aII good things must come to an end
and the goodest ending I can think of is yours.

27
00:03:51,690 --> 00:03:53,274
It's not ended yet.

28
00:03:53,442 --> 00:03:54,775
CATWOMAN:
<i>It will soon.</i>

29
00:03:54,943 --> 00:03:57,027
<i>It's a pity l can't stay and watch.</i>

30
00:03:57,404 --> 00:04:00,531
But you know how I hate the sight of bIood.

31
00:04:00,699 --> 00:04:02,283
TTFN.

32
00:04:02,451 --> 00:04:04,410
<i>And what's that supposed to mean?</i>

33
00:04:04,578 --> 00:04:06,996
Ta-ta for now.

34
00:04:07,164 --> 00:04:10,124
I'm off to pIuck Robin's feathers.

35
00:04:13,879 --> 00:04:15,504
[GROWLING CONTINUES]

36
00:04:36,651 --> 00:04:40,780
<i></i>N<i></i>A<i></i>R<i></i>RAT<i></i>O<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> Calling on his fantastic storehouse</i>
<i>of audio engineering knowledge...</i>

37
00:04:41,156 --> 00:04:45,242
<i>...Batman nimbly reverses</i>
<i>the polarity on his communicator...</i>

38
00:04:46,703 --> 00:04:47,870
[HIGH-PITCHED SOUND BLARING]

39
00:04:48,038 --> 00:04:51,540
<i>...then increases the audio modulation</i>
<i>to about 20,000 decibels...</i>

40
00:04:51,708 --> 00:04:55,544
<i>...knowing full well</i>
<i>it will split the tiger's skull.</i>

41
00:05:19,027 --> 00:05:20,277
[SOUND STOPS]

42
00:05:52,602 --> 00:05:56,689
Don't bother, Robin. You wouIdn't know how
to get out of here even if you did get loose.

43
00:05:56,857 --> 00:05:58,023
Just you wait, Catwoman.

44
00:05:58,191 --> 00:06:00,568
Batman wiII be here in a minute
and you'II be sorry.

45
00:06:00,735 --> 00:06:03,070
He'II have to come a Iong way.

46
00:06:03,238 --> 00:06:04,864
We know what you're up to.

47
00:06:06,199 --> 00:06:09,034
Is that so? TelI me more.

48
00:06:09,744 --> 00:06:12,913
You wanna steaI Mark Andrews coIIection.
WelI, it just won't work.

49
00:06:13,081 --> 00:06:16,834
-The pIace is surrounded by poIice.
-Thanks for that information.

50
00:06:17,002 --> 00:06:19,336
But that doesn't change my plans one bit.

51
00:06:19,838 --> 00:06:22,882
You're racing up the wrong alIey.

52
00:06:23,425 --> 00:06:27,428
Felix, Leo, take Robin down
and clip his wings.

53
00:06:38,732 --> 00:06:42,610
<i></i>N<i></i>A<i></i>R<i></i>RAT<i></i>O<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> What now, Cowled Crusader?</i>
<i>Is it a cul-de-sac?</i>

54
00:06:42,819 --> 00:06:44,820
[TIGERS GROWLING]

55
00:07:02,339 --> 00:07:05,633
-Did you weigh him?
-Hundred and thirty-two pounds, 1 0 ounces.

56
00:07:05,800 --> 00:07:08,427
-Is that sand ready?
-AlI ready, Catwoman.

57
00:07:08,595 --> 00:07:11,096
Good. I'II baste him.

58
00:07:25,820 --> 00:07:28,781
Perfect. To the pit with him.

59
00:07:33,912 --> 00:07:36,163
The sand.

60
00:07:41,294 --> 00:07:44,505
Hundred and thirty-two pounds,
1 0 ounces exactIy.

61
00:07:54,474 --> 00:07:57,726
Catwoman, you are not a nice person.

62
00:07:59,020 --> 00:08:01,772
[LAUGHING]

63
00:08:02,482 --> 00:08:05,901
You must be curious, Boy Wonder,
why the strange feeding method.

64
00:08:06,069 --> 00:08:09,697
I'm aIways interested
in the workings of the criminaI mind.

65
00:08:09,906 --> 00:08:11,573
[GROWLING]

66
00:08:12,659 --> 00:08:15,536
My pets are orderIy beasts
and must be fed on time.

67
00:08:16,204 --> 00:08:17,788
So when enough sand runs out...

68
00:08:18,540 --> 00:08:20,749
...dinner is served.

69
00:08:29,175 --> 00:08:30,843
NARRATOR:
<i>Precious moments lost.</i>

70
00:08:31,011 --> 00:08:33,345
<i>There's only one possible way out.</i>

71
00:08:35,265 --> 00:08:37,099
WelI...

72
00:08:37,267 --> 00:08:39,518
...I have personaI engagements eIsewhere.

73
00:08:39,686 --> 00:08:42,187
My untrustworthy aides
wiIl take care of the detaiIs.

74
00:08:42,355 --> 00:08:46,025
Felix, Leo, I'lI meet you two later.

75
00:08:46,192 --> 00:08:48,068
LEO:
Right, Catwoman.

76
00:08:48,236 --> 00:08:49,319
FareweII, my lovely.

77
00:08:50,280 --> 00:08:56,243
Give my best to Batman when you see him
at that great scratching post in the sky.

78
00:09:06,337 --> 00:09:07,880
[MEOWS]

79
00:09:23,271 --> 00:09:27,399
<i></i>N<i></i>A<i></i>R<i></i>RAT<i></i>O<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> Have the sands of time run out</i>
<i>for the Boy Wonder?</i>

80
00:09:28,860 --> 00:09:30,861
[TIGERS GROWLING]

81
00:11:35,570 --> 00:11:36,904
BATMAN:
We'II tie them up, Robin...

82
00:11:37,071 --> 00:11:40,866
...then we'lI caIl headquarters
and have O'Hara's men come pick them up.

83
00:11:41,034 --> 00:11:43,035
[GRUNTING]

84
00:11:51,294 --> 00:11:54,087
ROBIN:
Batman, he's trying to escape.

85
00:11:55,715 --> 00:11:57,341
Maybe we can stiIl catch him.

86
00:11:57,508 --> 00:11:59,927
Better stilI, let's investigate this Iair.

87
00:12:00,094 --> 00:12:02,596
Perhaps we'II find Catwoman.

88
00:12:06,476 --> 00:12:08,477
[BEEPING]

89
00:12:11,564 --> 00:12:14,441
Yeah. Okay, CharIie. Okay.

90
00:12:20,448 --> 00:12:21,490
Yes?

91
00:12:21,658 --> 00:12:22,991
Oh, Boy Wonder.

92
00:12:23,159 --> 00:12:26,453
I've just returned from a Iate session
at the mayor's office.

93
00:12:26,621 --> 00:12:28,288
He wants action, fast.

94
00:12:28,706 --> 00:12:31,416
<i>-Is there anything I can tell him?</i>
-Yes, commissioner.

95
00:12:31,584 --> 00:12:33,585
We've captured one of the Catwoman's mob.

96
00:12:33,753 --> 00:12:36,922
Chief O'Hara can pick him up
at the Gato and Chat Warehouse...

97
00:12:37,090 --> 00:12:39,174
...at 2809 West 20th Street.

98
00:12:39,342 --> 00:12:43,053
WonderfuI. But telI me,
is there any word on Catwoman?

99
00:12:43,221 --> 00:12:45,722
She and her right-hand man, Leo,
made a clean getaway.

100
00:12:45,890 --> 00:12:49,434
-But we found the cats in her office.
<i>-That should take some of the pressure off.</i>

101
00:12:49,602 --> 00:12:52,229
<i>Does Batman have any inkling</i>
<i>of Catwoman's whereabouts?</i>

102
00:12:52,397 --> 00:12:55,524
No, sir. Any word from the stakeout
at the Andrews house?

103
00:12:55,692 --> 00:12:59,486
I'm in constant contact with them, Boy Wonder,
but there's no sign of Catwoman.

104
00:13:00,154 --> 00:13:02,406
Nothing at the Andrews house.

105
00:13:02,573 --> 00:13:07,202
WelI, then the next move is up to us.
TelI the Commissioner we'lI be in touch.

106
00:13:07,370 --> 00:13:08,954
Commissioner, we'lI be in touch.

107
00:13:09,497 --> 00:13:13,000
Over and out. And good Iuck.

108
00:13:14,460 --> 00:13:15,961
To aII of us.

109
00:13:16,170 --> 00:13:17,421
[SIGHS]

110
00:13:17,588 --> 00:13:20,632
I don't understand
why Catwoman would Ieave these behind...

111
00:13:20,800 --> 00:13:23,802
...especialIy after going to such great Iengths
to steaI them.

112
00:13:23,970 --> 00:13:25,971
Perhaps she had another use for them.

113
00:13:26,139 --> 00:13:28,849
We'II find out when we examine them.

114
00:13:29,058 --> 00:13:32,811
Besides, she reaIIy didn't leave them behind.

115
00:13:32,979 --> 00:13:35,856
She probabIy expected to return.

116
00:13:43,239 --> 00:13:44,865
They've got to be the answer.

117
00:13:45,033 --> 00:13:46,658
But we've tried everything.

118
00:13:46,826 --> 00:13:49,828
The metaI analyzer, the spectroscope.

119
00:13:49,996 --> 00:13:52,914
Both negative, no hidden compartments.

120
00:13:53,082 --> 00:13:54,708
I just don't understand it.

121
00:13:54,876 --> 00:13:56,960
Look at the back of this cat.
What do you see?

122
00:13:57,128 --> 00:14:01,131
WelI, just some funny markings. Why?

123
00:14:01,299 --> 00:14:03,216
Look at the other one.

124
00:14:03,634 --> 00:14:05,886
WelI, some different markings.

125
00:14:06,512 --> 00:14:10,057
These cats are supposed to be identicaI.

126
00:14:10,892 --> 00:14:12,059
Wait a moment.

127
00:14:12,226 --> 00:14:14,227
Something just occurred to me.

128
00:14:22,111 --> 00:14:24,863
There's an obscure legend...

129
00:14:25,031 --> 00:14:29,117
...that these cats once belonged
to the notorious pirate Captain Manx.

130
00:14:29,285 --> 00:14:33,622
Isn't he the pirate who wilIed his treasure to
the underpriviIeged children of Gotham City...

131
00:14:33,790 --> 00:14:38,126
...as a repayment for alI the havoc he wreaked
on the city's ships when it was first founded?

132
00:14:38,461 --> 00:14:44,841
Mm. The unique thing about the Iegend is that
they never recovered one goId doubIoon.

133
00:14:45,009 --> 00:14:48,553
HoIy feIony.
Do you think Catwoman stumbIed onto this?

134
00:14:49,055 --> 00:14:51,431
We'II know as soon as I find
the information here...

135
00:14:51,599 --> 00:14:55,560
...in the second voIume
<i></i>of<i> The History of Gotham City.</i>

136
00:14:56,229 --> 00:14:58,230
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]

137
00:15:05,822 --> 00:15:07,781
What happened?

138
00:15:08,282 --> 00:15:10,283
Where's Felix?

139
00:15:10,535 --> 00:15:13,745
-It's a Iong story.
-WelI, I don't have time for Iong stories.

140
00:15:13,913 --> 00:15:15,914
Where are the cats?

141
00:15:16,916 --> 00:15:20,127
-You did save the cats, didn't you?
-Batman got them.

142
00:15:20,461 --> 00:15:22,462
Batman got them?

143
00:15:22,630 --> 00:15:24,256
WelI, that does it.

144
00:15:24,424 --> 00:15:27,717
That's another fine mess
you got us into, Leo.

145
00:15:28,594 --> 00:15:29,928
AlI right.

146
00:15:30,096 --> 00:15:32,389
Let's set up the Batman reception.

147
00:15:32,557 --> 00:15:35,809
Now that Batman's got the cats,
he's bound to figure out their secret.

148
00:15:37,520 --> 00:15:39,646
Put aIternate PIan B into effect.

149
00:15:40,731 --> 00:15:42,107
Great Scott. I found it.

150
00:15:42,275 --> 00:15:45,277
And it's just as I remembered it.
Look here, Robin.

151
00:15:46,612 --> 00:15:49,364
This is the shape of Gotham City
in those days.

152
00:15:49,532 --> 00:15:54,119
Since then, a Iot more Iand has been added,
but does this pattern look familiar to you?

153
00:15:54,287 --> 00:15:56,246
HoIy geography. Of course.

154
00:15:56,414 --> 00:16:00,083
That's the same markings we found
when you put the two cats together.

155
00:16:00,251 --> 00:16:03,837
HoIy geography indeed, Robin.

156
00:16:04,213 --> 00:16:07,132
Without each other,
these two cats are useIess...

157
00:16:07,300 --> 00:16:09,759
...but when put together, they form a map...

158
00:16:09,927 --> 00:16:14,514
...that wiIl lead us right to the hidden
treasure chest of Pirate Captain Manx himseIf.

159
00:16:14,682 --> 00:16:18,643
-Gosh, Batman.
-Now the question is, where is Catwoman?

160
00:16:18,811 --> 00:16:22,898
Hmm. WeIl, if Catwoman stilI had these cats
in her possession...

161
00:16:23,065 --> 00:16:25,275
...we'd have no troubIe finding her.

162
00:16:25,485 --> 00:16:28,528
That radioactive spray we used
stilI shows up.

163
00:16:28,696 --> 00:16:30,697
Yes, you're absoIuteIy correct.

164
00:16:30,865 --> 00:16:32,824
Don't hoId that cat so close to your face.

165
00:16:33,367 --> 00:16:35,619
Some of the radioactive spray
may rub off on you.

166
00:16:35,786 --> 00:16:38,914
Right. I should've thought of that myseIf.

167
00:16:40,583 --> 00:16:43,460
-Batman?
-Yes, Robin?

168
00:16:43,669 --> 00:16:49,049
If someone were to hoId these cats
close enough and Iong enough...

169
00:16:49,217 --> 00:16:52,177
...do you suppose the radioactivity
might show up on the person?

170
00:16:52,345 --> 00:16:53,929
Yes, quite possibIy.

171
00:16:54,096 --> 00:16:57,891
WelI, Catwoman was hoIding the cats, and--

172
00:16:58,059 --> 00:17:01,561
And we switch on the Batometer.

173
00:17:06,484 --> 00:17:08,485
[BATOMETER WHIRRING]

174
00:17:10,196 --> 00:17:12,322
ROBIN:
Batman, the Batometer is going crazy.

175
00:17:12,949 --> 00:17:15,325
Of course.
The cats are disturbing the calibrations.

176
00:17:15,493 --> 00:17:18,328
Better put them
in the Iead-shieIded compartment.

177
00:17:29,632 --> 00:17:30,799
There. There, Batman.

178
00:17:30,967 --> 00:17:33,760
There's the bIip. She's out at McGilroy Point.

179
00:17:34,220 --> 00:17:36,638
There's only one road Ieading into that area.

180
00:17:36,806 --> 00:17:39,641
If the Catwoman knows we're coming,
she'II be ready for us.

181
00:17:39,809 --> 00:17:42,852
Better use the Bat Armor. Let's go.

182
00:17:46,232 --> 00:17:48,108
[TIRES SCREECHING]

183
00:18:02,582 --> 00:18:04,624
-Did you get the road mined?
-Yes, ma'am.

184
00:18:04,792 --> 00:18:07,502
Good. I've got the spot in the cave marked.

185
00:18:07,670 --> 00:18:09,754
Get the tooIs.

186
00:18:22,935 --> 00:18:26,313
CATWOMAN:
At Iast, the pIunder of a dozen gaIIeons.

187
00:18:26,480 --> 00:18:29,691
Diamonds, rubies, emeraIds.

188
00:18:29,859 --> 00:18:32,485
Never again to face deprivation.

189
00:18:32,653 --> 00:18:35,947
From now on, pussy wilIows gaIore.

190
00:18:36,115 --> 00:18:39,909
-I'm rich.
-We are rich, Catwoman.

191
00:18:40,661 --> 00:18:43,705
Ah. And they thought we were after
the Mark Andrews colIection.

192
00:18:43,873 --> 00:18:45,874
[LAUGHS]

193
00:18:46,208 --> 00:18:49,085
They thought they were deaIing
with an ordinary cat burgIar.

194
00:18:49,253 --> 00:18:53,965
Here, fiII this up. That chest is too cIumsy.

195
00:18:54,133 --> 00:18:56,885
And now there are just two of us
left to share it.

196
00:18:58,304 --> 00:19:00,096
Yeah.

197
00:19:00,556 --> 00:19:04,100
Just two of us.

198
00:19:20,242 --> 00:19:22,952
Just as I thought.
She's mined the road with expIosives.

199
00:19:23,120 --> 00:19:27,248
No wonder you had me put on that Bat Armor.
Gosh, you reaIIy think of everything, Batman.

200
00:19:31,337 --> 00:19:32,420
What's that?

201
00:19:33,005 --> 00:19:34,047
[SIGHS]

202
00:19:34,215 --> 00:19:38,385
Although the Bat Armor protected our car,
those landmines bIew our tires.

203
00:19:38,552 --> 00:19:41,429
Robin, turn on
the automatic tire-repair device.

204
00:19:52,483 --> 00:19:54,484
[TIRES SCREECHING]

205
00:20:09,375 --> 00:20:11,084
[BATOMETER BEEPING]

206
00:20:14,088 --> 00:20:17,841
-She's within 1 00 feet of here.
-Yeah, but where?

207
00:20:18,175 --> 00:20:20,510
BATMAN:
Look at those footprints.

208
00:20:24,807 --> 00:20:25,932
[SIGHS]

209
00:20:26,100 --> 00:20:27,559
Only one man has feet that big.

210
00:20:27,727 --> 00:20:30,395
There must be an opening
somewhere near here.

211
00:20:35,317 --> 00:20:39,779
Boy, I wonder what my end's gonna be.

212
00:20:41,157 --> 00:20:42,574
[GRUNTS]

213
00:20:42,825 --> 00:20:44,451
This.

214
00:20:50,166 --> 00:20:53,626
There's never enough for two.

215
00:20:57,590 --> 00:21:00,175
Stay right where you are, Catwoman.

216
00:21:34,376 --> 00:21:36,711
BATMAN:
Don't. Don't do it, Catwoman.

217
00:21:37,129 --> 00:21:40,048
You'II never make that jump
with what you're carrying.

218
00:21:40,299 --> 00:21:43,468
Just watch me, Batman.

219
00:21:48,933 --> 00:21:50,850
CATWOMAN:
Batman, help me.

220
00:21:51,393 --> 00:21:52,644
Hang on, Catwoman.

221
00:21:52,812 --> 00:21:55,104
When I throw the Batrope,
reach out and catch it.

222
00:21:56,148 --> 00:21:58,358
I'm afraid.

223
00:21:59,068 --> 00:22:03,279
Let go of the bag, Catwoman, then you'II
be abIe to catch the rope with your free hand.

224
00:22:03,447 --> 00:22:06,157
I can't let go of it.

225
00:22:07,076 --> 00:22:08,576
Drop it, Catwoman.

226
00:22:08,744 --> 00:22:11,079
Otherwise, you'lI faII into that bottomIess pit.

227
00:22:11,539 --> 00:22:13,832
Nothing is worth that.

228
00:22:13,999 --> 00:22:17,877
CATWOMAN:
I can't let go.

229
00:22:22,424 --> 00:22:24,968
I can't.

230
00:22:26,428 --> 00:22:29,055
[CATWOMAN SCREAMS]

231
00:22:29,223 --> 00:22:30,598
ROBIN:
Catwoman.

232
00:22:30,766 --> 00:22:32,934
Can you hear me?

233
00:22:33,102 --> 00:22:35,436
Catwoman!

234
00:22:42,945 --> 00:22:45,029
It's no use, Robin.

235
00:22:45,447 --> 00:22:47,907
She probabIy went straight to the bottom.

236
00:22:48,617 --> 00:22:50,410
[MEOWING]

237
00:22:53,080 --> 00:22:54,747
Why didn't she Iet go of the bag?

238
00:22:54,915 --> 00:22:58,459
-Didn't she know what wouId happen?
-Greed is an overpowering emotion, Robin.

239
00:22:58,627 --> 00:23:03,298
It sometimes dims aIl the senses,
even that of self-preservation.

240
00:23:03,465 --> 00:23:06,426
I suppose in the end,
that's what trips up alI criminaIs.

241
00:23:06,594 --> 00:23:09,012
Do you think she might stiII be aIive?

242
00:23:09,179 --> 00:23:11,973
A cat is supposed to have nine Iives.

243
00:23:12,141 --> 00:23:13,474
It's hard to say.

244
00:23:17,563 --> 00:23:22,108
Bishop to Queen 6, third IeveI.

245
00:23:22,359 --> 00:23:26,446
This wiIl take a minute, Bruce.
I didn't figure on that move at aIl.

246
00:23:28,032 --> 00:23:29,490
[CHUCKLES]

247
00:23:30,576 --> 00:23:33,286
Begging your pardon, Master Dick...

248
00:23:33,454 --> 00:23:37,123
...but a knight-takes-bishop's pIay
might seem in order here.

249
00:23:37,291 --> 00:23:39,250
Thank you, AIfred.

250
00:23:43,964 --> 00:23:47,842
WelI, in that case, queen takes knight...

251
00:23:48,010 --> 00:23:51,554
-...and checkmate.
WOMAN: I said shoo, you deviI.

252
00:23:51,722 --> 00:23:53,681
Oh, honestIy.

253
00:23:55,017 --> 00:23:57,226
-My goodness.
-What's wrong, Aunt Harriet?

254
00:23:57,394 --> 00:24:00,104
It's this infernaI cat.

255
00:24:00,272 --> 00:24:03,775
The IittIe heathen stoIe the lobster
I was preparing for your dinner.

256
00:24:03,943 --> 00:24:05,652
This cat is a thief.

257
00:24:05,819 --> 00:24:08,363
WelI, we're doing our best to rehabiIitate it.

258
00:24:08,530 --> 00:24:11,532
WelI, it steaIs everything
it can Iay its paws on.

259
00:24:11,700 --> 00:24:15,244
You have to understand, Aunt Harriet,
the cat comes from a broken home.

260
00:24:15,454 --> 00:24:16,496
Oh.

261
00:24:16,664 --> 00:24:18,247
[CAT MEOWS THEN BRUCE LAUGHS]

262
00:24:21,085 --> 00:24:23,086
-Master Dick.
-Heh.

263
00:25:05,587 --> 00:25:07,588
[EngIish - US - SDH]

