1
00:00:10,344 --> 00:00:14,430
NARRATOR:
<i>So far, we have seen a peaceful matinee...</i>

2
00:00:14,598 --> 00:00:17,391
<i>...at a fashionable theater.</i>

3
00:00:19,061 --> 00:00:21,020
Stick them up.

4
00:00:21,563 --> 00:00:26,317
<i></i>N<i></i>A<i></i>R<i></i>RAT<i></i>O<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> Holy bombshell,</i>
<i>the crook caught by the Penguin.</i>

5
00:00:26,527 --> 00:00:31,531
<i>The loot restored,</i>
<i>and a beautiful rich admirer found.</i>

6
00:00:31,740 --> 00:00:37,912
<i>Can it be? That waddling master</i>
<i>of foul play gone straight?</i>

7
00:00:38,622 --> 00:00:43,501
<i>Grill that crook.</i>
<i>Make him admit he's a Penguin stooge.</i>

8
00:00:44,503 --> 00:00:48,047
<i>Useless. The bird won't sing.</i>

9
00:00:49,132 --> 00:00:54,470
<i>In the steam room of The Millionaire's Club,</i>
<i>an attempted kidnap.</i>

10
00:00:55,430 --> 00:01:00,184
<i>Again, foiled by the Penguin</i>
<i>and his magic umbrella.</i>

11
00:01:01,144 --> 00:01:06,983
<i>The Penguin, set up in business,</i>
<i>rival to the Dynamic Duo.</i>

12
00:01:08,277 --> 00:01:11,862
<i>Alfred the butler, an undercover agent...</i>

13
00:01:12,656 --> 00:01:14,824
<i>...caught in the act.</i>

14
00:01:15,867 --> 00:01:18,202
<i>A desperate escape.</i>

15
00:01:19,538 --> 00:01:23,499
<i>The Penguin must be after</i>
<i>those priceless jewels.</i>

16
00:01:24,710 --> 00:01:28,337
<i>Bait for a clever Penguin trap.</i>

17
00:01:29,381 --> 00:01:31,882
<i>But Penguin's too clever.</i>

18
00:01:32,968 --> 00:01:36,554
<i>Holy backfire, what a catastrophe.</i>

19
00:01:37,222 --> 00:01:41,726
<i>Snap goes the Penguin trap,</i>
<i>cement-filled umbrellas.</i>

20
00:01:42,227 --> 00:01:45,771
<i>Strung up behind a shooting gallery.</i>

21
00:01:46,565 --> 00:01:50,067
<i>Death at the unwitting hands of the police?</i>

22
00:01:50,235 --> 00:01:54,655
<i>Wait. The wildest is yet to come.</i>

23
00:02:51,672 --> 00:02:54,382
PENGUIN:
Now, gentIemen, at my instructions.

24
00:02:54,549 --> 00:02:56,217
Ready...

25
00:02:57,302 --> 00:02:59,136

...aim...

26
00:03:00,931 --> 00:03:02,181
...fire!

27
00:03:02,391 --> 00:03:04,892
[LAUGHING]

28
00:03:06,937 --> 00:03:10,398
-What's so funny, Penguin?
-Oh, the irony of it.

29
00:03:10,565 --> 00:03:12,733
The exquisite humor.

30
00:03:12,901 --> 00:03:16,529
Where's our check? The thousand bucks
for the poIice benevoIent fund.

31
00:03:16,697 --> 00:03:20,950
Yes. With my gratitude,
you've earned it. Ha, ha. It's certified.

32
00:03:21,118 --> 00:03:25,162
ROBIN: Holy hot foot. The bulIetproof soIes
of our shoes sure saved our lives.

33
00:03:25,330 --> 00:03:29,750
BATMAN: The shock has IuckiIy unjammed
my Batknife too. I'II cut these ropes.

34
00:03:29,918 --> 00:03:32,378
Unh. We'lI get out of here fast.

35
00:03:36,049 --> 00:03:38,968
You know, it's quite a recoiI for a popgun.

36
00:03:39,136 --> 00:03:42,054
You're right, Chief O'Hara.
I noticed that myself.

37
00:03:43,765 --> 00:03:50,396
Now, Iet's toss the costumed corpses
over the pier, to the sharks with them.

38
00:03:53,275 --> 00:03:57,278
Great bIubbering whale oiI.
They've evaporated.

39
00:03:57,446 --> 00:04:01,741
Slugged me when I wasn't Iooking.
Batarangs.

40
00:04:04,035 --> 00:04:09,039
Curses. Curses.
Now we'lI have to fight another round.

41
00:04:11,293 --> 00:04:15,671
Gosh, Batman. I stiIl think we should
have crashed in and caged that bird.

42
00:04:15,839 --> 00:04:17,673
On what charge?

43
00:04:17,841 --> 00:04:19,717
Attempted murder.

44
00:04:20,302 --> 00:04:23,137
Commissioner Gordon
and Chief O'Hara fired the guns.

45
00:04:23,305 --> 00:04:24,930
Ouch, yes.

46
00:04:25,098 --> 00:04:28,726
We're the fugitives.
We're wanted by the Iaw for burglary.

47
00:04:28,894 --> 00:04:33,063
Besides, the Penguin had legaIIy rented
that amusement pier.

48
00:04:33,231 --> 00:04:35,983
-We're the trespassers.
-HoIy nightmare.

49
00:04:36,151 --> 00:04:38,527
This game, Penguin hoIds aII the aces.

50
00:04:38,695 --> 00:04:42,490
He may be hoIding aIl the aces...

51
00:04:42,657 --> 00:04:46,577
...but tomorrow morning,
we pIay the trump card.

52
00:04:49,372 --> 00:04:54,084
Those masked menaces must be apprehended.
I won't stand for it.

53
00:04:54,252 --> 00:04:57,254
A civiI tongue, Penguin,
or I'II have you removed from my office.

54
00:04:57,672 --> 00:04:59,340
A civiI tongue, is it?

55
00:04:59,508 --> 00:05:03,260
You watch out or I'II have you
removed from your office.

56
00:05:03,428 --> 00:05:07,306
-What?
-My influential friends won't like this.

57
00:05:07,474 --> 00:05:11,060
They'lI have you thrown back
into the Department of Sanitation...

58
00:05:11,228 --> 00:05:14,939
...where you beIong
for harboring wanted criminals.

59
00:05:15,106 --> 00:05:17,149
An outrageous accusation.

60
00:05:17,317 --> 00:05:20,611
Open your yap, Penguin.
Make that charge again.

61
00:05:20,779 --> 00:05:24,406
-I'm afraid Penguin's right.
-My dear Ms. Starr.

62
00:05:24,574 --> 00:05:28,118
Do you pretend you can't find
these criminals, commissioner?

63
00:05:29,412 --> 00:05:32,248
What's the matter, commissioner?
Famous hotline out of order?

64
00:05:32,415 --> 00:05:35,543
Penguin, don't touch that phone. Unh!

65
00:05:35,710 --> 00:05:37,753
[BEEPING]

66
00:05:38,547 --> 00:05:41,632
-Yes, commissioner?
-Quack, quack, I'm on the phone.

67
00:05:42,050 --> 00:05:45,594
-Penguin.
-No answer, eh? Hmm?

68
00:05:45,762 --> 00:05:50,099
The heat is on, Batman. You'd better come in
and give yourself up on that burgIary charge.

69
00:05:50,267 --> 00:05:54,562
-InstantIy. Do you understand?
-I'II see you, Penguin.

70
00:05:54,729 --> 00:05:58,941
I'II be at your Protective Agency office
in 25 minutes.

71
00:05:59,109 --> 00:06:01,986
Did you hear that?
He's on his way to attack me.

72
00:06:02,153 --> 00:06:04,864
I demand protection.

73
00:06:05,782 --> 00:06:10,786
The Penguin is within his rights, Chief O'Hara.
Stake out the area.

74
00:06:10,954 --> 00:06:13,581
-Arrest Batman.
-Yes, sir.

75
00:06:13,748 --> 00:06:15,749
[LAUGHING]

76
00:06:21,256 --> 00:06:23,757
Get on the mobiIe Batphone.
CaIl Commissioner Gordon.

77
00:06:23,925 --> 00:06:25,175
Roger.

78
00:06:25,343 --> 00:06:28,053
Give him the foIlowing instructions....

79
00:06:46,406 --> 00:06:50,117
To arms, my fine, frothy finks.
Batman's on his way.

80
00:07:02,714 --> 00:07:04,423
[ROARS]

81
00:07:04,591 --> 00:07:08,344
WelI, the costumed crooks,
the dressed-up desperadoes.

82
00:07:08,887 --> 00:07:11,388
Your super brain power has driven us mad,
Penguin.

83
00:07:11,556 --> 00:07:12,973
Something snapped.

84
00:07:13,141 --> 00:07:16,894
We don't care if we go up the river
for a hundred years. We're getting you first.

85
00:07:17,062 --> 00:07:21,315
Quick, my finks, seIf-defense.
The Dynamic Duo has flipped their wigs.

86
00:07:40,335 --> 00:07:42,336
[ALL GRUNTING]

87
00:07:46,841 --> 00:07:48,467
[SIRENS APPROACHING]

88
00:07:52,597 --> 00:07:54,556
Batman, Iisten, it's the police.

89
00:07:56,434 --> 00:07:57,434
Let's get out of here.

90
00:08:11,324 --> 00:08:12,366
[TIRES SCREECH]

91
00:08:15,412 --> 00:08:17,788
Surrender, Batman. We're taking you in.

92
00:08:33,430 --> 00:08:34,722
Get them, coppers.

93
00:08:48,778 --> 00:08:51,405
Agh! Ah. Agh!

94
00:09:10,467 --> 00:09:14,511
Oh, frabjous day. CaIlooh! CaIlay!

95
00:09:14,679 --> 00:09:19,058
-Let's bag the Batmobile.
-SensationaI idea. Come on.

96
00:09:31,863 --> 00:09:35,115
Let's see, now,
how do you run this dratted thing?

97
00:09:51,674 --> 00:09:53,675
I'II calI the morgue.

98
00:09:54,219 --> 00:09:58,263
Don't feeI too sad, boys. You had to do it.

99
00:09:58,431 --> 00:10:03,560
There's nothing so tragic
as a good crime fighter turned bad.

100
00:10:11,152 --> 00:10:16,198
In view of their past services, I've given orders
that they be buried with fuIl poIice honors.

101
00:10:16,366 --> 00:10:20,786
-Despite the fact they died as fugitive feIons?
-Yes, George, despite that fact.

102
00:10:20,954 --> 00:10:24,957
<i>Nothing can erase the memory</i>
<i>of the deeds they performed before they...</i>

103
00:10:25,125 --> 00:10:26,333
<i>...became unhinged.</i>

104
00:10:26,501 --> 00:10:29,920
<i>Now, tell me, commissioner,</i>
<i>what do you think brought about this--</i>

105
00:10:30,713 --> 00:10:33,966
Batman and Robin, dead?

106
00:10:35,176 --> 00:10:38,720
What in the world is going to become of us?

107
00:10:39,139 --> 00:10:42,891
Perhaps that's a better question
than you realize, madam.

108
00:10:43,309 --> 00:10:49,148
How I wish Bruce and Dick were here.
Maybe they could consoIe me.

109
00:10:50,567 --> 00:10:53,318
I doubt that very much, Mrs. Cooper.

110
00:10:53,820 --> 00:10:55,112
I doubt it very much.

111
00:10:55,280 --> 00:10:57,739
-Thank you, commissioner.
-Anytime, George.

112
00:10:57,907 --> 00:10:59,741
-HeIlo, chief.
-George.

113
00:10:59,909 --> 00:11:01,785
-For your signature, commissioner.
-Oh?

114
00:11:01,953 --> 00:11:04,371
Yeah. It's a requisition sIip
for the ammo we used...

115
00:11:04,539 --> 00:11:06,915
...getting Batman and Robin
in the big gunfight.

116
00:11:07,083 --> 00:11:10,586
Two hundred and ninety-seven rounds
incIuding tommy gun and pistol.

117
00:11:10,753 --> 00:11:13,046
-Strange, isn't it?
-Isn't what strange?

118
00:11:13,214 --> 00:11:16,717
Two hundred and ninety-seven rounds
of bIank ammunition.

119
00:11:16,885 --> 00:11:20,012
Do you know them bIanks
cost more than the real ones?

120
00:11:23,641 --> 00:11:24,766
[DINGS]

121
00:11:27,979 --> 00:11:31,523
<i>Ahh. Oh, what a thrill, Pengy, darling...</i>

122
00:11:31,691 --> 00:11:35,986
<i>...driving in your Birdmobile through</i>
<i>Gotham City on an anti-crime patrol.</i>

123
00:11:36,696 --> 00:11:39,573
BirdmobiIe? What nerve.

124
00:11:39,741 --> 00:11:41,450
By whatever name...

125
00:11:41,618 --> 00:11:46,371
...that tiny TV transmitter we buiIt in the back
of the fueI gauge is functioning perfectly.

126
00:11:46,539 --> 00:11:49,583
Let's just hope some foolish felon
tries to start--

127
00:11:49,751 --> 00:11:52,461
Look. Isn't that a hoIdup?

128
00:11:52,629 --> 00:11:54,838
Hand over that payroIl or get ventiIated.

129
00:11:55,548 --> 00:11:59,218
-Pengy, it is a hoIdup.
-Was a hoIdup, you mean.

130
00:12:02,013 --> 00:12:04,431
[YELLING]

131
00:12:04,724 --> 00:12:09,061
<i>-Ha-ha-ha!</i>
<i>-Oh, Pengy, you routed him.</i>

132
00:12:09,229 --> 00:12:11,271
<i>What a crime fighter.</i>

133
00:12:11,439 --> 00:12:14,107
<i>What a man of action.</i>

134
00:12:16,110 --> 00:12:19,154
ROBIN: Holy mush.
-Bet you a miIkshake...

135
00:12:19,322 --> 00:12:24,660
...that so-caIled hoIdup Penguin
just spoiIed was another charade.

136
00:12:24,827 --> 00:12:29,456
Gosh, Batman. I think it's time we came back
from the grave and nail that brassy bird.

137
00:12:29,624 --> 00:12:33,585
Patience, Robin.
Our seeming demise is our trump card.

138
00:12:33,753 --> 00:12:36,797
That and Ietting him steaI the Batmobile.

139
00:12:39,509 --> 00:12:43,428
I'd sure Iike to try some of the other
speciaI gimmicks we instaIIed.

140
00:12:43,596 --> 00:12:46,556
Don't worry, Robin. We'Il have time.

141
00:12:46,724 --> 00:12:51,228
Just as soon
as the Penguin reveaIs his pIot.

142
00:12:51,396 --> 00:12:54,690
And I know it has something to do
with Sophia Starr.

143
00:12:55,358 --> 00:12:57,693
<i>Sweet Sophia.</i>

144
00:12:57,860 --> 00:13:00,320
<i>Darling, Pengy birdie.</i>

145
00:13:00,863 --> 00:13:04,157
HoIy Romeo and JuIiet.

146
00:13:14,335 --> 00:13:20,465
Sophia, Iook into my eyes, wilI you?

147
00:13:20,633 --> 00:13:24,845
WilI you?

148
00:13:25,013 --> 00:13:30,559
Oh, yes, Penguin. Yes. Yes.

149
00:13:31,394 --> 00:13:34,688
-Oh, yes.
-Yes.

150
00:13:41,529 --> 00:13:44,406
-A solid goId dinner service.
-Check.

151
00:13:44,574 --> 00:13:49,411
-A diamond-studded eIectric can opener.
-Check.

152
00:13:49,579 --> 00:13:52,164
-A oiI welI.
-Check.

153
00:13:52,332 --> 00:13:54,333
A oiI welI?

154
00:13:54,500 --> 00:13:56,752
The deed's in the enveIope, stupid.

155
00:13:56,919 --> 00:14:00,255
-From the bride's uncIe in Texas.
-Wow!

156
00:14:00,423 --> 00:14:01,840
[DOOR CLOSES]

157
00:14:03,634 --> 00:14:05,969
The guests are coming. Everything set?

158
00:14:06,137 --> 00:14:09,389
Yeah. The bomb we pIaced
in the water pipes ought to go off, right:

159
00:14:09,557 --> 00:14:11,808
[MOUTHS]
<i>Five, four, three, two, one.</i>

160
00:14:11,976 --> 00:14:14,144
[EXPLOSION]

161
00:14:21,944 --> 00:14:24,112
[PENGUIN LAUGHING]

162
00:14:26,532 --> 00:14:28,075
Perfect, eh?

163
00:14:28,242 --> 00:14:31,870
-Good gracious. What happened?
-Oh, nothing to bother you, my little Iove.

164
00:14:32,038 --> 00:14:34,164
One of those water pipes
seems to have burst.

165
00:14:34,332 --> 00:14:38,210
Luckily, we brought some water buckets
and umbrelIas too.

166
00:14:38,378 --> 00:14:40,587
Enough for a smalI Iist
of distinguished guests.

167
00:14:40,755 --> 00:14:44,925
Oh, you are fantastic, Penguin.
Is there anything you're not prepared for?

168
00:14:45,093 --> 00:14:48,553
I hope not, my sweet. Mm, I hope not.

169
00:14:51,099 --> 00:14:54,267
-What? It seems to be raining in here.
-I've never....

170
00:14:54,435 --> 00:14:55,977
[GUESTS MUTTERING]

171
00:14:56,145 --> 00:14:59,314
-Man the buckets, my good man.
-Sure thing, Mr. Penguin.

172
00:14:59,482 --> 00:15:01,608
The wedding?
How come it's raining in here?

173
00:15:01,776 --> 00:15:04,653
WOMAN: It's raining in the house.
MAN: Right in the house.

174
00:15:04,821 --> 00:15:07,531
This rainfaII, I've never seen anything like it.

175
00:15:08,032 --> 00:15:10,992
Pass out the emergency umbreIIas, Dove.

176
00:15:11,160 --> 00:15:13,286
Right away, Mr. Penguin.

177
00:15:19,502 --> 00:15:23,088
Here you are, foIks. Take your umbreIIas.

178
00:15:24,382 --> 00:15:26,675
He's gonna give us umbreIlas.

179
00:15:26,843 --> 00:15:30,178
The Penguin and umbreIIas?
It spelIs trouble.

180
00:15:30,346 --> 00:15:32,681
WelI, sure, then I'm glad
we're on the guest Iist.

181
00:15:33,307 --> 00:15:35,809
-Here.
-Ah, yes.

182
00:15:36,394 --> 00:15:38,395
[PENGUIN LAUGHING]

183
00:15:39,147 --> 00:15:42,899
Oh, how charming and unusuaI.

184
00:15:43,067 --> 00:15:45,777
An indoor wedding in the rain.

185
00:15:45,945 --> 00:15:49,239
AlI the gifts are on dispIay
and we have a charming buffet.

186
00:15:49,407 --> 00:15:50,991
-Everyone.
-Open your umbreIIas.

187
00:15:51,159 --> 00:15:52,909
-It's raining heavily in here.
-Yes.

188
00:15:53,077 --> 00:15:54,953
-Watch the bucket.
-Ha-ha-ha.

189
00:15:58,499 --> 00:16:00,917
Ah, ha, ha. How do you do? How do you do?

190
00:16:04,839 --> 00:16:07,966
Ha-ha-ha. Thank you. Thank you. Ha, ha.

191
00:16:14,640 --> 00:16:15,724
[EXPLOSION]

192
00:16:15,892 --> 00:16:17,893
[GUESTS YELLING]

193
00:16:20,229 --> 00:16:22,230
[LAUGHING]

194
00:16:39,999 --> 00:16:43,251
Great Scott. The wedding presents.

195
00:16:43,419 --> 00:16:46,796
One of your criminals has done that.

196
00:16:46,964 --> 00:16:51,968
He's taken advantage
of this bizarre confusion to steal my dowry.

197
00:16:52,136 --> 00:16:55,430
If you want to see the crook
who's behind this, look in the mirror.

198
00:16:55,598 --> 00:16:58,433
Mirror, mirror.

199
00:16:59,060 --> 00:17:04,564
Mirror, mirror on the walI,
who's the fairest fink of alI?

200
00:17:06,234 --> 00:17:08,610
[GASPING]

201
00:17:14,659 --> 00:17:16,660
Ah, oh!

202
00:17:18,079 --> 00:17:21,581
-Pengy, they've fainted.
-WelI, don't get upset.

203
00:17:21,749 --> 00:17:24,626
-We'II get to the bottom of this.
-EagIe-Eye, Dove, come here.

204
00:17:24,794 --> 00:17:25,919
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Yeah. Yeah.

205
00:17:26,087 --> 00:17:28,129
-Let's go.
-Where to, boss?

206
00:17:28,297 --> 00:17:31,967
WelI, the criminaIs must be beIow.
Quick, to the eIevator.

207
00:17:32,134 --> 00:17:35,595
We'II apprehend them
or we'II die in the attempt.

208
00:17:35,763 --> 00:17:38,348
Yes. Yes. Oh!

209
00:17:39,517 --> 00:17:41,268
Waugh, waugh, waugh.

210
00:17:41,435 --> 00:17:45,772
Oh, what a hauI.
What a criminaI cornucopia.

211
00:17:45,940 --> 00:17:49,150
-Penguin, you're a genius.
-Of course I'm a genius.

212
00:17:49,318 --> 00:17:53,780
It's too bad that our two costumed cIowns
aren't here to see my triumph.

213
00:17:53,948 --> 00:17:57,742
Into our BirdmobiIe. We'Il fIy Iike the wind...

214
00:17:57,910 --> 00:18:01,454
...to our secret impregnabIe hideaway.

215
00:18:12,842 --> 00:18:15,218
[LAUGHING]

216
00:18:16,262 --> 00:18:20,599
<i>What a brilliant bird am I.</i>
<i>What a brilliant bird am I.</i>

217
00:18:20,766 --> 00:18:23,768
<i>A fortune in wedding gifts</i>
<i>and still a bachelor.</i>

218
00:18:23,936 --> 00:18:25,937
[LAUGHING]

219
00:18:26,814 --> 00:18:29,899
What a dastardIy twisted plot.

220
00:18:30,067 --> 00:18:31,943
That Penguin's some fouI bird.

221
00:18:32,111 --> 00:18:35,655
Not only robbing his own wedding
but Ieaving that trusting girI at the aItar.

222
00:18:35,823 --> 00:18:37,991
-Let's go get him, huh?
-Right you are, Robin.

223
00:18:38,159 --> 00:18:42,370
Let's see how his course is coming in
on the mobiIe BatcycIe Batscanner.

224
00:18:43,331 --> 00:18:45,624
He's just passing Gotham City limits.

225
00:18:45,791 --> 00:18:47,959
Right. Let's go.

226
00:18:54,133 --> 00:18:57,302
[SINGING]
<i>A bachelor's life is the life for me</i>

227
00:18:57,470 --> 00:19:00,180
<i>Titwillow, titwillow, titwillow</i>

228
00:19:00,348 --> 00:19:03,099
<i>A bachelor's life is the life for me</i>

229
00:19:03,267 --> 00:19:07,896
<i>Titwillow, titwillow and titwillow</i>

230
00:19:12,526 --> 00:19:14,194
We're gaining, Batman.

231
00:19:14,362 --> 00:19:18,698
Batscanner says, "Range, 7490."

232
00:19:23,371 --> 00:19:27,791
Lucky for us he doesn't know
how to actuate the super-speed afterburner.

233
00:19:28,125 --> 00:19:31,711
-Time to joIt him with our gimmicks, huh?
-Roger.

234
00:19:31,879 --> 00:19:36,174
We'II start by giving his two stooges
a short sweet voyage into space.

235
00:19:36,342 --> 00:19:38,760
Here goes the remote controI ejector button.

236
00:19:43,724 --> 00:19:47,852
EagIe-Eye. Dove. Thundering feathers.

237
00:19:48,020 --> 00:19:51,314
I must have accidentalIy hit
some dratted button.

238
00:19:51,941 --> 00:19:55,735
Now for some amusing fun with the doors.

239
00:19:57,029 --> 00:19:59,948
[MUTTERING]

240
00:20:03,869 --> 00:20:06,579
FouIed-up secondhand car.

241
00:20:06,747 --> 00:20:09,499
Great meIting icebergs.

242
00:20:10,751 --> 00:20:15,088
This bird is beginning to fIy here.

243
00:20:15,256 --> 00:20:17,507
Come here, you bIack raven.

244
00:20:17,675 --> 00:20:19,217
[MUTTERING]

245
00:20:19,802 --> 00:20:23,888
Look. Look at him, Robin.
That crooked bird's going crazy.

246
00:20:24,056 --> 00:20:27,308
Be careful, Batman.
We don't want him to smash up the Batmobile.

247
00:20:27,476 --> 00:20:31,229
Good point, Robin. I'Il take over
the steering now by remote control.

248
00:20:39,196 --> 00:20:40,905
[GRUNTING]

249
00:20:48,998 --> 00:20:51,040
[YELLING]

250
00:20:52,626 --> 00:20:54,127
I hate you.

251
00:20:54,295 --> 00:20:56,671
[MUTTERING]

252
00:21:00,009 --> 00:21:04,554
Great meIting icebergs.
This filthy beast seems out of my control.

253
00:21:08,350 --> 00:21:12,228
-What's the range now?
-"One, six, zero, two."

254
00:21:12,396 --> 00:21:16,065
HoId tight, Penguin.
Emergency turn coming up.

255
00:21:24,033 --> 00:21:28,578
Forget the scenic route, you bIack vuIture.
Just get me back on the main road.

256
00:21:34,001 --> 00:21:38,254
-Look, Batman. Penguin's ugIy thugs.
-Let's rack them up, huh?

257
00:21:40,925 --> 00:21:42,258
Do you see what I see, Dove?

258
00:21:44,470 --> 00:21:48,431
-What do you see, EagIe-Eye?
-I see ghosts on a BatcycIe.

259
00:21:52,895 --> 00:21:56,773
Ghosts, huh? I don't think
you crooks have the right spirit.

260
00:22:07,535 --> 00:22:09,994
The BatmobiIe. Let's get the controIs.

261
00:22:19,088 --> 00:22:21,381
Back from the grave, you tricksters, eh?

262
00:22:21,549 --> 00:22:25,134
Back to send you on a honeymoon cruise,
Penguin. Up the river to the pen.

263
00:22:25,302 --> 00:22:28,012
-Gone straight, huh?
ROBIN: We'lI straighten you out.

264
00:22:36,313 --> 00:22:38,565
[PENGUIN GRUNTING]

265
00:22:45,823 --> 00:22:49,701
-Case cIosed, Batman?
-Yes. Except for one detail.

266
00:22:49,869 --> 00:22:52,412
-What's that?
-The BatmobiIe.

267
00:22:52,580 --> 00:22:55,498
We'II have to have it fumigated.

268
00:23:05,551 --> 00:23:08,386
Here you are, Ms. Starr,
aII the stolen gifts recovered.

269
00:23:09,930 --> 00:23:12,807
-I wonder.
-What, Ms. Starr?

270
00:23:13,684 --> 00:23:15,852
The Iove and affection I'd provide...

271
00:23:16,020 --> 00:23:20,023
...it might be just the thing that would turn him
into an honest, Iaw-abiding citizen.

272
00:23:20,357 --> 00:23:21,524
Great Scott, Ms. Starr.

273
00:23:21,692 --> 00:23:24,652
You mean you'd stiIl consider
becoming that crooked bird's wife?

274
00:23:25,154 --> 00:23:26,362
Why not?

275
00:23:26,530 --> 00:23:31,034
I'd make him a nest where he'd feeI
warm and protected and Ioved.

276
00:23:31,201 --> 00:23:33,453
It's a chaIIenge
to quicken any woman's heart.

277
00:23:36,081 --> 00:23:37,540
Officer, bring in Penguin.

278
00:23:43,213 --> 00:23:47,592
Oh, my dear Pengy. My poor IittIe sick bird.

279
00:23:47,760 --> 00:23:49,928
It was mine.
I teII you, it was aII in my grip.

280
00:23:50,095 --> 00:23:55,642
This was my oil weIl,
and this was my soIid gold dinner service.

281
00:23:55,809 --> 00:23:59,020
And this was my diamond-studded
can opener.

282
00:23:59,188 --> 00:24:02,357
-Greedy bird. Have you no conscience?
-This woman Ioves you, Penguin.

283
00:24:02,524 --> 00:24:06,444
-She's stilI wilIing to marry you.
-Who, me? The Penguin?

284
00:24:06,612 --> 00:24:10,198
-Married and kept in a bathtub?
-I Iove you, Pengy.

285
00:24:10,366 --> 00:24:12,492
I'd try very hard to reform you.

286
00:24:12,660 --> 00:24:14,869
Great heavenly ice floes.

287
00:24:15,037 --> 00:24:17,622
Take me to prison.

288
00:25:08,090 --> 00:25:10,091
[EngIish - US - SDH]

