1
00:00:10,177 --> 00:00:13,262
NARRATOR:
<i>Another exciting event in Gotham City.</i>

2
00:00:13,472 --> 00:00:18,184
<i>An unveiling at Madame Soleil's</i>
<i>Wax Museum.</i>

3
00:00:19,937 --> 00:00:23,648
<i>A tribute to the city's</i>
<i>most illustrious crime fighter.</i>

4
00:00:23,815 --> 00:00:25,733
[APPLAUSE]

5
00:00:26,777 --> 00:00:30,112
Thank you, Monsieur Mayor.

6
00:00:30,322 --> 00:00:32,949
Monsieur the governor, the mayor...

7
00:00:33,158 --> 00:00:37,703
...and most honored dignitaries
of Gotham City.

8
00:00:37,913 --> 00:00:43,417
I know you are anxious to see
what I, the famous Madame Soleil...

9
00:00:43,627 --> 00:00:47,922
...have imported for you
aII the way from Paris, France.

10
00:00:48,131 --> 00:00:54,053
<i>M</i><i>e</i><i>s</i> <i>a</i><i>m</i><i>i</i><i>s</i><i>,</i> I unveiI this wax figure of Batman.

11
00:00:56,348 --> 00:00:59,267
[GONG RINGS & GUESTS MUTTERING]

12
00:00:59,434 --> 00:01:00,893
[SOLEIL SPEAKS IN FRENCH]

13
00:01:01,103 --> 00:01:03,271
What is this ghastIy travesty?

14
00:01:03,480 --> 00:01:06,482
Why, that's not Batman. That's the RiddIer.

15
00:01:06,692 --> 00:01:10,361
RIDDLER [ON RECORDING]:
<i>Surprise, surprise. Ha-ha-ha!</i>

16
00:01:10,779 --> 00:01:14,490
<i>What is black and white and red all over?</i>

17
00:01:16,243 --> 00:01:18,202
[ALL SCREAMING]

18
00:01:22,374 --> 00:01:24,625
[RIDDLER LAUGHING]

19
00:01:25,127 --> 00:01:30,006
<i>Illustrious friends, if that little riddle</i>
<i>is too hard for you...</i>

20
00:01:30,215 --> 00:01:32,258
<i>...why, here's another.</i>

21
00:01:32,467 --> 00:01:37,013
<i>What has branches and leaves and no bark?</i>

22
00:01:37,180 --> 00:01:39,181
[RIDDLER LAUGHING
& GUESTS SCREAMING]

23
00:01:43,228 --> 00:01:46,856
What did you say, Madame SoIeiI?

24
00:01:47,065 --> 00:01:49,984
The figure of Batman stoIen?

25
00:01:50,986 --> 00:01:53,321
It's the work of the RiddIer.

26
00:01:53,530 --> 00:01:56,949
Don't touch a thing. We'Il take care of it.

27
00:01:59,202 --> 00:02:01,746
WelI, you heard, chief.
The RiddIer's at it again.

28
00:02:01,955 --> 00:02:04,624
Only two weeks out ofjail
and he's up to his old tricks.

29
00:02:04,833 --> 00:02:07,543
I knew it was too good to Iast.

30
00:02:09,171 --> 00:02:11,839
There's only one thing to do.

31
00:02:12,049 --> 00:02:15,551
We may never know the identity of the man
behind the mask...

32
00:02:15,761 --> 00:02:18,929
...but he is the onIy one
who can cope with the RiddIer.

33
00:02:20,891 --> 00:02:25,478
<i></i>N<i></i>A<i></i>R<i></i>RAT<i></i>O<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> And in Wayne Manor, stately</i>
<i>residence of millionaire Bruce Wayne...</i>

34
00:02:25,687 --> 00:02:28,648
<i>...and his youthful ward Dick Grayson.</i>

35
00:02:28,857 --> 00:02:31,233
He's just come in, sir. I'II get him for you.

36
00:02:33,362 --> 00:02:35,488
I thought Lima was the capital of Ecuador.

37
00:02:35,697 --> 00:02:39,283
Now, as you can see, I was right.
It's the capital of Peru.

38
00:02:39,493 --> 00:02:43,204
Oh, I just love this game of capitaIs.
It's so educationaI.

39
00:02:43,413 --> 00:02:46,582
Not only that. If we don't know
aII about our friends to the south...

40
00:02:46,792 --> 00:02:48,626
...how can we carry on
our good-neighbor poIicy?

41
00:02:48,794 --> 00:02:50,753
-Ahem.
-Yes, AIfred.

42
00:02:50,921 --> 00:02:53,130
[WHISPERS]
It's the Batphone, sir.

43
00:02:54,675 --> 00:02:56,509
Oh, Aunt Harriet, I forgot to teIl you.

44
00:02:56,718 --> 00:02:59,553
Dick and I are having dinner
with an oId colIege chum of mine.

45
00:02:59,763 --> 00:03:02,973
He's promised to show Dick how to tie fIies.
He's an expert fisherman.

46
00:03:03,183 --> 00:03:05,810
Let's hurry, Dick, or we're gonna be Iate.

47
00:03:06,853 --> 00:03:11,691
Oh, those two. Hither, thither and yon.

48
00:03:15,112 --> 00:03:18,614
-Yes, commissioner.
-The RiddIer, he struck again.

49
00:03:18,824 --> 00:03:20,950
We're on our way.

50
00:03:21,159 --> 00:03:23,077
To the Bat-poles.

51
00:05:16,274 --> 00:05:18,609
[RIDDLER LAUGHING]

52
00:05:18,777 --> 00:05:22,446
<i>What is black and white and red all over?</i>

53
00:05:22,656 --> 00:05:24,323
He must be kidding. That's too easy.

54
00:05:24,533 --> 00:05:27,827
We figured that one out ourseIves,
Boy Wonder. It's a newspaper.

55
00:05:28,036 --> 00:05:32,206
You know only too welI how the RiddIer likes
to taunt us with these disguised cIues...

56
00:05:32,415 --> 00:05:35,417
...clues that aIways reveal
whatever pIot he's hatching.

57
00:05:35,627 --> 00:05:38,128
This pause here is where
the tricky paint gun went off.

58
00:05:38,338 --> 00:05:39,713
<i></i>R<i></i>I<i></i>D<i></i>D<i></i>L<i></i>E<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> Illustrious friends--</i>
-Shh.

59
00:05:39,923 --> 00:05:41,841
-Here comes the second riddle.
RIDDLER: Ha-ha-ha!

60
00:05:42,008 --> 00:05:46,720
<i>--if that little riddle is too hard for you,</i>
<i>why, here's another.</i>

61
00:05:46,930 --> 00:05:51,684
<i>What has branches and leaves</i>
<i>and no bark? Hmm?</i>

62
00:05:51,893 --> 00:05:53,018
That's it aII there is.

63
00:05:53,228 --> 00:05:55,604
There's aIways some definite connection...

64
00:05:55,814 --> 00:05:59,483
...between the answers to his riddIes
and his nefarious pIans.

65
00:05:59,693 --> 00:06:03,946
What has Ieaves and branches but no bark?

66
00:06:04,155 --> 00:06:06,949
Hey, a book has Ieaves.

67
00:06:07,158 --> 00:06:11,662
-But a book has no branches.
-Yes, but a library does.

68
00:06:11,872 --> 00:06:16,458
Then the answer to the first riddIe
couId've been "book" instead of "newspaper."

69
00:06:16,668 --> 00:06:18,460
You've done it again, chum.

70
00:06:18,670 --> 00:06:21,422
The answer is Iibrary, but what library?

71
00:06:21,631 --> 00:06:26,176
If I know the Riddler, it'II be the biggest Iibrary,
the Gotham City Library.

72
00:06:26,386 --> 00:06:28,470
But what wouId he want
at the pubIic Iibrary?

73
00:06:28,680 --> 00:06:32,516
We'II never find out standing here.
Let's go, Robin.

74
00:06:34,060 --> 00:06:40,232
<i></i>N<i></i>A<i></i>R<i></i>RAT<i></i>O<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> Meanwhile, in a secret hideaway</i>
<i>beneath this innocent-looking candle factory.</i>

75
00:06:51,453 --> 00:06:56,081
Oh, if only this were the real Batman. Oh!

76
00:06:56,291 --> 00:07:00,920
'Tis a consummation devoutIy to be wished.

77
00:07:01,129 --> 00:07:03,589
That his too, too soIid flesh...

78
00:07:03,798 --> 00:07:08,552
...wouId melt, thaw
and resoIve itseIf into a dew.

79
00:07:08,762 --> 00:07:12,848
Oh, Riddler, honey, that's beautiful.

80
00:07:13,058 --> 00:07:15,267
I wrote it myself.

81
00:07:19,439 --> 00:07:25,110
Little do they suspect the reaI reason
why I stole the wax figure of Batman.

82
00:07:25,320 --> 00:07:29,114
I knew. I knew those duII customs inspectors
would never think of Iooking...

83
00:07:29,324 --> 00:07:32,785
...for this revoIutionary new ring
of wax universal soIvent...

84
00:07:32,994 --> 00:07:36,497
...in the mannequin
of their precious champion.

85
00:07:36,706 --> 00:07:40,292
Big deaI. Wax is wax.
What's so special about this stuff?

86
00:07:40,502 --> 00:07:45,381
Oh, you don't know, my pretty IittIe Moth,
what a universaI solvent is.

87
00:07:45,590 --> 00:07:47,341
It can eat through anything.

88
00:07:47,550 --> 00:07:52,721
This remarkabIe wax can be found onIy
in the hives of the Cognac district of France.

89
00:07:52,931 --> 00:07:56,392
No wonder the United States government
has banned its importation.

90
00:07:56,601 --> 00:07:59,144
It might faIl into the wrong hands.

91
00:07:59,854 --> 00:08:03,107
Why, with this iIIegalIy imported substance...

92
00:08:03,316 --> 00:08:07,736
...there is no vault I cannot enter.

93
00:08:07,904 --> 00:08:09,989
Aah!

94
00:08:10,156 --> 00:08:12,449
Hear me, worId!

95
00:08:12,659 --> 00:08:16,578
Nothing can stop me now! Ha-ha-ha!

96
00:08:39,811 --> 00:08:43,230
-Ain't he ever gonna move?
-Yeah, we gotta get in the vault.

97
00:08:43,440 --> 00:08:47,693
Remember, it is better
to Iight one IittIe candle...

98
00:08:47,902 --> 00:08:50,612
...than to curse the darkness.

99
00:09:19,809 --> 00:09:22,102
QuickIy, Moth,
Batman's had time to soIve my cIue.

100
00:09:22,312 --> 00:09:25,647
-Go downstairs and keep a sharp Iookout.
-Okay.

101
00:09:25,815 --> 00:09:27,399
[LAUGHING]

102
00:09:29,069 --> 00:09:30,778
Won't be Iong now.

103
00:09:30,987 --> 00:09:34,782
That rare oId book,
<i>The Lost Treasures of the Incas</i>.<i></i>.<i></i>.<i></i>

104
00:09:34,991 --> 00:09:38,994
...wiIl soon be in my hands.

105
00:09:39,204 --> 00:09:42,039
Ain't somebody bound to hear us
when we break into the vault?

106
00:09:42,248 --> 00:09:43,415
Don't talk stupid.

107
00:09:43,625 --> 00:09:45,667
Why do you think
I went to so much troubIe...

108
00:09:45,877 --> 00:09:49,296
...to smuggle in this universal wax soIvent?

109
00:09:49,464 --> 00:09:51,465
[LAUGHING]

110
00:09:57,847 --> 00:09:59,848
Genius.

111
00:10:00,058 --> 00:10:02,851
So far so good.

112
00:10:08,733 --> 00:10:10,234
[LAUGHING]

113
00:10:47,147 --> 00:10:51,191
Ahh. Go on. Ha-ha-ha.

114
00:10:59,742 --> 00:11:04,121
Now, remember, no writing in the margins.

115
00:11:11,629 --> 00:11:16,175
Heavens to Betsy. It can't be, but it is.

116
00:11:16,384 --> 00:11:17,801
The dynamic duo.

117
00:11:18,595 --> 00:11:20,220
Can I be of any heIp to you at aIl?

118
00:11:20,430 --> 00:11:22,931
Have you seen any
Unusual-Iooking peopIe around here?

119
00:11:23,141 --> 00:11:26,185
Unusual? In what way unusual?

120
00:11:26,394 --> 00:11:31,356
Their garb. For instance, a man wearing a bright
green suit with big black question marks on it.

121
00:11:31,566 --> 00:11:33,400
Let me think a moment.

122
00:11:33,610 --> 00:11:35,861
No, I can't say that I have, offhand.

123
00:11:36,070 --> 00:11:38,614
But then I see so many peopIe
in the course of the day.

124
00:11:38,823 --> 00:11:41,825
We have reason to beIieve that a serious crime
wiIl be committed here.

125
00:11:42,035 --> 00:11:44,036
ROBIN: We sure have.
PRENTICE: Oh, dear.

126
00:11:44,245 --> 00:11:46,872
Where is the vauIt in which you store
your most precious books?

127
00:11:47,081 --> 00:11:50,250
It's upstairs. FoIIow me.

128
00:11:58,593 --> 00:12:01,511
Boss, this is Moth. They're on their way up.

129
00:12:01,721 --> 00:12:03,096
I'II be ready for them.

130
00:12:03,306 --> 00:12:05,807
Hey, here it is, boss.

131
00:12:07,352 --> 00:12:08,727
Oh?

132
00:12:10,939 --> 00:12:12,397
Oh, heh.

133
00:12:14,317 --> 00:12:17,778
At Iast I found it.

134
00:12:18,863 --> 00:12:23,033
This wiIl lead me right
to the lost treasure of the Incas.

135
00:12:23,243 --> 00:12:28,288
Every greedy bone in my body cries out...

136
00:12:28,498 --> 00:12:32,376
...huzzah, huzzah!

137
00:12:32,543 --> 00:12:34,878
[LAUGHING]

138
00:12:37,382 --> 00:12:40,133
My stars. Look at that hoIe
and the lock's gone.

139
00:12:40,343 --> 00:12:44,888
CarefuI, Robin, this Iooks like a robbery.
Wait there, Ms. Prentice.

140
00:12:53,690 --> 00:12:55,732
As you can see, Batman...

141
00:12:55,942 --> 00:12:59,987
...by the deadly weapons we hoId,
you'd be fooIs to move.

142
00:13:00,196 --> 00:13:03,031
-What are you doing here?
-Checking out a book.

143
00:13:03,241 --> 00:13:06,118
-"Checking out a book"?
-Exactly, Boy Wonder.

144
00:13:06,327 --> 00:13:08,787
<i>Lost Treasure of the Incas.</i>

145
00:13:08,997 --> 00:13:10,956
What would he want with a book Iike that?

146
00:13:11,165 --> 00:13:14,376
Who can expIain the devious mind
of an arch criminaI?

147
00:13:14,585 --> 00:13:19,214
-You'II never get away with this, Riddler.
-WouId you Iike to make a IittIe wager?

148
00:13:19,424 --> 00:13:20,674
I never gambIe.

149
00:13:46,284 --> 00:13:47,784
HoIy muciIage.

150
00:13:49,620 --> 00:13:51,330
[LAUGHING]

151
00:13:51,497 --> 00:13:54,374
I can't move my feet. I'm stuck to the floor.

152
00:13:54,584 --> 00:13:55,917
Yes, it's my own concoction.

153
00:13:56,127 --> 00:14:01,256
I caIl it "Dr. RiddIer's Instant Forever Stick
Invisible Wax EmuIsion."

154
00:14:01,466 --> 00:14:02,632
[RINGING]

155
00:14:03,843 --> 00:14:04,968
Boss, you hit the alarm.

156
00:14:05,178 --> 00:14:09,097
An unfortunate error on my part,
but Iucky for you, Batman.

157
00:14:09,307 --> 00:14:10,807
Let's get out of here, boss.

158
00:14:11,017 --> 00:14:15,020
Since you'lI be sticking around for a IittIe whiIe,
I'II Ieave you a riddIe to work on.

159
00:14:15,229 --> 00:14:19,441
The more you take away, the larger it grows.

160
00:14:23,863 --> 00:14:26,281
What is it? Ha-ha-ha!

161
00:14:26,449 --> 00:14:28,241
[COUGHING]

162
00:14:33,706 --> 00:14:35,248
ROBIN:
They've gone.

163
00:14:35,458 --> 00:14:39,086
We must get out of this. I'Il try the Iaser gun.

164
00:14:41,047 --> 00:14:43,382
What devilish sticky stuff.

165
00:14:43,591 --> 00:14:46,676
If only the RiddIer's inventive mind
couId be channeIed for good...

166
00:14:46,886 --> 00:14:49,096
...what a better worId this wouId be.

167
00:14:49,972 --> 00:14:52,516
It's working, Robin.
The wax is beginning to melt.

168
00:14:52,725 --> 00:14:54,601
PRENTICE:
Are you alI right in there?

169
00:14:54,811 --> 00:14:57,646
Yes. It's safe to come in now, Ms. Prentice.

170
00:14:57,855 --> 00:15:01,441
-Oh, saints above, how did that hoIe get there?
ROBIN: That's it.

171
00:15:01,651 --> 00:15:04,152
-What is it?
-The answer to that riddIe. Don't you see?

172
00:15:04,362 --> 00:15:06,947
The more you take away from a hole,
the Iarger it grows.

173
00:15:07,156 --> 00:15:12,619
-You're right. What can that mean? UnIess....
-Yes?

174
00:15:20,878 --> 00:15:24,297
There's a strange, waxy substance here.

175
00:15:24,507 --> 00:15:25,549
Could this be his cIue?

176
00:15:25,758 --> 00:15:28,301
But how is this done? I heard no expIosion.

177
00:15:28,511 --> 00:15:31,638
We must take this back
to the Batcave at once and anaIyze it.

178
00:15:31,848 --> 00:15:36,893
UnIess I miss my guess,
I'm hoIding the answer in my hand.

179
00:15:51,075 --> 00:15:53,243
[TIRES SCREECHING]

180
00:15:57,123 --> 00:15:58,248
We've no time to waste.

181
00:15:58,458 --> 00:16:02,127
Let's get this sampIe of wax
to the hyper-spectrographic analyzer.

182
00:16:02,336 --> 00:16:05,922
This shouId teIl us
what makes up this waxy substance.

183
00:16:07,884 --> 00:16:09,342
Aha!

184
00:16:09,510 --> 00:16:13,430
It's just as I thought. Nitrogen
is one of the component elements.

185
00:16:13,639 --> 00:16:15,932
That orange color,
doesn't that mean uranium?

186
00:16:16,142 --> 00:16:19,769
-Right on the nose. You're catching on fast.
-No kidding? Gee.

187
00:16:19,979 --> 00:16:23,773
-But what about that bIue Iine?
-That one's easy. It's sodium.

188
00:16:23,983 --> 00:16:27,194
Of course, this is a universaI wax soIvent.

189
00:16:27,403 --> 00:16:29,779
So that's how they got into that vault.

190
00:16:29,989 --> 00:16:33,283
If the RiddIer left this as a cIue,
I don't get it. Do you?

191
00:16:33,493 --> 00:16:35,619
WelI, there's something here
that escapes me.

192
00:16:35,828 --> 00:16:41,249
Nitrogen, Uranium, Sodium,
what couId it possibly mean?

193
00:16:41,459 --> 00:16:45,295
If you take the first three letters
of those eIements it speIIs N-U-S...

194
00:16:45,505 --> 00:16:49,007
-...but that doesn't mean anything.
-Reverse the order and what do you have?

195
00:16:49,217 --> 00:16:52,552
-S-U-N.
-Of course, that's got to be it.

196
00:16:52,762 --> 00:16:54,221
But what's it supposed to mean?

197
00:16:54,430 --> 00:16:57,265
I'm surprised at you.
You're supposed to be studying French.

198
00:16:57,475 --> 00:16:59,726
-What's the French word for Sun?
<i>-Soleil</i>.<i></i>

199
00:16:59,936 --> 00:17:00,977
Correct.

200
00:17:01,187 --> 00:17:05,982
The RiddIer has Ieft us a cIear indication
of where he intends to strike next.

201
00:17:06,192 --> 00:17:09,861
Back at Madame SoIeiI's Wax Museum.

202
00:17:10,071 --> 00:17:12,239
What are we waiting for?

203
00:17:24,252 --> 00:17:28,213
Madame SoIeiI? Madame SoIeiI?

204
00:17:28,422 --> 00:17:30,715
It's Batman and Robin.

205
00:17:30,925 --> 00:17:33,301
Are you here?

206
00:17:33,511 --> 00:17:36,179
Such vandalism.

207
00:17:36,806 --> 00:17:40,350
What a disastrous unveiIing
this must have been.

208
00:17:41,269 --> 00:17:44,396
Boy, wax museums are sure spooky.

209
00:17:44,605 --> 00:17:47,440
You think the RiddIer is here somewhere?

210
00:17:51,862 --> 00:17:56,116
NARRATOR: <i>F</i><i>o</i><i>r</i> <i>h</i><i>e</i><i>a</i><i>v</i><i>e</i><i>n</i><i>'s</i> <i>s</i><i>a</i><i>k</i><i>e</i><i>,</i>
<i>caped crusaders, watch out.</i>

211
00:17:57,118 --> 00:17:58,785
[BOTH GROANING]

212
00:18:02,790 --> 00:18:04,165
Good shot, boss.

213
00:18:04,375 --> 00:18:07,127
Music hath the charm
to sooth the savage beast.

214
00:18:07,336 --> 00:18:08,670
THUG:
You sure soothed them boss.

215
00:18:08,879 --> 00:18:11,089
You soothed them right to sIeep
with that thing.

216
00:18:11,299 --> 00:18:14,301
MOTH: They Iook dead to me.
RIDDLER: Just drugged, my pet.

217
00:18:14,510 --> 00:18:15,635
Why kilI them fast...

218
00:18:15,845 --> 00:18:20,807
...when watching them die slowly
is so much more entertaining.

219
00:18:20,975 --> 00:18:22,809
[LAUGHING]

220
00:18:24,437 --> 00:18:26,104
Ah.

221
00:18:33,821 --> 00:18:39,659
Beauty, after aIl is in the eye of the behoIder.

222
00:18:48,294 --> 00:18:50,128
[LAUGHING]

223
00:18:53,132 --> 00:18:54,674
Ah.

224
00:18:55,176 --> 00:18:57,135
WelI, what do you know?

225
00:18:57,345 --> 00:19:00,305
A dividend I hadn't considered.

226
00:19:01,557 --> 00:19:04,184
What a haul this day has yielded.

227
00:19:04,393 --> 00:19:07,812
First, the rare oId book
on the Iost treasure of the Incas...

228
00:19:08,022 --> 00:19:10,649
...then the invincible Batman and Robin...

229
00:19:10,858 --> 00:19:12,651
...and now...

230
00:19:12,818 --> 00:19:14,569
[LAUGHING]

231
00:19:14,737 --> 00:19:19,491
...the famous Batmobile for my very own.

232
00:19:21,952 --> 00:19:24,245
Remember, this thing's Ioaded
with burgIar aIarms.

233
00:19:24,455 --> 00:19:26,247
Don't you think I know that?

234
00:19:26,749 --> 00:19:30,960
Ha-ha-ha. A IittIe snip here.

235
00:19:31,170 --> 00:19:33,338
A IittIe snip there.

236
00:19:33,506 --> 00:19:35,298
[LAUGHING]

237
00:19:35,925 --> 00:19:37,967
Now, it's safe to drive.

238
00:19:38,177 --> 00:19:39,719
You're gonna drive the BatmobiIe?

239
00:19:39,929 --> 00:19:42,097
"Finders keepers, Iosers weepers,"
I aIways say.

240
00:19:42,306 --> 00:19:43,348
What do we do now?

241
00:19:43,557 --> 00:19:47,894
You take Batman and Robin out
to the candIe factory and I'Il meet you there.

242
00:19:49,230 --> 00:19:51,189
[LAUGHING]

243
00:20:18,384 --> 00:20:20,468
We'd better get
our everyday cIothes back on.

244
00:20:20,678 --> 00:20:22,178
We Iook too suspicious this way.

245
00:20:22,388 --> 00:20:25,181
Just as soon as we get
these two prize packages inside.

246
00:20:25,391 --> 00:20:28,560
Hey, look. Look, he's coming to.

247
00:20:29,186 --> 00:20:33,231
Aw, he Iooks so handsome
beneath that mask.

248
00:20:34,316 --> 00:20:37,652
A diamondback rattIesnake
is a handsome creature too...

249
00:20:37,862 --> 00:20:39,612
...but dangerous and deadIy.

250
00:20:39,822 --> 00:20:42,907
Remember, Moth,
Batman is our sworn enemy.

251
00:20:43,117 --> 00:20:47,120
We can iII afford such emotions as pity.

252
00:20:47,329 --> 00:20:49,456
Where am I?

253
00:20:50,624 --> 00:20:55,420
Ah, you could say you're
in the proverbial pickIe, Batman.

254
00:20:55,629 --> 00:20:57,380
Take them in.

255
00:21:17,401 --> 00:21:19,694
Robin, do you hear me?

256
00:21:19,904 --> 00:21:22,864
Batman, what happened to us?

257
00:21:23,073 --> 00:21:26,576
It seems you have been overpowered again.

258
00:21:26,786 --> 00:21:28,912
But how?

259
00:21:29,121 --> 00:21:32,707
The Iast thing I remember,
we were in the wax museum.

260
00:21:32,917 --> 00:21:35,627
We just passed
the RevoIutionary War scene.

261
00:21:35,836 --> 00:21:37,545
You're getting warm.

262
00:21:38,172 --> 00:21:40,006
So that's how it was done.

263
00:21:40,216 --> 00:21:44,093
-How what was done?
-Oh, it's so cIear now.

264
00:21:44,303 --> 00:21:47,555
We were victimized by a repeating bIowgun.

265
00:21:47,765 --> 00:21:51,184
HoIy iodine. So that's why
the back of my neck smarts.

266
00:21:56,190 --> 00:21:57,899
The wax is hot enough now, boss.

267
00:21:58,067 --> 00:22:02,821
If they want a lifeIike figure of their precious
Batman for the wax museum...

268
00:22:03,030 --> 00:22:04,447
...we'II give it to them.

269
00:22:04,657 --> 00:22:07,325
We'II even throw in a dividend.

270
00:22:07,535 --> 00:22:09,327
Robin.

271
00:22:10,037 --> 00:22:11,329
You fiend!

272
00:22:11,539 --> 00:22:17,585
Sticks and stones may break my bones,
but names wiIl never hurt me.

273
00:22:18,796 --> 00:22:23,925
Matches, start the motor, slowly.

274
00:22:24,134 --> 00:22:26,594
Very slowly.

275
00:22:27,471 --> 00:22:30,223
Oh, I want to savor...

276
00:22:30,432 --> 00:22:35,603
...each sweet, delicious moment of this.

277
00:22:35,813 --> 00:22:37,146
Gotcha, boss.

278
00:22:42,319 --> 00:22:47,448
RiddIer, teIl me why you removed
my wax figure from Madame SoIeiI's?

279
00:22:47,658 --> 00:22:52,579
How else couId I smuggIe in
that revoIutionary new ring of wax soIvent?

280
00:22:52,788 --> 00:22:56,374
But why go to alI that trouble?
WouIdn't TNT have been much simpIer?

281
00:22:56,584 --> 00:23:00,461
Have you ever been in a quiet Iibrary
when TNT went off?

282
00:23:00,671 --> 00:23:02,714
It makes a frightening noise.

283
00:23:02,923 --> 00:23:06,676
Why did you steaI that rare oId book
on the Iost treasure of the Incas?

284
00:23:06,886 --> 00:23:11,097
What possibIe meaning couId
a scholarIy book Iike that have for you?

285
00:23:11,974 --> 00:23:15,935
For two peopIe
about to become human candIes...

286
00:23:16,145 --> 00:23:17,979
...you have a Iot of questions.

287
00:23:18,856 --> 00:23:22,775
I'm aIways interested
in the way the criminaI mind works.

288
00:23:22,985 --> 00:23:25,445
WelI, then, I'II telI you.

289
00:23:26,947 --> 00:23:32,285
Within that rare oId book,
I found an ancient Incan riddle...

290
00:23:32,494 --> 00:23:38,249
...which wiIl lead me right
to the fabIed Iost treasure of the Incas.

291
00:23:38,876 --> 00:23:40,919
You must be mad.

292
00:23:41,128 --> 00:23:43,796
The Iost treasures of the Incas
is onIy a legend.

293
00:23:44,006 --> 00:23:47,175
Ah, but that's
where you're mistaken, Batman.

294
00:23:47,384 --> 00:23:50,887
The treasure is real, very reaI...

295
00:23:51,096 --> 00:23:56,601
...but unfortunateIy,
you won't be around to see it.

296
00:24:01,231 --> 00:24:03,232
[LAUGHING]

297
00:24:04,151 --> 00:24:06,027
[NARRATOR READING ON-SCREEN TEXT]

298
00:25:11,969 --> 00:25:13,970
[EngIish - US - SDH]

