1
00:00:09,885 --> 00:00:11,636
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]

2
00:00:13,305 --> 00:00:16,015
NARRATOR:
<i>In last night's Bat-adventure we saw:</i>

3
00:00:16,183 --> 00:00:18,935
<i>Gotham City dignitaries gather.</i>

4
00:00:20,854 --> 00:00:22,897
<i>An unveiling.</i>

5
00:00:23,106 --> 00:00:26,025
<i>A ghastly travesty.</i>

6
00:00:26,485 --> 00:00:29,820
<i>The Riddler at large again.</i>

7
00:00:33,367 --> 00:00:35,576
<i>Pandemonium.</i>

8
00:00:35,786 --> 00:00:38,829
<i>A riddle for a clue.</i>

9
00:00:40,791 --> 00:00:43,251
<i>A call for help.</i>

10
00:00:45,254 --> 00:00:47,713
<i>To the rescue.</i>

11
00:00:48,340 --> 00:00:52,343
<i>Riddle solved, onto the library.</i>

12
00:00:52,553 --> 00:00:55,471
<i>A ring of wax.</i>

13
00:00:59,268 --> 00:01:02,853
<i>A rare old book stolen.</i>

14
00:01:05,899 --> 00:01:08,901
<i>A strange discovery.</i>

15
00:01:11,780 --> 00:01:14,031
<i>It's a clue.</i>

16
00:01:14,700 --> 00:01:18,244
<i>Batman grabbed the gauntlet.</i>

17
00:01:23,125 --> 00:01:25,334
<i>Was it a trap?</i>

18
00:01:26,628 --> 00:01:29,171
<i>Watch out, Batman.</i>

19
00:01:30,382 --> 00:01:32,049
<i>Too late.</i>

20
00:01:34,177 --> 00:01:36,304
<i>Helpless.</i>

21
00:01:40,183 --> 00:01:42,893
<i>A fatal dip.</i>

22
00:01:43,645 --> 00:01:46,689
<i>And in just one bubbling minute....</i>

23
00:01:46,857 --> 00:01:51,193
<i>But wait, the most terrifying is yet to come.</i>

24
00:03:03,975 --> 00:03:05,643
[RIDDLER CACKLING]

25
00:03:08,772 --> 00:03:12,316
HoIy paraffin, Batman,
this is going to be a close one.

26
00:03:12,526 --> 00:03:13,776
Too cIose.

27
00:03:15,195 --> 00:03:18,197
Oh, this is my dream come true.

28
00:03:18,407 --> 00:03:22,785
With you two out of the way,
there is nothing that stands between me...

29
00:03:22,953 --> 00:03:25,663
...and the Iost treasure of the Incas.

30
00:03:25,872 --> 00:03:29,583
And it's worth miIIions. MilIions.

31
00:03:29,793 --> 00:03:31,877
Do you hear me, Batman?

32
00:03:33,505 --> 00:03:36,674
Remember, RiddIer,
you can't buy friends with money.

33
00:03:36,883 --> 00:03:38,384
With money, who needs friends?

34
00:03:38,885 --> 00:03:40,803
[MOTH COUGHING
AND RIDDLER CHUCKLING]

35
00:03:40,971 --> 00:03:45,057
RiddIer, honey, these fumes are terribIe.
Can't we go beIow?

36
00:03:45,308 --> 00:03:48,477
I want to watch this to its gIorious finaIe.

37
00:03:48,687 --> 00:03:51,897
Can't we watch it just as weII
from your candIe scope?

38
00:03:52,107 --> 00:03:53,899
WelI, aII right.

39
00:03:54,109 --> 00:03:55,526
The fumes are getting to me too.

40
00:03:55,694 --> 00:03:56,736
[COUGHS]

41
00:03:58,029 --> 00:04:00,156
Keep smiIing, you two.

42
00:04:00,365 --> 00:04:03,826
Remember,
I'd Iike nice expressions on your faces...

43
00:04:03,994 --> 00:04:07,037
...when we deIiver you to the wax museum.

44
00:04:08,623 --> 00:04:11,459
Bye. Let's go.

45
00:04:12,961 --> 00:04:15,045
They're going, Batman. They're going.

46
00:04:15,255 --> 00:04:18,549
Good.
Now to find a way out of this predicament.

47
00:04:22,095 --> 00:04:24,555
-Wait a minute. What's that?
-Where?

48
00:04:24,723 --> 00:04:29,101
That barrel over there
with a chemical formuIa written on it.

49
00:04:29,394 --> 00:04:31,937
I can't see alI the formula...

50
00:04:32,147 --> 00:04:37,151
...but unless I miss my guess,
that's the solution for treating candIewicks.

51
00:04:37,319 --> 00:04:42,698
-It's highly explosive when it's exposed to heat.
-I can't see how that's gonna do us much good.

52
00:04:46,995 --> 00:04:49,038
Matches, down scope.

53
00:05:00,008 --> 00:05:04,386
Ah. The candIe scope is working beautifuIly.

54
00:05:04,554 --> 00:05:06,514
Oh, Iet me see, let me see.

55
00:05:06,723 --> 00:05:10,017
AlI right, but just for a second.

56
00:05:11,978 --> 00:05:15,356
Aw. It does seem a shame.

57
00:05:16,024 --> 00:05:17,817
Moth...

58
00:05:18,068 --> 00:05:21,695
...if you expect to get anywhere
in this arch-criminaI game...

59
00:05:21,863 --> 00:05:23,823
...you can't be soft.

60
00:05:23,990 --> 00:05:28,494
You must Iearn to controI your emotions.

61
00:05:36,211 --> 00:05:39,171
Uh-oh. We're getting
awfuIly close to that wax.

62
00:05:39,339 --> 00:05:40,506
[ROBIN COUGHS]

63
00:05:40,674 --> 00:05:42,466
Those fumes are getting pretty strong.

64
00:05:42,634 --> 00:05:46,804
Don't give up, Robin.
Remember, where there's a wiII, there's a way.

65
00:05:46,972 --> 00:05:50,683
If only we could ignite
that barrel of chemicaI soIution down there...

66
00:05:50,892 --> 00:05:54,019
...I feel certain it wouId bIow us free.

67
00:05:57,107 --> 00:06:00,484
I don't know whether it'lI work,
but I think it's worth a try.

68
00:06:00,652 --> 00:06:02,111
I can't see what you're doing.

69
00:06:02,279 --> 00:06:05,281
There's a shaft of sunIight
coming through the roof.

70
00:06:05,448 --> 00:06:07,783
If I can just twist around a IittIe...

71
00:06:07,951 --> 00:06:11,245
...and reflect it
in my highIy poIished beIt buckIe...

72
00:06:11,413 --> 00:06:14,665
...with a IittIe bit of luck,
maybe I can direct it at the barreI.

73
00:06:20,338 --> 00:06:23,007
What are they doing up there?
Something nearly bIinded me.

74
00:06:23,216 --> 00:06:25,634
Let me take a Iook, boss.

75
00:06:29,389 --> 00:06:31,432
I don't see nothing wrong, boss.

76
00:06:35,353 --> 00:06:38,689
Something is awfuIIy bright up there.

77
00:06:43,153 --> 00:06:45,487
I think I've got the right angIe now.

78
00:06:45,697 --> 00:06:48,198
HoId perfectIy stiIl.

79
00:06:53,371 --> 00:06:55,080
There. I'm right on the mark.

80
00:06:55,248 --> 00:06:56,999
Prepare yourseIf for the shock.

81
00:06:58,043 --> 00:07:01,128
What are they doing up there?

82
00:07:04,424 --> 00:07:06,467
Was that an explosion?

83
00:07:14,768 --> 00:07:18,812
Could the expIosion have
bIown them to bits?

84
00:07:26,738 --> 00:07:28,948
[CACKLING]

85
00:07:34,996 --> 00:07:39,667
Be stilI, my throbbing heart.

86
00:07:39,834 --> 00:07:43,712
My fondest dream's come true.

87
00:07:44,965 --> 00:07:48,425
Batman and Robin, dead.

88
00:07:49,427 --> 00:07:53,806
Dead.

89
00:07:54,015 --> 00:07:57,184
My cup runneth over.

90
00:07:57,477 --> 00:07:59,228
Up scope.

91
00:07:59,604 --> 00:08:01,939
Can we forget about them now
and go find that Iost treasure?

92
00:08:02,107 --> 00:08:03,148
RIDDLER:
Ah. Oh.

93
00:08:03,316 --> 00:08:09,530
Let me savor this moment, so divine,
seeing Batman and Robin dead.

94
00:08:09,739 --> 00:08:13,325
It's more important than any treasure.

95
00:08:13,535 --> 00:08:17,705
More important than aII those Incan bobbIes,
bangIes and beads?

96
00:08:17,914 --> 00:08:19,665
Not to me, it ain't.

97
00:08:19,874 --> 00:08:21,458
Impatience, thy name is woman.

98
00:08:21,668 --> 00:08:24,503
First, I must caIl Commissioner Gordon...

99
00:08:24,671 --> 00:08:28,173
...and telI him the good news
about his beIoved Caped Crusaders...

100
00:08:28,341 --> 00:08:31,218
...and then confound him with a IittIe riddIe.

101
00:08:31,386 --> 00:08:34,304
Oh, why take time for that?

102
00:08:36,266 --> 00:08:39,268
Crime is no fun without riddIes.

103
00:08:39,686 --> 00:08:44,148
I'II have you know, that's the main reason
I took up this crime game.

104
00:08:45,984 --> 00:08:47,234
AlI of you, in the truck.

105
00:08:47,444 --> 00:08:49,153
Ain't you taking the BatmobiIe, boss?

106
00:08:49,320 --> 00:08:51,280
It'd be too conspicuous where we're going.

107
00:08:51,448 --> 00:08:54,074
I'II be with you in a minute. Go on.

108
00:08:59,831 --> 00:09:01,582
[PHONE RINGS]

109
00:09:02,417 --> 00:09:03,959
Commissioner Gordon here.

110
00:09:04,377 --> 00:09:06,587
This is the RiddIer.

111
00:09:06,796 --> 00:09:10,215
I have some news for you
about the Iate Dynamic Duo.

112
00:09:10,550 --> 00:09:13,052
-Late?
-I'm sorry to be the one...

113
00:09:13,219 --> 00:09:16,388
...to break this unfortunate news to you,
commissioner.

114
00:09:16,598 --> 00:09:19,266
Batman and Robin, dead?

115
00:09:19,517 --> 00:09:21,060
I can't believe it.

116
00:09:21,561 --> 00:09:26,565
If you had anything to do with this, Riddler,
I'II track you down to the ends of the Earth.

117
00:09:26,775 --> 00:09:28,567
And that's a soIemn promise.

118
00:09:29,152 --> 00:09:31,612
WhiIe you're at it, commissioner,
ponder this riddle.

119
00:09:31,780 --> 00:09:36,075
What has four Iegs, runs day and night,
but never gets anywhere?

120
00:09:36,284 --> 00:09:41,622
-Now, see here, you cheap scoundreI--
-By the time you figure it out, it'II be too Iate.

121
00:09:41,790 --> 00:09:43,290
[CACKLING]

122
00:09:59,057 --> 00:10:01,141
Are you alI right, Robin?

123
00:10:01,684 --> 00:10:04,269
Gosh, we were aImost goners.

124
00:10:04,479 --> 00:10:05,813
Those guys mean business.

125
00:10:06,022 --> 00:10:08,857
It's a miracIe we were bIown free
by that expIosion.

126
00:10:09,067 --> 00:10:11,693
Let's just be thankfuI
that my calcuIations were correct.

127
00:10:11,861 --> 00:10:13,654
I don't know how you do it.

128
00:10:13,863 --> 00:10:16,240
There's no time for that now.

129
00:10:18,618 --> 00:10:21,245
Good, they didn't take the BatmobiIe.

130
00:10:26,668 --> 00:10:29,795
I think we'd better calI
Commissioner Gordon.

131
00:10:31,131 --> 00:10:33,090
-Commissioner Gordon?
-Who is this?

132
00:10:33,299 --> 00:10:34,883
-Why, this is Batman.
GORDON: <i>B</i><i>a</i><i>t</i><i>m</i><i>a</i><i>n</i><i>.</i>

133
00:10:35,051 --> 00:10:37,803
Your Caped Crusader. Is something wrong?

134
00:10:38,221 --> 00:10:39,763
The RiddIer said you were dead.

135
00:10:40,140 --> 00:10:41,807
WishfuI thinking on his part.

136
00:10:42,016 --> 00:10:43,725
We're alive and raring to go.

137
00:10:44,060 --> 00:10:46,520
WelI, I must say, this is good news.

138
00:10:46,688 --> 00:10:50,190
But now back to business.
What do you make of this cIue the RiddIer left:

139
00:10:50,650 --> 00:10:54,403
<i>"What has four legs, runs day and night,</i>
<i>but never gets anywhere?"</i>

140
00:10:54,612 --> 00:10:56,321
That's the riddIe, word for word.

141
00:10:56,531 --> 00:10:58,907
We'II get on it right away, commissioner.

142
00:10:59,159 --> 00:11:02,119
What has four Iegs, runs day and night,
but never gets anywhere?

143
00:11:02,328 --> 00:11:04,246
This isn't going to be easy, Robin.

144
00:11:04,455 --> 00:11:05,747
A river runs day and night.

145
00:11:05,957 --> 00:11:08,750
Yes, but it gets somewhere.
It runs to the ocean.

146
00:11:08,960 --> 00:11:12,880
But a fountain.... It could be a fountain.

147
00:11:13,089 --> 00:11:15,090
I think you're on the right track, Robin.

148
00:11:15,258 --> 00:11:17,301
But that four-Iegs business, that stumps me.

149
00:11:17,468 --> 00:11:20,095
An animaI has four Iegs.

150
00:11:20,305 --> 00:11:23,682
Wait a minute.
Maybe the fountain has an animal in it.

151
00:11:24,726 --> 00:11:28,770
The famous Iion fountains
in front of the Gotham City Museum.

152
00:11:29,105 --> 00:11:30,814
Gosh, Batman, I think you're wrong.

153
00:11:30,982 --> 00:11:34,067
The Iion fountains aren't running.
The water shortage, remember?

154
00:11:34,235 --> 00:11:38,071
That's what that cheating deviI wants us
to think, Robin. I'm sure I'm right.

155
00:11:38,281 --> 00:11:41,783
And that's where the RiddIer must be going,
and we must go without deIay.

156
00:11:41,993 --> 00:11:43,076
HoId tight.

157
00:11:54,214 --> 00:11:58,091
How couId a sarcophagus
be so hard to find?

158
00:11:58,301 --> 00:12:01,595
Gee, boss, I don't even know
what an esophagus Iooks Iike.

159
00:12:02,222 --> 00:12:04,056
You numskuIl, you're no heIp to me here.

160
00:12:04,224 --> 00:12:06,475
You and Matches go upstairs,
keep a look out.

161
00:12:06,643 --> 00:12:08,685
Sure, boss.

162
00:12:11,105 --> 00:12:16,485
Oh, Riddler, honey,
this pIace gives me a nice case of the jitters.

163
00:12:16,861 --> 00:12:20,197
What are aIl those nasty-looking things?

164
00:12:22,408 --> 00:12:27,871
A few IittIe fun things from the MiddIe Ages,
my IittIe Moth.

165
00:12:29,165 --> 00:12:30,749
That tub there...

166
00:12:31,251 --> 00:12:35,504
...that sweet IittIe thing
was caIled the maiden's bath.

167
00:12:37,632 --> 00:12:39,174
And this...

168
00:12:39,467 --> 00:12:41,677
...the exquisite iron mask.

169
00:12:41,844 --> 00:12:43,136
[CHUCKLES]

170
00:12:45,139 --> 00:12:48,809
And this, the beIoved stocks. Oh.

171
00:12:48,977 --> 00:12:52,104
And that wheel over there...

172
00:12:52,313 --> 00:12:56,108
...the beautifulIy ingenious wheeI of death.

173
00:12:58,736 --> 00:13:03,448
And Iast but not least, the rack.

174
00:13:08,871 --> 00:13:10,289
Oh.

175
00:13:11,207 --> 00:13:15,335
Those were the good oId days.

176
00:13:15,670 --> 00:13:17,421
I'm sorry I asked.

177
00:13:31,394 --> 00:13:34,896
Is it possibIe this has some connection
with the Iost treasure of the Incas?

178
00:13:35,064 --> 00:13:38,233
Aunt Harriet was reading to me about it.
It's in aII the newspapers.

179
00:13:38,401 --> 00:13:41,361
They can't exhibit it
untiI they build an airtight display case.

180
00:13:41,529 --> 00:13:44,239
If it's exposed to air, it wiII crumbIe to dust.

181
00:13:44,449 --> 00:13:45,866
It's beginning to make sense.

182
00:13:46,034 --> 00:13:49,619
The Iost treasure of the Incas
must be hidden inside that sarcophagus.

183
00:13:49,787 --> 00:13:51,580
I'd stake my Iife on it.

184
00:13:51,789 --> 00:13:55,584
-So that's what he Iearned from that oId book.
-I hope we're not too Iate, Batman.

185
00:13:55,752 --> 00:13:58,503
So do I. Even now,
RiddIer and his gang may be destroying...

186
00:13:58,671 --> 00:14:01,173
...one of the worId's
greatest archeoIogical treasures.

187
00:14:01,341 --> 00:14:03,675
And for a mere miIIion-doIlars
worth ofjeweIs.

188
00:14:07,096 --> 00:14:09,556
It's Iocked. They must be closed today.

189
00:14:09,766 --> 00:14:11,850
How do we get in?

190
00:14:13,978 --> 00:14:16,438
Batman. Look, that window.

191
00:14:16,939 --> 00:14:17,981
BATMAN:
It's open.

192
00:14:18,566 --> 00:14:22,569
-But it's too smaIl. I'd never make it.
-But I could. I couId, Batman.

193
00:14:24,572 --> 00:14:26,114
-It's dangerous.
-Let me do it.

194
00:14:26,282 --> 00:14:30,827
I promise I'Il come right down
and open the door for you. PIease, Batman.

195
00:14:31,037 --> 00:14:34,414
Be careful. Don't try to capture the RiddIer
and the gang by yourseIf.

196
00:14:34,874 --> 00:14:37,501
Come immediateIy downstairs
and open the door for me.

197
00:14:37,710 --> 00:14:39,669
-I'II handle it. Do you understand?
-Roger.

198
00:14:39,837 --> 00:14:43,882
And take your Bat-communicator
and keep in touch.

199
00:14:44,592 --> 00:14:46,468
Stand cIear.

200
00:14:49,806 --> 00:14:51,515
Robin.

201
00:14:59,774 --> 00:15:03,193
BATMAN [OVER COM]: <i>K</i><i>e</i><i>e</i><i>p</i> <i>i</i><i>n</i> <i>to</i><i>u</i><i>c</i><i>h</i> <i>w</i><i>i</i><i>t</i><i>h</i> <i>m</i><i>e</i>
<i>on your throat communicator.</i>

202
00:15:04,695 --> 00:15:07,155
GolIy, Batman, I hope we're not too Iate.

203
00:15:07,365 --> 00:15:11,493
I join you in that hope. I shudder to think
how it might affect our foreign reIations...

204
00:15:11,661 --> 00:15:14,996
-...if anything happened to this exhibit.
-How do you mean, Batman?

205
00:15:15,206 --> 00:15:18,208
Can you imagine the reaction
of our good neighbors to the south...

206
00:15:18,376 --> 00:15:21,086
...shouId we aIIow their national treasure
to be destroyed?

207
00:15:21,254 --> 00:15:22,462
Gosh, I see what you mean.

208
00:15:27,844 --> 00:15:30,345
Take care, Robin.

209
00:15:39,522 --> 00:15:41,022
You. I thought you were dead.

210
00:15:41,232 --> 00:15:43,692
I'II show you how dead I am.

211
00:15:46,320 --> 00:15:49,489
Hey, Matches, give me a hand,
I can't handIe him.

212
00:15:51,242 --> 00:15:52,742
No.

213
00:15:53,369 --> 00:15:57,122
TALLOW: Watch your back!
MATCHES: Now you're making me mad, kid.

214
00:16:15,600 --> 00:16:17,309
Robin.

215
00:16:17,560 --> 00:16:20,854
Robin? Do you hear me?

216
00:16:21,689 --> 00:16:24,316
Is something wrong, Robin?

217
00:16:24,525 --> 00:16:25,650
Robin.

218
00:16:25,860 --> 00:16:28,653
Come in, Robin.

219
00:16:32,492 --> 00:16:34,201
Hey, boss, Iook what we found.

220
00:16:34,410 --> 00:16:35,535
RIDDLER:
Huh?

221
00:16:37,955 --> 00:16:39,331
You--

222
00:16:40,082 --> 00:16:42,834
-But you're dead.
-No thanks to you that I'm not.

223
00:16:45,796 --> 00:16:49,090
And Batman? He lives too?

224
00:16:49,300 --> 00:16:50,467
No, you fiend.

225
00:16:50,635 --> 00:16:54,429
You've destroyed the finest man that ever lived,
and I'lI get you for it.

226
00:16:54,597 --> 00:16:58,767
You pernicious pipsqueak.
You're in no position to threaten anyone.

227
00:16:58,935 --> 00:17:00,852
Put him on the rack.

228
00:17:05,691 --> 00:17:09,986
If he doesn't fit, stretch him to size.

229
00:17:10,196 --> 00:17:12,405
But don't hurt him.

230
00:17:15,243 --> 00:17:20,413
Robin, if you can hear me,
I'm coming in after you.

231
00:17:41,102 --> 00:17:42,477
Commissioner.

232
00:17:42,645 --> 00:17:44,271
I'm at the Gotham City Museum.

233
00:17:44,480 --> 00:17:47,148
Robin's inside and I'm going in after him.

234
00:17:47,358 --> 00:17:49,192
You'd better send some men over.

235
00:17:49,402 --> 00:17:50,902
Right.

236
00:17:54,782 --> 00:17:56,283
[TIRES SCREECH]

237
00:18:00,371 --> 00:18:01,913
[GRUNTING]

238
00:18:04,875 --> 00:18:07,502
You may think you have the upper hand now,
but wait.

239
00:18:09,547 --> 00:18:11,715
Hey, boss, I think I found it.

240
00:18:11,924 --> 00:18:14,884
What? The sarcophagus?

241
00:18:15,052 --> 00:18:16,970
-Yeah, it's over here.
RIDDLER: The sarcophagus?

242
00:18:17,138 --> 00:18:19,431
[RIDDLER CACKLING]

243
00:18:21,767 --> 00:18:23,977
Just think, think...

244
00:18:24,186 --> 00:18:26,438
...in a few short moments...

245
00:18:26,647 --> 00:18:30,609
...the Iost treasure of the Incans
shaIl be mine. Mine.

246
00:18:30,818 --> 00:18:33,653
Ours, honey. Ours.

247
00:18:34,030 --> 00:18:36,448
Who said you can't take it with you?

248
00:18:36,616 --> 00:18:39,534
Lucky for me, the Incan emperors did.

249
00:18:39,744 --> 00:18:41,911
At Ieast, their jeweIs.

250
00:18:42,079 --> 00:18:43,913
[CACKLING]

251
00:18:49,629 --> 00:18:53,131
Oh, the sarcophagus.

252
00:18:56,761 --> 00:18:59,554
Oh, it's too bad Batman's dead.

253
00:18:59,764 --> 00:19:02,390
If only he couId see me now.

254
00:19:05,519 --> 00:19:07,062
[MOTH & MATCHES SHRIEK]

255
00:19:08,272 --> 00:19:09,814
RIDDLER:
Egad, it's Batman.

256
00:19:10,691 --> 00:19:14,694
It can't be. I saw you dead with my own eyes.

257
00:19:15,196 --> 00:19:18,031
You Iied to me, Boy Wonder.

258
00:19:18,240 --> 00:19:21,493
A IittIe white lie is excusabIe...

259
00:19:21,702 --> 00:19:26,748
...when deaIing with the Iikes of you,
you black-hearted scoundrel.

260
00:19:27,375 --> 00:19:30,627
WelI, don't just stand there. Get him, men.

261
00:20:15,005 --> 00:20:17,882
This is gonna hurt me more than it does you.

262
00:20:24,807 --> 00:20:26,141
Get him, Matches. Get him.

263
00:20:33,941 --> 00:20:37,402
I don't know about you, Riddler, honey,
but I'm getting out of here. Oh!

264
00:20:38,904 --> 00:20:40,697
AlI right, Riddler...

265
00:20:40,948 --> 00:20:42,699
...now it's your turn.

266
00:20:42,867 --> 00:20:44,868
No, no. No.

267
00:20:48,038 --> 00:20:50,790
-Sorry, ma'am.
ROBIN: Batman.

268
00:20:51,167 --> 00:20:52,459
Batman.

269
00:20:52,626 --> 00:20:55,378
HoIy smoke,
the candIe is stiIl burning under the wax.

270
00:20:55,546 --> 00:20:58,923
-Put it out before it eats through.
-Good thinking, Robin.

271
00:20:59,842 --> 00:21:00,925
Just in time.

272
00:21:03,262 --> 00:21:04,471
[CHUCKLES]

273
00:21:04,680 --> 00:21:06,931
Watch out, Batman.

274
00:21:19,111 --> 00:21:20,862
[RIDDLER GRUNTING]

275
00:21:21,864 --> 00:21:22,989
Oh! Ah!

276
00:21:23,157 --> 00:21:26,201
Didn't your mother ever telI you
not to pIay with knives, Riddler?

277
00:21:26,410 --> 00:21:29,496
Can't we taIk this over, Batman? Ah!

278
00:21:30,623 --> 00:21:34,083
Let me give you one Iast word of advice.
Give up your eviI ways.

279
00:21:34,293 --> 00:21:37,670
When you've paid your debt to society,
and pay it you wiII...

280
00:21:37,880 --> 00:21:40,298
...start Iife anew as a respected citizen.

281
00:21:40,466 --> 00:21:42,842
I'II give you anything, anything.
Anything you want.

282
00:21:43,010 --> 00:21:45,845
Just name it, Batman. Name it. Aah!

283
00:21:46,055 --> 00:21:47,096
Oh! Ow!

284
00:21:47,264 --> 00:21:51,976
Batman, that smarts. Ooh.

285
00:21:57,358 --> 00:21:59,150
Robin, are you aIl right?

286
00:21:59,360 --> 00:22:01,361
I'm just a little sore, Batman. That's aIl.

287
00:22:01,529 --> 00:22:05,031
One of Aunt Harriet's good nourishing meaIs
wiIl set everything right again.

288
00:22:05,199 --> 00:22:08,034
I sure worked up an appetite, I'II teIl you that.

289
00:22:08,202 --> 00:22:11,162
You're aIl under arrest.
Now, no monkey business.

290
00:22:11,372 --> 00:22:13,498
We got you covered.

291
00:22:14,750 --> 00:22:16,793
There's no need for guns, Chief O'Hara.

292
00:22:17,002 --> 00:22:18,920
There's no more fight Ieft in them.

293
00:22:19,088 --> 00:22:21,923
When Commissioner Gordon toId me
to go to the museum...

294
00:22:22,091 --> 00:22:26,219
...naturaIIy I thought he meant the wax museum,
otherwise we'd have been here sooner.

295
00:22:26,387 --> 00:22:29,722
Anyone can make that mistake, Chief O'Hara.
There's no harm done, chief.

296
00:22:29,890 --> 00:22:34,769
The RiddIer and his accompIices are ready
to be delivered into your capabIe hands.

297
00:22:37,022 --> 00:22:41,067
Oh, Batman, honey. Moth's Iearned her lesson,
reaIly she has. Crime doesn't pay.

298
00:22:41,277 --> 00:22:44,404
UnfortunateIy,
you Iearned your lesson too Iate, Moth.

299
00:22:44,613 --> 00:22:47,740
A moth that pIays around candIes
is bound to be burned.

300
00:22:48,158 --> 00:22:49,576
[MOTH SHRIEKS]

301
00:22:54,164 --> 00:22:57,083
Oh. Batman.

302
00:22:57,668 --> 00:23:00,336
You may have won the battIe...

303
00:23:00,588 --> 00:23:03,631
...but the war isn't over yet.

304
00:23:13,475 --> 00:23:18,271
This is certainIy a very educationaI way
to spend an afternoon.

305
00:23:18,480 --> 00:23:20,773
Yes, and it's going to come in
so handy at schooI.

306
00:23:20,941 --> 00:23:24,110
-I think I'lI do my end-of-term report on it.
-Very good.

307
00:23:24,278 --> 00:23:27,488
Most Americans don't realize
what we owe to the ancient Incans.

308
00:23:27,698 --> 00:23:30,658
Very few appreciate
that they gave us the white potato...

309
00:23:30,826 --> 00:23:33,077
...and many varieties of Indian corn.

310
00:23:33,245 --> 00:23:36,080
Now whenever I eat mashed potatoes,
I, for one, wilI think of the Incas.

311
00:23:36,248 --> 00:23:38,666
BRUCE: Heh.
-Mercy aIive.

312
00:23:38,876 --> 00:23:41,753
Have you ever seen such beautiful jeweIs?

313
00:23:41,962 --> 00:23:44,547
They must have cost a king's ransom.

314
00:23:44,757 --> 00:23:49,344
It says here that they found the jeweIs
in a secret paneI in the sarcophagus.

315
00:23:49,553 --> 00:23:53,556
They were hidden to guard against grave
robbers who were very prevaIent in oIden days.

316
00:23:53,724 --> 00:23:58,186
WelI, thank goodness we don't have
anything Iike that to worry about today.

317
00:23:58,395 --> 00:23:59,938
I think we shouId be Ieaving now.

318
00:24:00,147 --> 00:24:05,318
Oh, Bruce, I want just one more peek
at this oId Incan emperor.

319
00:24:05,819 --> 00:24:07,278
WilI you Iook at that?

320
00:24:07,446 --> 00:24:12,575
Isn't he preserved niceIy
for aII those thousands of years?

321
00:24:12,785 --> 00:24:15,328
It's remarkabIe.

322
00:24:16,080 --> 00:24:19,123
The oId boy nearIy didn't make it.

323
00:24:24,421 --> 00:24:27,632
NARRATOR: <i>N</i><i>e</i><i>x</i><i>t</i> <i>w</i><i>e</i><i>e</i><i>k,</i>
<i>Batman jousts with the Joker again.</i>

324
00:25:12,261 --> 00:25:14,262
[EngIish - US - SDH]

