1
00:00:10,886 --> 00:00:14,889
NARRATOR:
<i>We've already seen innocent shoppers.</i>

2
00:00:16,892 --> 00:00:18,476
<i>A stick-up.</i>

3
00:00:20,437 --> 00:00:22,355
<i>It's the Joker.</i>

4
00:00:24,816 --> 00:00:26,275
<i>A clue?</i>

5
00:00:27,778 --> 00:00:29,862
<i>Yes, to oriental royalty.</i>

6
00:00:32,658 --> 00:00:35,493
<i>Theft of the gold golf clubs.</i>

7
00:00:37,579 --> 00:00:39,288
<i>After them!</i>

8
00:00:40,582 --> 00:00:43,918
<i>But no, theft of the Maharaja.</i>

9
00:00:45,212 --> 00:00:48,297
<i>Did the van vanish...</i>

10
00:00:48,966 --> 00:00:50,466
<i>...or shrink?</i>

11
00:00:52,344 --> 00:00:54,804
<i>Traced to their lair...</i>

12
00:00:56,014 --> 00:00:58,224
<i>...but not surprised.</i>

13
00:00:59,935 --> 00:01:02,186
<i>Wrapped for mailing.</i>

14
00:01:03,647 --> 00:01:05,898
<i>Into the mailbox.</i>

15
00:01:06,900 --> 00:01:09,944
<i>Addressed to oblivion.</i>

16
00:01:11,321 --> 00:01:14,156
<i>Is there no way out?</i>

17
00:01:15,701 --> 00:01:17,702
<i>No way but up?</i>

18
00:01:18,537 --> 00:01:21,497
<i>Let's all hold our breath for one minute.</i>

19
00:01:21,665 --> 00:01:24,750
<i>The gasser is yet to come.</i>

20
00:02:32,903 --> 00:02:35,738
NARRATOR:
<i>Oh, no. Don't give up.</i>

21
00:02:50,671 --> 00:02:52,213
They're so brave.

22
00:02:52,381 --> 00:02:56,509
Yes. One must concede
that they have courage. Heh, heh.

23
00:02:57,094 --> 00:02:58,761
I can't stand it.

24
00:02:58,929 --> 00:03:01,347
Oh, don't think about it, my dear.

25
00:03:01,515 --> 00:03:05,267
Think about how simple things wilI be
with Batman out of our way forever.

26
00:03:05,435 --> 00:03:09,480
Think of aIl the things you can buy
with what we can steaI. Heh, heh.

27
00:03:09,648 --> 00:03:11,232
But that's a good idea.

28
00:03:11,400 --> 00:03:13,651
I better check the gauge.

29
00:03:14,736 --> 00:03:20,282
Aah! The gas is 20 feet high in the chimney.
They must be gone. Heh, heh.

30
00:03:20,450 --> 00:03:23,536
Goodbye, dynamic duo. Heh, heh.

31
00:03:23,704 --> 00:03:25,913
<i></i>M<i></i>A<i></i>N<i></i>:<i> Okay, Joker, let's get out of here.</i>
JOKER: <i>N</i><i>o</i><i>,</i> <i>w</i><i>a</i><i>i</i><i>t</i><i>.</i>

32
00:03:26,081 --> 00:03:29,458
<i>First we must shut off the poisonous gas</i>
<i>and pump it out.</i>

33
00:03:29,626 --> 00:03:31,377
<i>Some passerby might get killed.</i>

34
00:03:31,545 --> 00:03:32,962
Yeah, I guess you're right.

35
00:03:33,130 --> 00:03:34,380
Oh, there, there.

36
00:03:42,097 --> 00:03:43,472
-Heh, heh.
-Okay, it's off.

37
00:03:43,640 --> 00:03:46,225
Ah, get the truck and load up.
QuickIy, quickIy.

38
00:03:46,393 --> 00:03:48,686
Go on, boys. Go on, me Iads.

39
00:03:48,854 --> 00:03:51,647
I think I'lI check to make sure.

40
00:03:55,360 --> 00:03:56,402
[JOKER CACKLING]

41
00:03:59,030 --> 00:04:00,072
[JOKER GASPING]

42
00:04:01,616 --> 00:04:04,744
Curses. They're getting away.

43
00:04:16,465 --> 00:04:18,048
Look. They discovered we're gone.

44
00:04:22,137 --> 00:04:25,973
Hey, boss. Hey, boss, boss, boss.
Look, Iook, look. They're up on the chimney.

45
00:04:26,141 --> 00:04:28,350
I know that, you fooI.

46
00:04:28,518 --> 00:04:32,062
-How did they get up there?
-They took the elevator, what do you think?

47
00:04:32,230 --> 00:04:34,440
You want us to get a rifle and shoot them?

48
00:04:34,608 --> 00:04:35,941
No, wait a minute.

49
00:04:36,109 --> 00:04:39,779
I've got a much more succuIent idea.
Heh, heh.

50
00:04:39,946 --> 00:04:41,822
Get in, get in.

51
00:04:44,951 --> 00:04:45,993
[LAUGHING]

52
00:04:47,496 --> 00:04:48,954
Strange, they're Ieaving.

53
00:04:49,122 --> 00:04:51,123
Perhaps they've changed their pIans.

54
00:04:51,291 --> 00:04:52,958
Now we'lI have to find them again.

55
00:04:53,126 --> 00:04:56,378
Right. Let's go.
Remember, the Maharaja's stilI in their power.

56
00:05:32,082 --> 00:05:37,002
Ah, drat. Nothing from this hole
from the goIf course or from the stoIen hairpin.

57
00:05:37,170 --> 00:05:39,129
What did the Joker use the hairpin for?

58
00:05:39,297 --> 00:05:42,967
To trigger the gas bomb
that knocked out the Maharaja.

59
00:05:43,635 --> 00:05:45,386
The gas bomb.

60
00:05:46,012 --> 00:05:49,390
Of course. If a trace of the gas remains....

61
00:06:05,198 --> 00:06:06,782
We've got it.

62
00:06:15,417 --> 00:06:17,459
Ah-ha. That's it.

63
00:06:17,627 --> 00:06:20,671
It's an uncommon gas.
In fact, I know of but one pIace...

64
00:06:20,839 --> 00:06:22,882
-...in Gotham City it'd be available.
-Where?

65
00:06:23,049 --> 00:06:25,384
The Ferguson NoveIty
and Magician Supply Company.

66
00:06:25,552 --> 00:06:27,928
-That's it.
-Right, and we've gotta hurry.

67
00:06:28,096 --> 00:06:30,222
If the Maharaja isn't recovered soon...

68
00:06:30,390 --> 00:06:33,517
...it couId make things very difficuIt
with his government.

69
00:06:34,394 --> 00:06:36,812
In fact, I'm surprised there hasn't been--

70
00:06:36,980 --> 00:06:39,607
-WelI, let's go.
-Wait. We'lI go...

71
00:06:39,774 --> 00:06:41,775
...but as Dick Grayson and Bruce Wayne.

72
00:06:41,943 --> 00:06:45,946
-Why? Do you think...?
-That it's being used as a front by the Joker?

73
00:06:46,740 --> 00:06:48,240
Exactly.

74
00:06:56,708 --> 00:06:57,750
[DICK LAUGHS]

75
00:06:57,918 --> 00:06:59,293
Who does this remind you of?

76
00:06:59,461 --> 00:07:00,920
CarefuI, oId chum.

77
00:07:05,717 --> 00:07:09,053
-Good afternoon. May I help you?
-Thank you.

78
00:07:09,220 --> 00:07:11,597
We thought we might find
some amusing favors...

79
00:07:11,765 --> 00:07:13,766
...for a party this young man's giving.

80
00:07:13,934 --> 00:07:15,392
To be sure.

81
00:07:15,560 --> 00:07:16,644
How about these?

82
00:07:17,312 --> 00:07:18,354
[DICK CHUCKLES]

83
00:07:23,693 --> 00:07:25,569
Very ingenious.

84
00:07:25,737 --> 00:07:27,237
Oh, miss.

85
00:07:27,739 --> 00:07:30,366
What is a "one-way gIass
reversing refractor"?

86
00:07:30,533 --> 00:07:34,161
A prism, which pIaced flush
against any one way gIass...

87
00:07:34,329 --> 00:07:37,998
...wiIl by refraction enabIe one
to Iook through the one way glass...

88
00:07:38,166 --> 00:07:40,751
...in the direction opposite
for which it was designed.

89
00:07:41,419 --> 00:07:44,588
-Oh, you mean like one-way mirrors and stuff.
-Yes.

90
00:07:44,756 --> 00:07:47,007
You can look through from the wrong side.

91
00:07:47,717 --> 00:07:49,176
That's right.

92
00:07:49,344 --> 00:07:52,096
Gee, Bruce, this wouId be keen
for spies, wouIdn't it?

93
00:07:52,263 --> 00:07:55,891
Dick, why don't you seIect something you Iike
and I'lI just, um, browse around.

94
00:08:05,568 --> 00:08:06,610
[TSKS]

95
00:08:16,913 --> 00:08:18,914
JILL:
Anything suspicious?

96
00:08:19,541 --> 00:08:22,501
No, just some squares.

97
00:08:27,549 --> 00:08:30,175
WelI, what are you Iooking at?

98
00:08:30,343 --> 00:08:33,470
A big, fat bundIe of ransom.

99
00:08:33,638 --> 00:08:36,181
And I think we've waited long enough.

100
00:09:10,550 --> 00:09:14,303
BATMAN: So this is the photograph we took
from across the street.

101
00:09:14,471 --> 00:09:16,972
Now, judging from the topography...

102
00:09:17,140 --> 00:09:21,310
...the underground prison room shouId be
located about here, under the hilI.

103
00:09:21,478 --> 00:09:23,896
HoIy impregnabiIity. It's good as a fort.

104
00:09:24,064 --> 00:09:27,524
And if the poIice try to break in,
the Joker wouId get too much warning.

105
00:09:27,692 --> 00:09:29,318
The Maharaja could be injured.

106
00:09:29,486 --> 00:09:31,737
So we have to find a way to get in secretly.

107
00:09:31,905 --> 00:09:33,280
But how?

108
00:09:33,448 --> 00:09:38,869
Fortunately, I got a glimpse
of a large square grilI in the back waII.

109
00:09:39,037 --> 00:09:40,704
What do you think it is, Batman?

110
00:09:40,872 --> 00:09:43,999
UnIess I missed my guess,
it's the cover for a ventiIating shaft...

111
00:09:44,167 --> 00:09:47,711
...which comes out right here,
on top of the hiII, straight above.

112
00:09:47,879 --> 00:09:50,506
HoIy camoufIage. What a way to get in.

113
00:09:50,673 --> 00:09:52,549
If only we knew where it was.

114
00:09:52,717 --> 00:09:56,178
If my trigonometry is correct...

115
00:09:56,596 --> 00:10:00,224
...and based on this photograph,
it should emerge...

116
00:10:03,436 --> 00:10:04,895
...right here.

117
00:10:05,063 --> 00:10:06,355
Gosh, Batman.

118
00:10:06,523 --> 00:10:09,483
-I'II never negIect my math again.
-Let's go.

119
00:10:20,954 --> 00:10:24,498
ROBIN: Batman, where are you?
-Shh. Shh.

120
00:10:27,001 --> 00:10:30,129
If it's nearby,
they could hear us down under.

121
00:10:45,061 --> 00:10:46,562
ROBIN:
I think I found it.

122
00:10:47,772 --> 00:10:50,524
How far did you say that room was
underground?

123
00:10:50,692 --> 00:10:53,861
About 50 feet,
enough to give us good momentum.

124
00:10:54,028 --> 00:10:57,614
Oh, boy, I'lI say. Can I go first?
I wanna see their faces.

125
00:10:59,242 --> 00:11:01,285
Dynamic seniority.

126
00:11:02,745 --> 00:11:05,956
This could be a mistake, I suppose.

127
00:11:06,541 --> 00:11:09,334
WelI, look out beIow.

128
00:11:14,465 --> 00:11:16,842
Don't anyone move. You're aIl under arrest.

129
00:11:17,385 --> 00:11:21,054
-It's Batman.
-Joker, where's the Maharaja?

130
00:11:21,222 --> 00:11:23,974
-I toId you he'd find us, you cIown.
-Ugh.

131
00:11:24,142 --> 00:11:28,103
What's the matter with you, Batman?
I'm the funny man.

132
00:11:28,271 --> 00:11:31,690
To arms, men! RepeI the invaders!

133
00:11:31,858 --> 00:11:34,735
AlI right. If that's the way you want it.

134
00:11:36,946 --> 00:11:37,988
[ALARM WAILING]

135
00:11:57,717 --> 00:11:58,759
[YELLS]

136
00:12:01,554 --> 00:12:02,596
[GRUNTS]

137
00:12:12,106 --> 00:12:13,148
[GRUNTING]

138
00:12:29,040 --> 00:12:31,750
Egads, the tide's turning against us.

139
00:12:31,918 --> 00:12:35,045
-Let's scram, Joker.
-Oh, okay.

140
00:12:43,846 --> 00:12:45,931
-What happened?
-Where did they go?

141
00:12:49,477 --> 00:12:50,936
Aah! Holy moIehiIl.

142
00:12:51,104 --> 00:12:53,730
-They went into the mountain.
-Fiends.

143
00:12:54,691 --> 00:12:57,025
ProbabIy comes out
on the other side of the hiIl.

144
00:12:57,193 --> 00:12:59,528
But where's the Maharaja? I didn't see him.

145
00:12:59,696 --> 00:13:03,156
They probabIy moved him before we got here.
We'II make a thorough search.

146
00:13:03,324 --> 00:13:05,867
I don't expect to find anything.

147
00:13:13,501 --> 00:13:14,543
[PHONE RINGING]

148
00:13:22,176 --> 00:13:23,677
Commissioner Gordon.

149
00:13:23,845 --> 00:13:25,762
Oh, heIIo, Batman.

150
00:13:25,930 --> 00:13:28,015
Yes, I've been waiting for you to caII.

151
00:13:28,182 --> 00:13:29,808
I hope you have good news for us.

152
00:13:29,976 --> 00:13:31,727
I'm afraid not, commissioner.

153
00:13:31,894 --> 00:13:34,980
We've traced the Joker here to his hideout
and surprised him...

154
00:13:35,148 --> 00:13:37,816
...but he eIuded us, I'm afraid.

155
00:13:37,984 --> 00:13:40,944
-And the Maharaja?
-There was no sign of him.

156
00:13:41,112 --> 00:13:43,780
If we don't find him soon,
I shaII notify Washington.

157
00:13:43,948 --> 00:13:45,907
Yes, I'm aware of that.

158
00:13:46,075 --> 00:13:49,119
-Have you heard about the ransom yet?
GORDON: <i>N</i><i>o</i><i>.</i>

159
00:13:50,121 --> 00:13:55,208
You might send the wagon over here.
There are four of the Joker's men to pick up.

160
00:13:55,376 --> 00:13:58,211
We're at the Ferguson Magicians
and Novelty Supply.

161
00:13:59,339 --> 00:14:01,089
Okay, I'Il take care of that
and notify the--

162
00:14:01,257 --> 00:14:02,299
[DOOR OPENS]

163
00:14:02,467 --> 00:14:03,508
Wait a minute.

164
00:14:03,676 --> 00:14:05,719
Commissioner,
the Joker is on the air on our band.

165
00:14:05,887 --> 00:14:07,929
-He wants to speak to you.
-Bring him in.

166
00:14:08,097 --> 00:14:09,681
-Did you hear that, Batman?
BATMAN: <i>Y</i><i>e</i><i>s</i><i>.</i>

167
00:14:09,849 --> 00:14:11,516
WelI, hang on and Iisten.

168
00:14:19,025 --> 00:14:22,819
This is Commissioner Gordon's office.
Go ahead, Joker.

169
00:14:23,404 --> 00:14:26,406
<i></i>J<i></i>O<i></i>K<i></i>E<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> Good evening, commissioner.</i>
<i>Happy to find you in.</i>

170
00:14:26,574 --> 00:14:28,992
<i>Perhaps you can do me a favor.</i>

171
00:14:29,160 --> 00:14:30,619
I warn you, Joker...

172
00:14:30,787 --> 00:14:35,207
...if the Maharaja is harmed,
we'II hunt you down if it takes 1 00 years.

173
00:14:35,375 --> 00:14:39,753
<i></i>J<i></i>O<i></i>K<i></i>E<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> By that time, my jokes would be stale,</i>
<i>wouldn't they, commissioner? Heh, heh.</i>

174
00:14:39,921 --> 00:14:42,547
I haven't the time for chitchat
with your kind, Joker.

175
00:14:42,715 --> 00:14:44,466
If you have something to say, say it.

176
00:14:44,634 --> 00:14:48,637
<i></i>J<i></i>O<i></i>K<i></i>E<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> Very well. I want to talk to Batman.</i>
<i>Can you arrange it?</i>

177
00:14:49,764 --> 00:14:51,848
-Did you hear that, Batman?
<i></i>B<i></i>AT<i></i>M<i></i>A<i></i>N<i></i>:<i> Yes, I heard it.</i>

178
00:14:52,016 --> 00:14:54,976
-Do you wanna taIk to him?
-By alI means.

179
00:14:55,478 --> 00:15:00,107
I just happen to be in touch with Batman now
and we have set up a relay here in the office.

180
00:15:00,274 --> 00:15:02,692
The next time you speak,
he wilI hear your voice...

181
00:15:02,860 --> 00:15:05,320
...and you can hear his reply.

182
00:15:05,488 --> 00:15:07,447
JOKER:
<i>What superb service.</i>

183
00:15:07,615 --> 00:15:10,367
<i>-Are you there, Batman?</i>
-I'm here.

184
00:15:10,535 --> 00:15:15,497
<i></i>J<i></i>O<i></i>K<i></i>E<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> Well, the fun and games are over, old</i>
<i>fellow, and it's time for the harvest, as it were.</i>

185
00:15:15,665 --> 00:15:19,418
<i>I want to enlist your help</i>
<i>in the ransom arrangements.</i>

186
00:15:21,129 --> 00:15:22,212
Never.

187
00:15:22,380 --> 00:15:25,590
<i></i>J<i></i>O<i></i>K<i></i>E<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> Now, don't take a stand</i>
<i>until you've heard everything, old boy.</i>

188
00:15:25,758 --> 00:15:29,052
<i>I've a friend here who wants to talk to you.</i>

189
00:15:30,012 --> 00:15:33,390
MAHARAJA:
<i>This is Maharaja of Nimpa speaking.</i>

190
00:15:34,517 --> 00:15:36,810
Your highness, are you aIl right?

191
00:15:36,978 --> 00:15:42,107
<i></i>M<i></i>A<i></i>H<i></i>A<i></i>RA<i></i>J<i></i>A<i></i>:<i> Quite all right, thank you, and</i>
<i>enjoying delightful interval with bandit Joker.</i>

192
00:15:42,900 --> 00:15:44,901
<i>But now time to return to business.</i>

193
00:15:45,570 --> 00:15:50,157
<i>Would Batman please arrange</i>
<i>to cash personal check tomorrow?</i>

194
00:15:50,324 --> 00:15:52,534
Your check? What for?

195
00:15:52,702 --> 00:15:55,162
MAHARAJA:
<i>For ransom money, what else?</i>

196
00:15:55,329 --> 00:15:57,998
You're gonna cash
the ransom check yourseIf?

197
00:15:59,333 --> 00:16:00,584
For how much?

198
00:16:00,751 --> 00:16:03,128
MAHARAJA:
<i>Half-million dollars, U.S.</i>

199
00:16:03,754 --> 00:16:06,673
<i></i>B<i></i>AT<i></i>M<i></i>A<i></i>N<i></i>:<i> And how do you intend</i>
<i>to pay it to the Joker?</i>

200
00:16:06,841 --> 00:16:10,969
<i></i>M<i></i>A<i></i>H<i></i>A<i></i>RA<i></i>J<i></i>A<i></i>:<i> That is already arranged</i>
<i>between bandit Joker and Maharaja.</i>

201
00:16:11,637 --> 00:16:13,054
<i>What is matter?</i>

202
00:16:13,222 --> 00:16:15,140
<i>You not approve?</i>

203
00:16:15,308 --> 00:16:19,269
I certainIy do not approve.
I'II have nothing to do with it.

204
00:16:19,437 --> 00:16:23,523
You're free to do as you wish, of course,
but Ieave me out of this.

205
00:16:23,691 --> 00:16:27,360
<i></i>M<i></i>A<i></i>H<i></i>A<i></i>RAJ<i></i>A<i></i>:<i> But unfortunate,</i>
<i>not possible to leave you out.</i>

206
00:16:27,528 --> 00:16:29,988
<i>I will let bandit Joker explain.</i>

207
00:16:30,531 --> 00:16:33,283
JOKER:
<i>You see, that's part of the price, Batman.</i>

208
00:16:33,451 --> 00:16:35,243
<i>You make the arrangements...</i>

209
00:16:35,411 --> 00:16:38,121
<i>...you be present</i>
<i>when he cashes the check...</i>

210
00:16:38,289 --> 00:16:40,707
<i>...and you endorse the check.</i>

211
00:16:41,209 --> 00:16:45,128
<i>Otherwise, no Maharaja.</i>

212
00:16:45,296 --> 00:16:47,130
[JOKER LAUGHS]

213
00:16:47,298 --> 00:16:49,925
It's a rotten bargain, Joker.

214
00:16:50,718 --> 00:16:54,095
But the Maharaja's safety counts
above everything eIse.

215
00:16:54,764 --> 00:16:56,097
You've won.

216
00:16:57,642 --> 00:17:00,352
The Gotham City State Bank...

217
00:17:00,520 --> 00:17:01,895
...main office...

218
00:17:02,063 --> 00:17:05,398
...tomorrow morning, 1 0:00.

219
00:17:06,567 --> 00:17:10,237
NARRATOR:
<i>Is it always darkest just before the dawn?</i>

220
00:17:12,323 --> 00:17:16,493
<i>Not when dawn, that is to say, 1 0 a.m...</i>

221
00:17:16,661 --> 00:17:19,579
<i>...brings ruin and humiliation.</i>

222
00:17:20,122 --> 00:17:24,084
PRESCOTT:
Four hundred and fifty, 460, 470...

223
00:17:24,252 --> 00:17:27,754
...480, one haIf miIIion doIlars.

224
00:17:27,922 --> 00:17:30,966
There he is, right on time.

225
00:17:32,093 --> 00:17:33,134
[KNOCK ON DOOR]

226
00:17:34,470 --> 00:17:36,555
This way, your highness.

227
00:17:40,935 --> 00:17:43,436
I am Prescott BeImont, Your Highness.

228
00:17:43,604 --> 00:17:46,856
I don't beIieve you've met Batman
and his associate, Robin.

229
00:17:47,024 --> 00:17:50,318
How do you do?
I wanna thank you for cooperating, Batman.

230
00:17:50,486 --> 00:17:53,196
-You have the money?
-Yes, it's aII here.

231
00:17:53,364 --> 00:17:54,406
Ah.

232
00:17:56,993 --> 00:17:58,410
Good.

233
00:18:10,006 --> 00:18:15,093
-Paid to the order of Batman.
-One T.

234
00:18:15,636 --> 00:18:17,971
MAHARAJA:
Five hundred thousand doIlars...

235
00:18:19,015 --> 00:18:21,057
...and no cents.

236
00:18:27,773 --> 00:18:29,941
Now, you wiII endorse.

237
00:18:31,485 --> 00:18:33,570
'Tis a sad day for Batman.

238
00:18:33,738 --> 00:18:36,615
Forced to use his name for a criminaI payoff.

239
00:18:36,782 --> 00:18:39,826
Yes. I'm afraid
this wiIl tarnish his image considerabIy.

240
00:18:42,204 --> 00:18:45,957
Good. Now I wilI take the money.

241
00:18:47,960 --> 00:18:49,502
Don't you wanna count it?

242
00:18:50,463 --> 00:18:53,173
-Did you count it?
-WelI, yes, of course.

243
00:18:53,674 --> 00:18:55,091
Why should we both count it?

244
00:18:55,551 --> 00:18:57,344
Oh, weII....

245
00:18:57,511 --> 00:18:58,553
[LAUGHS]

246
00:18:59,972 --> 00:19:01,222
Your Highness...

247
00:19:01,390 --> 00:19:04,601
...do you actualIy intend
to give this fortune to that criminaI...

248
00:19:04,769 --> 00:19:07,354
...even though you're free
and there's no necessity?

249
00:19:07,521 --> 00:19:08,855
Last desperate effort.

250
00:19:09,357 --> 00:19:13,777
Why not?
You see, Joker is an honorable bandit.

251
00:19:13,944 --> 00:19:15,278
We made a bargain.

252
00:19:15,446 --> 00:19:20,283
He kept his side. Now, Nimpanese
gentleman must keep my side.

253
00:19:21,577 --> 00:19:24,454
Yes, I can see that
you'd wanna keep your word...

254
00:19:24,622 --> 00:19:26,581
...even to a lying criminaI.

255
00:19:27,166 --> 00:19:29,626
MAHARAJA:
But to me, Joker did not lie.

256
00:19:29,794 --> 00:19:33,797
You see, in my country,
a bandit is an honorabIe profession.

257
00:19:33,964 --> 00:19:38,134
And if peopIe Iie to bandits,
pretty soon bandit wiIl lie to people...

258
00:19:38,302 --> 00:19:42,263
...and everybody wiII not beIieve the other
and they wiIl fight amongst themselves.

259
00:19:42,431 --> 00:19:45,308
And then pretty soon,
nobody wiII have anything.

260
00:19:45,476 --> 00:19:49,437
Also, in my country,
popuIation is 80 percent--

261
00:19:49,605 --> 00:19:50,647
[SCREAMS]

262
00:19:50,815 --> 00:19:52,399
-Let's go!
-Oh, no, you don't.

263
00:20:03,953 --> 00:20:04,994
[GRUNTING]

264
00:20:07,081 --> 00:20:08,790
Batman, what are you doing?

265
00:20:48,205 --> 00:20:51,124
-It's the Joker.
O'HARA: That it is.

266
00:20:51,292 --> 00:20:52,584
But where's the Maharaja?

267
00:20:52,752 --> 00:20:55,170
-There isn't any.
-There never was.

268
00:20:55,337 --> 00:20:59,215
-You mean it was the Joker aIl the time?
-Right.

269
00:20:59,383 --> 00:21:01,593
As you recalI,
you never saw them together.

270
00:21:02,470 --> 00:21:06,264
Then his goaI was not onIy
an historic criminaI coup...

271
00:21:06,432 --> 00:21:09,017
-...but your disgrace as weII?
-Not only that.

272
00:21:09,185 --> 00:21:13,855
My endorsement on a worthIess check
for haIf a miIlion dolIars.

273
00:21:14,023 --> 00:21:15,982
If you hadn't thwarted them....

274
00:21:16,150 --> 00:21:20,320
Oh, Batman, how did you ever see through
his deviIish pIot?

275
00:21:21,447 --> 00:21:25,241
It wasn't difficult, if you remember the key
to the Joker's twisted mind.

276
00:21:25,409 --> 00:21:27,786
ROBIN:
He never means what he seems to mean.

277
00:21:28,579 --> 00:21:30,121
Now, why didn't we think of that?

278
00:21:30,289 --> 00:21:34,959
Also, it seems strange that
we'd heard no protest from his government.

279
00:21:35,127 --> 00:21:37,879
So Batman calIed the paIace of Nimpa.

280
00:21:38,047 --> 00:21:42,926
The real Maharaja is on a hunting trip
in the Nimpa mountains.

281
00:21:43,093 --> 00:21:44,928
You've done it again, Batman.

282
00:21:48,724 --> 00:21:53,353
Egads, I'm deflated.

283
00:21:53,521 --> 00:21:56,189
A fitting end for you, Joker.

284
00:21:56,357 --> 00:21:58,233
Like the rest of your criminaI iIk...

285
00:21:58,400 --> 00:22:01,986
...you were never anything
but a threatening bag of hot air.

286
00:22:02,154 --> 00:22:05,573
Chief O'Hara, calI your men.
Cart this human trash away.

287
00:22:05,741 --> 00:22:07,075
Right.

288
00:22:19,213 --> 00:22:22,590
NARRATOR:
<i>An hour or so later at stately Wayne Manor...</i>

289
00:22:22,758 --> 00:22:26,135
<i>...where everything is now tranquil and serene.</i>

290
00:22:26,303 --> 00:22:27,929
<i>Or is it?</i>

291
00:22:28,097 --> 00:22:29,138
[BEEPING]

292
00:22:40,401 --> 00:22:42,277
Are you sure you want him, sir?

293
00:22:42,444 --> 00:22:47,115
I got the impression that he had just
satisfactorily concIuded the, um, due.

294
00:22:47,283 --> 00:22:50,243
But I must speak to him immediately, please.

295
00:22:51,662 --> 00:22:53,621
If you insist, sir.

296
00:22:55,875 --> 00:23:01,379
No, Dick.
You'II get as fat as the Maharaja of Nimpa.

297
00:23:01,547 --> 00:23:03,131
Who, Aunt Harriet?

298
00:23:03,299 --> 00:23:05,633
The Maharaja of Nimpa.

299
00:23:05,801 --> 00:23:09,137
I just saw his picture
in the Gotham City Herald.

300
00:23:09,305 --> 00:23:11,431
He was on a tiger hunting expedition...

301
00:23:11,599 --> 00:23:15,768
...and you never saw anybody so fat
in your whole Iife.

302
00:23:15,936 --> 00:23:17,854
Mercy aIive, with aIl his money...

303
00:23:18,022 --> 00:23:21,774
...you'd think he couId afford
to see a doctor about a diet.

304
00:23:22,651 --> 00:23:24,986
It's the Batphone, sir.

305
00:23:25,154 --> 00:23:26,321
Now?

306
00:23:28,574 --> 00:23:30,033
That reminds me, Dick.

307
00:23:30,200 --> 00:23:32,493
I have a new voIume on tiger hunting.

308
00:23:32,661 --> 00:23:35,330
It's in the study,
I've been meaning to show it to you.

309
00:23:35,497 --> 00:23:37,415
HoIy encore, you mean...?

310
00:23:37,583 --> 00:23:41,669
-Gosh, Bruce, I'm interested in tiger hunting.
-Excuse us, Aunt Harriet.

311
00:23:42,671 --> 00:23:45,632
-Tea, madame?
-Oh, yes, AIfred.

312
00:23:50,846 --> 00:23:52,138
Yes, commissioner?

313
00:23:52,306 --> 00:23:53,681
Shocking news, Batman.

314
00:23:54,558 --> 00:23:55,642
What couId it be?

315
00:23:55,809 --> 00:23:58,102
I've heard a most alarming rumor...

316
00:23:58,270 --> 00:24:01,564
...that you've been asked to go to CaIifornia
and run for governor.

317
00:24:01,732 --> 00:24:03,107
[CHUCKLES]

318
00:24:03,275 --> 00:24:06,945
CaIm your fears, commissioner.
The rumor is unfounded.

319
00:24:07,112 --> 00:24:10,156
As Iong as there's a criminaI at Iarge
in Gotham City...

320
00:24:10,324 --> 00:24:12,158
...wiId horses couIdn't drag me away.

321
00:24:12,743 --> 00:24:15,244
Oh, thank heavens, Batman.

322
00:24:15,412 --> 00:24:17,038
Saints be praised.

323
00:24:17,206 --> 00:24:18,915
Good bye, commissioner.

324
00:24:19,083 --> 00:24:21,125
HoIy GoIden Gate.

325
00:24:26,966 --> 00:24:30,510
<i></i>N<i></i>A<i></i>R<i></i>RAT<i></i>O<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> Next week, King Tut tangoes</i>
<i>with the dynamic duo.</i>

326
00:25:14,304 --> 00:25:16,305
[EngIish - US - SDH]

