1
00:00:11,053 --> 00:00:14,263
NARRATOR:
<i>Afternoon in Gotham Central Park...</i>

2
00:00:14,431 --> 00:00:19,936
<i>...noble sanctuary of nature</i>
<i>in the midst of the teeming metropolis.</i>

3
00:00:20,729 --> 00:00:24,857
<i>Tranquility, peace, quiet.</i>

4
00:00:25,025 --> 00:00:31,822
<i>The deceptive quiet of the jungle</i>
<i>where a criminal beast is to about to spring.</i>

5
00:01:01,770 --> 00:01:02,812
[SCREAMS]

6
00:01:20,872 --> 00:01:22,790
NEFERTITI:
<i>Now, hear this.</i>

7
00:01:22,958 --> 00:01:24,917
<i>Now, hear this.</i>

8
00:01:25,544 --> 00:01:30,881
<i>It is written in the stars that on this day</i>
<i>shall the great king of the Nile...</i>

9
00:01:31,049 --> 00:01:33,050
<i>...rise up from the tomb.</i>

10
00:01:33,218 --> 00:01:36,846
<i>And he shall claim his kingdom</i>
<i>of Gotham City.</i>

11
00:01:37,014 --> 00:01:41,267
<i>And all who oppose him</i>
<i>shall be smitten dead.</i>

12
00:01:41,435 --> 00:01:42,476
"Giant Sphinx."

13
00:01:43,854 --> 00:01:47,565
"Uttering demented threats
in Gotham Central Park in a woman's voice"?

14
00:01:47,733 --> 00:01:49,900
Sure, and it couId be harmIess, sir.

15
00:01:50,068 --> 00:01:52,028
Uh, how so, Chief O'Hara?

16
00:01:52,195 --> 00:01:54,238
There was a piece in the paper this morning.

17
00:01:54,406 --> 00:01:57,533
The Gotham City museum
is unveiIing a new exhibit...

18
00:01:57,701 --> 00:02:00,119
...of Egyptian antiques this very day.

19
00:02:00,287 --> 00:02:01,329
Of course.

20
00:02:01,496 --> 00:02:03,998
-And this couId be just a pubIicity stunt.
-Yes, sir.

21
00:02:04,166 --> 00:02:08,628
Is there no Iimit to the brazen effrontery
of the press agent?

22
00:02:08,795 --> 00:02:11,464
I'II put paid to their stunts.

23
00:02:11,632 --> 00:02:12,673
BONNIE [OVER INTERCOM]:
<i>Y</i><i>e</i><i>s</i><i>?</i>

24
00:02:12,841 --> 00:02:15,343
Bonnie, get me my good friend,
miIIionaire Bruce Wayne.

25
00:02:15,510 --> 00:02:18,137
I expect he'II be at his stateIy residence,
Wayne Manor.

26
00:02:18,805 --> 00:02:21,140
WelI, time to leave for the museum,
one and aII.

27
00:02:21,308 --> 00:02:22,350
Mercy, yes.

28
00:02:22,517 --> 00:02:23,559
Let's not be Iate, Bruce.

29
00:02:23,727 --> 00:02:24,769
[PHONE RINGS]

30
00:02:24,936 --> 00:02:28,522
There isn't anything I enjoy
more than a nice fresh exhibit...

31
00:02:28,690 --> 00:02:31,275
-...of Egyptian antiquities.
-Ahem.

32
00:02:31,443 --> 00:02:33,611
-What is it, AIfred?
-The teIephone, madam.

33
00:02:34,029 --> 00:02:37,782
PoIice Commissioner Gordon
wishes to speak with, uh, Mr. Wayne.

34
00:02:37,949 --> 00:02:39,825
-With me, AIfred?
-Yes, sir.

35
00:02:39,993 --> 00:02:43,037
He was most distinct,
"With Mr. Bruce Wayne."

36
00:02:43,205 --> 00:02:44,330
Excuse me, Aunt Harriet.

37
00:02:47,959 --> 00:02:49,001
Bruce Wayne speaking.

38
00:02:49,169 --> 00:02:50,920
Oh, uh, sorry to bother you, Bruce.

39
00:02:51,088 --> 00:02:54,340
But you're on the board of trustees
of the Gotham Museum, aren't you?

40
00:02:54,508 --> 00:02:56,300
CertainIy. I'm treasurer, in fact.

41
00:02:56,468 --> 00:02:58,260
GORDON:
<i>Well, you've gone too far, Bruce.</i>

42
00:02:58,428 --> 00:03:03,849
This Sphinx which has reared itseIf at the park,
this terrifying pubIicity stunt, it--

43
00:03:04,017 --> 00:03:05,393
This what?

44
00:03:06,103 --> 00:03:09,397
You mean it isn't a publicity stunt?

45
00:03:09,564 --> 00:03:13,317
My dear commissioner,
I think you've taken leave of your wits.

46
00:03:13,485 --> 00:03:14,652
Goodbye.

47
00:03:18,073 --> 00:03:23,744
Imagine, the idea of the Gotham museum
puIling a pubIicity stunt.

48
00:03:23,912 --> 00:03:27,957
-So if it's not a stunt--
-Precisely, Chief O'Hara.

49
00:03:28,125 --> 00:03:34,463
This phenomenon takes on new dimensions,
strange and sinister dimensions.

50
00:03:34,631 --> 00:03:40,052
In fact, there's only one man aIive
who can take its measure.

51
00:03:47,394 --> 00:03:48,436
[BATPHONE BEEPING]

52
00:03:52,816 --> 00:03:54,859
I'II summon him, sir.

53
00:04:10,459 --> 00:04:12,042
Bruce, come on.

54
00:04:12,210 --> 00:04:14,587
What on Earth's the matter with you two?

55
00:04:14,755 --> 00:04:17,631
I don't know, Aunt Harriet.
It's just that-- A Sphinx, he said.

56
00:04:17,799 --> 00:04:20,217
Gosh, Bruce,
if that means what it couId mean....

57
00:04:20,385 --> 00:04:23,053
-We'II know soon enough.
-Excuse me, sir.

58
00:04:23,346 --> 00:04:24,889
Something in red, AIfred?

59
00:04:25,474 --> 00:04:26,557
Precisely, sir.

60
00:04:27,142 --> 00:04:28,851
Great heavens, how forgetfuI of me.

61
00:04:29,019 --> 00:04:32,563
This new voIume by Professor Red
on ancient Egyptian cat worship cuIts.

62
00:04:32,731 --> 00:04:35,232
I'd promised the museum committee
I'd Iook through it.

63
00:04:35,400 --> 00:04:37,318
-Come on, Dick.
-Bruce.

64
00:04:37,486 --> 00:04:41,155
Those antiquities have waited thousands
of years for us, Aunt Harriet.

65
00:04:41,323 --> 00:04:43,282
They'lI wait a IittIe Ionger.

66
00:04:45,827 --> 00:04:49,038
Mercy aIive, such an impetuous pair.

67
00:04:49,206 --> 00:04:52,792
There shouId be some way
to harness such energy.

68
00:04:55,837 --> 00:04:56,879
Yes, commissioner?

69
00:04:57,047 --> 00:04:59,423
GORDON:
<i>A strange and terrible threat to Gotham City.</i>

70
00:04:59,591 --> 00:05:01,717
An uItimatum from the remote past.

71
00:05:01,885 --> 00:05:03,677
We're on our way.

72
00:05:03,929 --> 00:05:06,972
HoIy hierogIyphics,
this might mean a battIe royale.

73
00:05:07,140 --> 00:05:09,225
Not the first, Dick, nor the last.

74
00:05:09,392 --> 00:05:11,268
To the Batpoles.

75
00:06:39,065 --> 00:06:42,234
There's no doubt at aIl.

76
00:06:43,111 --> 00:06:46,655
We're faced with that arch criminaI King Tut.

77
00:06:46,823 --> 00:06:49,491
Gosh. And everyone thought he died
in that warehouse fire.

78
00:06:49,659 --> 00:06:50,951
We were mistaken it seems.

79
00:06:51,119 --> 00:06:54,496
He's risen Iike a phoenix
from the ashes to....

80
00:06:56,958 --> 00:06:59,418
Just what was his threat, commissioner?

81
00:06:59,586 --> 00:07:00,961
Grandiose, Batman.

82
00:07:01,129 --> 00:07:02,963
He cIaimed Gotham City for his own.

83
00:07:03,131 --> 00:07:05,591
In a greedy femaIe voice.

84
00:07:05,759 --> 00:07:10,054
So our mad pharaoh
has found himseIf a Nefertiti.

85
00:07:10,221 --> 00:07:13,641
Some hapIess femaIe entrapped
in a Iife of crime.

86
00:07:13,808 --> 00:07:15,851
The situation is grim, Batman.

87
00:07:16,019 --> 00:07:19,438
We've cordoned off the park
but I fear panic wiIl soon rear its ugIy head.

88
00:07:19,606 --> 00:07:22,149
We couId caII out the National Guard.

89
00:07:22,317 --> 00:07:25,027
Have them bIast that pagan Sphinx
with their artiIIery.

90
00:07:25,195 --> 00:07:26,612
No, Chief O'Hara. No.

91
00:07:26,780 --> 00:07:28,489
-No?
-No.

92
00:07:28,657 --> 00:07:32,493
If that were our objective, I couId do it
more simpIy with the Batmobile's Batbeam.

93
00:07:32,661 --> 00:07:36,205
Batman is right. King Tut may be a super crook
but he's a sick man too.

94
00:07:36,373 --> 00:07:38,499
Precisely, Robin.

95
00:07:38,667 --> 00:07:44,129
Let's not forget that he was once
an eminent professor at Yale University.

96
00:07:44,297 --> 00:07:47,174
That he was struck on the head
during a student riot...

97
00:07:47,342 --> 00:07:51,428
...and awoke with a strange
doubIe deIusion...

98
00:07:51,596 --> 00:07:54,431
...that Gotham City is the reincarnation
of ancient Thebes...

99
00:07:54,599 --> 00:07:59,311
...and he himseIf,
the pharaoh known to history as King Tut.

100
00:08:00,772 --> 00:08:02,606
This man is to be pitied.

101
00:08:02,774 --> 00:08:04,733
Pitied, Batman? Ha.

102
00:08:04,901 --> 00:08:08,445
How can one pity a criminaI
who threatens our entire citizenry with death?

103
00:08:08,613 --> 00:08:11,991
Pitied, commissioner,
tempered with caution.

104
00:08:12,158 --> 00:08:14,827
Our first aim is to thwart his criminaI pIans.

105
00:08:14,995 --> 00:08:16,412
What couId it be?

106
00:08:16,579 --> 00:08:19,331
A mad dream to make subjects of us aIl.

107
00:08:19,499 --> 00:08:21,250
O'HARA:
But why tip us off?

108
00:08:21,418 --> 00:08:23,627
Why warn us
that he's trying to make a comeback?

109
00:08:23,795 --> 00:08:26,046
Maybe the Sphinx wilI give us a cIue.

110
00:08:26,214 --> 00:08:27,381
Robin's right.

111
00:08:27,549 --> 00:08:29,216
And we don't have a moment to Iose.

112
00:08:29,384 --> 00:08:32,553
Let's take a close Iook
at that inscrutabIe Iady.

113
00:08:32,721 --> 00:08:35,347
Be careful, Batman. Be careful.

114
00:08:37,058 --> 00:08:40,561
NARRATOR:
<i>Meanwhile, in the palace of King Tut...</i>

115
00:08:40,729 --> 00:08:44,857
<i>...bizarre remnants</i>
<i>of last year's Gotham City exposition.</i>

116
00:08:45,025 --> 00:08:50,988
<i>Chief O'Hara's question is echoed</i>
<i>inside the moldering great hall.</i>

117
00:08:51,156 --> 00:08:52,448
I don't get it.

118
00:08:52,615 --> 00:08:56,577
If you're gonna move
in on somebody's territory, why tip him off?

119
00:08:56,745 --> 00:08:58,787
How should I know?
I'm onIy the Grand Vizier.

120
00:08:58,955 --> 00:09:01,540
Why don't you ask his royaI highness?

121
00:09:17,515 --> 00:09:20,059
You may rise.

122
00:09:22,645 --> 00:09:24,605
LoyaI subjects...

123
00:09:24,773 --> 00:09:28,275
...we are pIeased to inform you
that phase one of our royaI master pIan...

124
00:09:28,443 --> 00:09:31,028
...has succeeded as prophesied.

125
00:09:31,196 --> 00:09:32,571
Hey, that's great, boss.

126
00:09:33,907 --> 00:09:35,783
I mean, your royaI highness.

127
00:09:36,618 --> 00:09:41,080
Phase two wiIl now be put into being.

128
00:09:41,247 --> 00:09:43,957
-Are there any questions?
-I got one.

129
00:09:44,125 --> 00:09:46,168
You may speak, RoyaI Scrivener.

130
00:09:46,336 --> 00:09:47,377
Like why?

131
00:09:47,545 --> 00:09:49,379
Why put that hunk of rock in the park...

132
00:09:49,547 --> 00:09:51,465
...and tip off what we're gonna do?

133
00:09:51,633 --> 00:09:53,133
You're a twit.

134
00:09:54,427 --> 00:09:57,221
It's mereIy a sovereign subterfuge...

135
00:09:57,388 --> 00:10:03,060
...to exterminate a winged rodent
once and for alI, Batman.

136
00:10:03,561 --> 00:10:07,189
He shouId be biting at the bait about now.

137
00:10:07,357 --> 00:10:09,191
Oh, boy.

138
00:10:09,359 --> 00:10:12,569
AlI haiI to King Tut.

139
00:10:12,737 --> 00:10:18,200
Great lord of Thebes, nemesis of the Nile.

140
00:10:20,495 --> 00:10:23,413
Thank you, Grand Vizier, thank you.

141
00:10:23,581 --> 00:10:26,041
It was deIightfuIIy spoken.

142
00:10:26,543 --> 00:10:29,461
However, just on the off chance...

143
00:10:29,629 --> 00:10:33,757
...that the dynamic duo
shouId elude our snick-snack-snare...

144
00:10:33,925 --> 00:10:35,425
...battIe stations.

145
00:10:35,593 --> 00:10:37,344
To the royaI barque.

146
00:10:37,512 --> 00:10:42,391
We'II Iend our sinister Sphinx support.

147
00:10:43,601 --> 00:10:45,060
What do you make of it, Batman?

148
00:10:45,228 --> 00:10:49,022
A rather good imitation
of the fourth dynasty Sphinx of Giza.

149
00:10:49,190 --> 00:10:50,524
[STATUE WHIRS]

150
00:10:50,692 --> 00:10:52,943
HoIy hurricane, what's that?

151
00:10:53,111 --> 00:10:56,697
I think it means the Sphinx
is going to make another pronouncement.

152
00:10:56,865 --> 00:10:58,615
NEFERTITI:
<i>Now, hear this.</i>

153
00:10:58,783 --> 00:11:00,826
<i>Now, hear this.</i>

154
00:11:00,994 --> 00:11:04,872
<i>Whosoever transgresses</i>
<i>upon the Sacred Sphinx...</i>

155
00:11:05,039 --> 00:11:11,545
<i>...shall be smitten down by Anubis,</i>
<i>the jackal god, guardian of the cemeteries...</i>

156
00:11:11,713 --> 00:11:15,132
<i>...and that goes double for Batman.</i>

157
00:11:15,300 --> 00:11:18,343
-ChalIenge?
-So be it. Up we go.

158
00:11:27,645 --> 00:11:28,896
ROBIN:
What do you think, Batman?

159
00:11:29,063 --> 00:11:31,190
Could it be fuIl of King Tut's henchmen?

160
00:11:31,357 --> 00:11:34,276
If it is,
there must be a secret entrance somewhere.

161
00:11:34,819 --> 00:11:36,445
Look here.

162
00:11:37,197 --> 00:11:40,240
-This must be it.
-Don't touch that handle, Robin.

163
00:11:40,408 --> 00:11:43,535
-We don't know what we're up against yet.
-You're right.

164
00:11:43,703 --> 00:11:46,538
The Sphinx couId be booby trapped.

165
00:11:47,040 --> 00:11:49,124
Let's play it safe.

166
00:12:10,647 --> 00:12:11,813
HoIy whiskers!

167
00:12:11,981 --> 00:12:13,690
That was a cIose shave.

168
00:12:13,858 --> 00:12:16,610
There's no Ionger any doubt, Robin.

169
00:12:17,028 --> 00:12:21,698
The brilIiant, warped mind of King Tut
is bent on murder.

170
00:12:33,920 --> 00:12:35,879
SignaI from Nefertiti.

171
00:12:36,047 --> 00:12:37,923
Indeed.

172
00:12:38,091 --> 00:12:42,344
What does great Ra, god of the sun,
have to inform us?

173
00:12:45,056 --> 00:12:48,225
-Dynamic duo escaped.
-Pfft.

174
00:12:49,394 --> 00:12:52,688
Curses of Amenhotep!

175
00:12:53,940 --> 00:12:55,482
Your pharaoh speaks.

176
00:12:55,650 --> 00:13:00,112
Slaves and heIot swordsmen,
prepare for action.

177
00:13:00,280 --> 00:13:03,073
What's our next move, Batman?
Destroy this crooked Sphinx?

178
00:13:03,241 --> 00:13:04,616
No. I don't think so, Robin.

179
00:13:04,784 --> 00:13:08,453
It's better to Ieave it here
under police observation so they....

180
00:13:08,621 --> 00:13:11,373
Robin, Iook over there.

181
00:13:13,501 --> 00:13:15,127
HoIy masquerade.

182
00:13:15,295 --> 00:13:17,546
That's a pretty odd getup
for a waIk in the park.

183
00:13:17,714 --> 00:13:19,006
Odd indeed.

184
00:13:19,173 --> 00:13:21,258
It's a costume of the 14th dynasty.

185
00:13:21,426 --> 00:13:22,801
King Tut's dynasty.

186
00:13:22,969 --> 00:13:24,720
Wow, Iet's get her.

187
00:13:26,639 --> 00:13:28,307
BATMAN:
HaIt, you deIuded creature.

188
00:13:29,350 --> 00:13:32,561
We've got you. Escape is impossibIe.

189
00:13:38,609 --> 00:13:42,154
HoIy asp! A trick Egyptian snake.

190
00:13:43,323 --> 00:13:45,073
Look out, Robin.

191
00:14:06,137 --> 00:14:09,139
-Quick. Let's hotfoot it after them.
-No, Robin. Wait.

192
00:14:09,307 --> 00:14:11,933
-I think that's exactIy what they want.
-Why?

193
00:14:12,101 --> 00:14:14,353
An oId game
to draw us away from the reaI target.

194
00:14:14,520 --> 00:14:15,562
Of course.

195
00:14:15,730 --> 00:14:18,148
-The Egyptian exhibit at the museum.
-Right.

196
00:14:18,316 --> 00:14:23,653
The museum where Bruce Wayne
wiIl deal them a smaIl surprise.

197
00:14:28,868 --> 00:14:32,579
<i></i>N<i></i>A<i></i>R<i></i>RAT<i></i>O<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> A short while later</i>
<i>at the Gotham City museum.</i>

198
00:14:33,956 --> 00:14:36,124
You wilI note the twin embIems
of the two lands.

199
00:14:36,292 --> 00:14:38,794
The Iarge carneIian cobra here...

200
00:14:38,961 --> 00:14:41,338
...which is representative of Upper Egypt...

201
00:14:41,506 --> 00:14:46,301
...and the vuIture, which is the cuIt sign
of Lower Egypt and carved from Iapis lazuli.

202
00:14:46,469 --> 00:14:47,511
-Mr. Wayne?
-Yes?

203
00:14:47,678 --> 00:14:49,137
What is the vaIue of the crown?

204
00:14:49,305 --> 00:14:52,849
I don't reaIIy know
except that as a rare and historic art treasure...

205
00:14:53,017 --> 00:14:54,434
...it's undoubtedIy priceIess.

206
00:14:54,602 --> 00:14:58,105
Oh, you might inform your readers
that it's very welI-guarded at aIl times.

207
00:14:58,272 --> 00:14:59,731
[CHUCKLING]

208
00:14:59,899 --> 00:15:01,608
Now, Iadies and gentIemen...

209
00:15:01,776 --> 00:15:04,736
...in deference to the press here
which has deadIines to meet...

210
00:15:04,904 --> 00:15:09,950
...I'm sure, I propose now to offer to you
the piece de resistance...

211
00:15:10,118 --> 00:15:13,286
...the mummified remains of....

212
00:15:15,915 --> 00:15:18,417
AlI we know
about this particuIar gentIeman...

213
00:15:18,584 --> 00:15:22,796
...is that he was a king in the 14th dynasty
and reigned in 1 500 B.C.

214
00:15:22,964 --> 00:15:25,424
Now, if my arithmetic is correct...

215
00:15:25,591 --> 00:15:30,470
...that would mean that he's been dead
approximateIy 3500 years.

216
00:15:30,638 --> 00:15:32,931
And I beIieve it's safe to state...

217
00:15:33,099 --> 00:15:37,602
...that this particuIar pharaoh felIow
wiIl not rise again.

218
00:15:59,167 --> 00:16:01,751
It's alive. The Sphinx's prophecy was right.

219
00:16:01,919 --> 00:16:03,086
The king has risen again.

220
00:16:03,254 --> 00:16:06,465
Is there a doctor in the house?

221
00:16:07,258 --> 00:16:09,217
It is impossible. Isn't it, Bruce?

222
00:16:09,385 --> 00:16:11,303
It's fantastic, incredibIe.

223
00:16:11,471 --> 00:16:15,515
The preservation techniques,
what a man he must have been.

224
00:16:17,310 --> 00:16:19,060
The imagination boggIes.

225
00:16:19,228 --> 00:16:20,520
MAN:
The ambuIance is here.

226
00:16:20,688 --> 00:16:22,981
Make way for the stretcher bearers.

227
00:16:31,491 --> 00:16:33,408
I'II Ieave you to restore order here.

228
00:16:33,576 --> 00:16:36,495
I think I shouId go aIong to the hospitaI.

229
00:16:42,168 --> 00:16:44,669
Mr. Wayne, what happened?
Is he stilI aIive?

230
00:16:44,837 --> 00:16:46,338
What about the prophecy now?

231
00:16:46,506 --> 00:16:48,340
No comment.

232
00:16:51,010 --> 00:16:52,052
[KING TUT GROANING]

233
00:16:54,180 --> 00:16:56,264
Hey, he's coming to.

234
00:16:56,432 --> 00:16:59,267
I rather expected he would.
He may wanna teII us something.

235
00:16:59,435 --> 00:17:01,436
-What do you think he's saying?
-Shh. Shh.

236
00:17:02,605 --> 00:17:04,814
-Maybe this wiIl heIp.
-Shh.

237
00:17:05,483 --> 00:17:06,525
[CHOKING]

238
00:17:35,388 --> 00:17:37,597
AlI haiI your majesty.

239
00:17:37,765 --> 00:17:39,558
Phase two has worked perfectIy.

240
00:17:39,725 --> 00:17:41,059
NaturaIIy.

241
00:17:41,227 --> 00:17:44,062
It was foreseen in the scrolIs.

242
00:17:44,230 --> 00:17:47,566
To the paIace with this helot.

243
00:17:47,733 --> 00:17:51,111
-Your whim is our command, oh, Majesty.
-Heh, heh.

244
00:18:34,071 --> 00:18:35,113
[HUMMING]

245
00:18:43,205 --> 00:18:46,291
Nefertiti, you abandoned wench.

246
00:18:46,459 --> 00:18:50,962
How many times must I teIl you,
queens consume nectar and ambrosia.

247
00:18:51,130 --> 00:18:53,173
Not hot dogs.

248
00:18:53,341 --> 00:18:54,466
So I get hungry.

249
00:18:54,634 --> 00:18:57,927
Living on nothing but figs
and dates and pomegranate.

250
00:18:58,095 --> 00:19:01,473
-You wanna bite?
-Aah! Unclean.

251
00:19:02,600 --> 00:19:07,437
I must proclaim my reincarnation
to the faithfuI.

252
00:19:07,605 --> 00:19:09,898
Give me the teIephone.

253
00:19:17,448 --> 00:19:22,994
Osmond Abu, switcher of messages,
your pharaoh speaks.

254
00:19:23,162 --> 00:19:25,205
OSMOND [OVER PHONE]:
<i>What is your desire, great pharaoh?</i>

255
00:19:25,373 --> 00:19:30,835
Connect me to the voice box of the Sphinx
in Gotham Central Park, please.

256
00:19:31,003 --> 00:19:32,671
OSMOND:
<i>It shall be done, great pharaoh.</i>

257
00:19:32,838 --> 00:19:33,880
[CHUCKLES]

258
00:19:35,716 --> 00:19:41,012
Instruct the royaI charioteer,
to my paIace with haste.

259
00:19:42,431 --> 00:19:43,473
[HORN BLOWS]

260
00:19:45,142 --> 00:19:47,894
Home, toots, and step on it.

261
00:19:57,571 --> 00:19:58,613
[CHATTERING]

262
00:20:13,921 --> 00:20:14,963
[HORN WHIRS]

263
00:20:24,181 --> 00:20:26,683
NEFERTITI:
Now, hear this. Now, hear this.

264
00:20:26,851 --> 00:20:31,438
As it was written in the stars,
so it has come to pass.

265
00:20:31,731 --> 00:20:35,066
The great king of the NiIe
has risen from the sands of time...

266
00:20:35,234 --> 00:20:37,777
...to recIaim his Iost kingdom.

267
00:20:41,824 --> 00:20:46,202
NEFERTITI: <i>T</i><i>h</i><i>e</i> <i>n</i><i>e</i><i>xt</i> <i>v</i><i>o</i><i>i</i><i>c</i><i>e</i> <i>yo</i><i>u</i> <i>wi</i><i>l</i><i>l</i> <i>h</i><i>e</i><i>a</i><i>r</i>
<i>will be King Tut himself.</i>

268
00:20:49,081 --> 00:20:50,123
[CLEARS THROAT]

269
00:20:51,292 --> 00:20:56,004
LoyaI subjects and heIots, this is your king.

270
00:20:56,172 --> 00:20:59,924
KING TUT: <i>A</i><i>s</i> <i>o</i><i>u</i><i>r</i> <i>fi</i><i>rs</i><i>t</i> <i>fo</i><i>y</i><i>a</i><i>l</i> <i>a</i><i>c</i><i>t,</i>
<i>we have perpetrated the abduction...</i>

271
00:21:00,092 --> 00:21:03,595
<i>...of your millionaire philanthropist,</i>
<i>Bruce Wayne.</i>

272
00:21:04,013 --> 00:21:08,349
<i>He will be held prisoner</i>
<i>until our royal demands are met.</i>

273
00:21:08,517 --> 00:21:15,523
These demands wilI be made known to you
by our inscrutabIe Sphinx at a Iater date.

274
00:21:15,691 --> 00:21:20,987
KING TUT: <i>I</i><i>n</i> <i>t</i><i>h</i><i>e</i> <i>m</i><i>e</i><i>a</i><i>n</i><i>t</i><i>i</i><i>m</i><i>e</i><i>,</i>
<i>the police are warned not to interfere...</i>

275
00:21:21,155 --> 00:21:24,073
<i>...and this includes the dynamic duo.</i>

276
00:21:24,241 --> 00:21:28,870
<i>And pass my words on,</i>
<i>all ye within my reach.</i>

277
00:21:29,038 --> 00:21:31,873
Remember, Batman...

278
00:21:32,041 --> 00:21:37,253
...Bruce Wayne's Iife is in your hand.

279
00:21:46,889 --> 00:21:49,265
SCRIVENER: I wonder how much he's gonna ask
for Bruce Wayne.

280
00:21:49,433 --> 00:21:51,726
GRAND VIZIER:
I hear he's a rich milIionaire.

281
00:21:52,770 --> 00:21:56,856
You know, Harry,
that Tut's a kook but he's got brains.

282
00:21:57,024 --> 00:22:00,360
I wouIdn't be surprised
if he didn't wind up with the keenest gang...

283
00:22:00,528 --> 00:22:02,904
-...since oId Moe got the hot squad.
-Heh, heh.

284
00:22:06,408 --> 00:22:07,450
[BEEPING]

285
00:22:09,411 --> 00:22:10,495
Robin speaking.

286
00:22:10,663 --> 00:22:13,122
Uh, put Batman on, boy wonder.

287
00:22:13,290 --> 00:22:14,415
It's a crisis.

288
00:22:14,583 --> 00:22:16,543
Bruce Wayne has just been kidnapped.

289
00:22:16,710 --> 00:22:18,419
Bruce Wayne kidnapped? How? When?

290
00:22:18,587 --> 00:22:19,629
Only minutes ago.

291
00:22:19,797 --> 00:22:22,632
The King Tut resurrection
was just an eIaborate smokescreen...

292
00:22:22,800 --> 00:22:25,009
...to conceaI his crime.
Let me speak to Batman.

293
00:22:25,177 --> 00:22:27,554
Oh, I wish I couId,
but I don't know where he is.

294
00:22:27,721 --> 00:22:29,639
Soon as you hear from him,
there's not a minute to be Iost.

295
00:22:29,807 --> 00:22:32,475
Bruce Wayne
is one of our most prominent milIionaires.

296
00:22:32,643 --> 00:22:35,937
-So I've heard.
-This abductor may ask a king's ransom.

297
00:22:36,105 --> 00:22:37,564
We've got to move fast.

298
00:22:37,731 --> 00:22:40,233
I can't understand where Batman could be.

299
00:22:40,401 --> 00:22:42,610
Neither can I. Goodbye, commissioner.

300
00:22:42,778 --> 00:22:44,988
You've heard the caIamitous news,
master Robin?

301
00:22:45,155 --> 00:22:48,199
-Yes. Does Aunt Harriet know?
-On the 3 o'clock news.

302
00:22:48,367 --> 00:22:53,663
I'm afraid she's badly shaken
and I must admit, it's Ieft me a bit shaken too.

303
00:22:53,831 --> 00:22:55,290
Is there nothing to be done?

304
00:22:55,457 --> 00:22:56,749
Don't lose heart, Alfred.

305
00:22:56,917 --> 00:22:58,877
Batman is, welI, Batman.

306
00:22:59,044 --> 00:23:01,546
He'II get a message to us somehow.

307
00:24:02,524 --> 00:24:04,692
[NARRATOR READING ON-SCREEN TEXT]

308
00:25:13,971 --> 00:25:15,972
[EngIish - US - SDH]

