1
00:00:08,967 --> 00:00:12,637
NARRATOR:
<i>Gotham City, metropolis of wonders...</i>

2
00:00:12,846 --> 00:00:15,973
<i>...architectural queen of the world.</i>

3
00:00:16,183 --> 00:00:20,269
<i>A new jewel is about to be added</i>
<i>to her crown.</i>

4
00:00:20,479 --> 00:00:23,439
MAN: Distinguished guests,
ladies and gentIeman...

5
00:00:23,649 --> 00:00:27,235
...the mightiest bridge in the world
becomes a part of our city.

6
00:00:27,444 --> 00:00:29,570
[APPLAUSE]

7
00:00:29,780 --> 00:00:33,533
I hereby dedicate this engineering triumph...

8
00:00:33,742 --> 00:00:36,661
<i>...the Amerigo Columbus Bridge.</i>

9
00:00:37,621 --> 00:00:39,205
NARRATOR:
<i>And in Wayne Manor...</i>

10
00:00:39,414 --> 00:00:44,835
<i>...stately home of millionaire Bruce Wayne</i>
<i>and his youthful ward, Dick Grayson:</i>

11
00:00:45,045 --> 00:00:46,420
Bruce, quick. Come here, look.

12
00:00:47,756 --> 00:00:48,798
BRUCE:
What is it, Dick?

13
00:00:49,132 --> 00:00:51,551
In the crowd there, I just saw the Bookworm.

14
00:00:51,760 --> 00:00:53,886
-Are you sure?
-How couId I mistake him?

15
00:00:54,096 --> 00:00:57,056
Those crazy cIothes
that look Iike rare, old book bindings.

16
00:00:57,266 --> 00:01:00,142
And I'm pretty sure
he had on his trick eyegIasses too.

17
00:01:00,352 --> 00:01:02,853
The ones with the secret radio stuff buiIt in.

18
00:01:03,063 --> 00:01:05,439
Strange. What wouId a crook
like the Bookworm...

19
00:01:05,649 --> 00:01:07,275
...be doing at the dedication of a bridge?

20
00:01:07,484 --> 00:01:10,778
Let's watch.
Maybe he'II show his nasty nose again.

21
00:01:20,539 --> 00:01:22,331
Bookworm to Printer's Devil.

22
00:01:22,541 --> 00:01:24,500
<i>Bookworm to Printer's Devil.</i>

23
00:01:24,918 --> 00:01:27,378
Start chapter one.

24
00:01:27,588 --> 00:01:30,381
DEVIL [OVER RADIO]:
<i>Devil to Bookworm. Got you, boss.</i>

25
00:01:31,842 --> 00:01:33,342
[GRUNTS]

26
00:01:33,885 --> 00:01:35,094
HoIy homicide.

27
00:01:35,304 --> 00:01:37,722
-TelI me I'm having a nightmare.
BRUCE: Steady, Dick.

28
00:01:37,931 --> 00:01:42,643
-It happened, alI right.
-Commissioner Gordon kiIIed.

29
00:01:42,978 --> 00:01:46,063
This is one time we don't wait
for the Batphone.

30
00:01:46,273 --> 00:01:50,192
Oh! Aah! Oh, my dears. My dears.

31
00:01:50,402 --> 00:01:53,362
I was watching in the music room.
Did you see it too?

32
00:01:53,572 --> 00:01:54,947
We did, indeed, Aunt Harriet.

33
00:01:56,116 --> 00:01:59,619
I just hope
they were watching the television.

34
00:01:59,828 --> 00:02:01,037
They?

35
00:02:01,246 --> 00:02:03,122
Batman and Robin.

36
00:02:03,707 --> 00:02:06,167
Who eIse can save us now?

37
00:02:06,376 --> 00:02:09,503
Don't worry, Aunt Harriet.
I guess there's not much those two miss.

38
00:02:09,713 --> 00:02:13,966
Come on, Dick. Let's drive into the city
and pay our respects to a Iate, great man.

39
00:02:14,176 --> 00:02:15,968
Right, Bruce.

40
00:02:16,261 --> 00:02:18,304
It's the Ieast we can do.

41
00:02:18,513 --> 00:02:20,222
[SOBBING]

42
00:02:25,937 --> 00:02:28,356
I soIemnly swear
by my oath as a crime fighter...

43
00:02:28,565 --> 00:02:31,942
...that this outrage wilI not go unavenged.

44
00:02:32,319 --> 00:02:34,528
To the Batpoles.

45
00:04:38,361 --> 00:04:39,945
ROBIN:
Look. What'd I teIl you?

46
00:04:40,155 --> 00:04:41,947
Yes, it's the Bookworm aIl right.

47
00:04:42,157 --> 00:04:44,366
Oh, you pasty-faced deviI.

48
00:04:44,576 --> 00:04:47,745
If I couId onIy get me mitts around your neck,
I'd strangIe you!

49
00:04:47,954 --> 00:04:49,997
You bea-- You--

50
00:04:50,207 --> 00:04:52,917
PuII yourself together, Chief O'Hara.

51
00:04:53,418 --> 00:04:56,670
The mere fact that he was at the scene
is no proof of guilt.

52
00:04:56,880 --> 00:05:00,257
Outrage. Worst insult I've ever suffered
in my whoIe Iife.

53
00:05:00,467 --> 00:05:04,345
Miss WilIiams, please. What are you up to?

54
00:05:04,554 --> 00:05:06,263
GentIemen, back to your departments.

55
00:05:06,473 --> 00:05:10,434
-Saints alive.
-HoIy reincarnation.

56
00:05:12,771 --> 00:05:15,898
You weren't at the ceremony at the new bridge,
commissioner?

57
00:05:16,274 --> 00:05:17,733
I was not.

58
00:05:17,943 --> 00:05:22,863
Thanks to a monumentaIly stupid poIice officer
who gave me a ticket as I Ieft my Iuncheon.

59
00:05:23,073 --> 00:05:25,616
Me, arrested for overtime parking.

60
00:05:25,826 --> 00:05:27,827
[LAUGHING]

61
00:05:31,706 --> 00:05:33,207
GORDON:
Chief O'Hara.

62
00:05:33,625 --> 00:05:36,669
Are you anxious to be transferred
to the Department of Sanitation?

63
00:05:37,170 --> 00:05:38,796
No, sir.

64
00:05:39,005 --> 00:05:41,632
May I see that ticket, commissioner?

65
00:05:45,804 --> 00:05:51,517
Badge number 1 887.

66
00:05:51,726 --> 00:05:55,521
-Signed by A.S. ScarIet.
O'HARA: Wait.

67
00:05:56,064 --> 00:05:58,941
There is no badge 1 887 on the force.

68
00:05:59,317 --> 00:06:00,609
Of course not.

69
00:06:00,819 --> 00:06:04,238
A.S. ScarIet stands for <i>A</i> <i>S</i><i>t</i><i>u</i><i>d</i><i>y</i> <i>i</i><i>n</i> <i>S</i><i>c</i><i>a</i><i>rl</i><i>e</i><i>t</i><i>.</i>

70
00:06:04,447 --> 00:06:08,701
A SherIock HoImes adventure novel
first pubIished in 1 887.

71
00:06:08,910 --> 00:06:12,204
What a typicaI twisted Bookworm joke.

72
00:06:12,414 --> 00:06:14,206
Bookworm?

73
00:06:14,457 --> 00:06:17,543
Say, what, uh--? What is alI this?

74
00:06:17,752 --> 00:06:19,545
Why are you here, Batman?

75
00:06:19,880 --> 00:06:21,714
To investigate your murder, my friend.

76
00:06:22,591 --> 00:06:24,508
-What?
BATMAN: At the bridge this morning.

77
00:06:24,718 --> 00:06:26,802
There was an impostor
made up to Iook like you.

78
00:06:27,012 --> 00:06:29,680
He was apparently murdered by a rifIe bulIet
and felI into the river.

79
00:06:29,890 --> 00:06:33,851
Good grief. Then that so-calIed policeman
who pinched me--

80
00:06:34,060 --> 00:06:36,729
-Another phony.
-Right, Robin.

81
00:06:36,938 --> 00:06:38,856
A mere iIIusion of death, commissioner...

82
00:06:39,065 --> 00:06:42,067
...performed by an expert high diver
in Bookworm's pay.

83
00:06:42,986 --> 00:06:46,238
But why?
What on earth was the point of that charade?

84
00:06:46,448 --> 00:06:48,157
I don't know. It could have been mereIy--

85
00:06:48,366 --> 00:06:49,909
[DEVICE BEEPING]

86
00:06:52,871 --> 00:06:55,414
The bomb detector in the BatmobiIe,
it's flashing red.

87
00:06:55,624 --> 00:06:57,750
Quick, hit the radio-controI ejector button.

88
00:07:03,214 --> 00:07:05,549
HoIy expIosion.

89
00:07:12,515 --> 00:07:15,809
DEVIL [OVER RADIO]:
<i>Printer's Devil to Bookworm headquarters.</i>

90
00:07:16,811 --> 00:07:29,365
<i>Devil to Bookworm.</i>

91
00:07:29,991 --> 00:07:32,493
I read you, Printer's DeviI.

92
00:07:35,288 --> 00:07:38,332
DEVIL:
<i>Plot A, wash out.</i>

93
00:07:38,541 --> 00:07:41,669
<i>He got rid of the bomb with a tricky ejector.</i>

94
00:07:41,878 --> 00:07:43,212
What about pIot B?

95
00:07:43,421 --> 00:07:46,674
I don't know, Bookworm.
It's stiIl up in the air. It--

96
00:07:46,883 --> 00:07:49,176
Ah, here it comes now.

97
00:07:50,387 --> 00:07:52,888
What condition is it in? Is my pIot B IegibIe?

98
00:07:56,101 --> 00:07:57,977
PerfectIy.

99
00:07:59,938 --> 00:08:01,939
And here come the bat-eared boobs too.

100
00:08:02,148 --> 00:08:03,357
Return to headquarters.

101
00:08:03,566 --> 00:08:05,401
I read you. Over and out.

102
00:08:05,819 --> 00:08:07,611
Batman, Iook.

103
00:08:10,365 --> 00:08:11,949
Strange.

104
00:08:12,242 --> 00:08:15,244
A scorched, powder-burnt book cover.

105
00:08:15,453 --> 00:08:18,163
Seems to be made of asbestos.

106
00:08:19,833 --> 00:08:21,709
Excuse me, sir.

107
00:08:21,960 --> 00:08:23,460
Did you see where this came from?

108
00:08:23,670 --> 00:08:26,714
Out of the sky, Batman. Out of the sky.
Just after that expIosion.

109
00:08:27,007 --> 00:08:30,384
TypicaI of the Bookworm
to pIace his IethaI weapon inside a book.

110
00:08:30,593 --> 00:08:32,845
-Bookworm?
-Sorry, citizen, police business.

111
00:08:33,054 --> 00:08:34,430
You'd better move aIong.

112
00:08:34,639 --> 00:08:36,598
-Good Iuck, Batman.
-Thank you.

113
00:08:37,267 --> 00:08:38,767
You can stilI read the cover.

114
00:08:38,977 --> 00:08:43,022
<i>"For Whom the Bell Tolls</i>
by Ernest Hemmingway."

115
00:08:43,273 --> 00:08:45,816
It's the grimmest warning we've ever had.

116
00:08:46,026 --> 00:08:47,359
Warning?

117
00:08:47,569 --> 00:08:49,069
Hemmingway's titIe.

118
00:08:49,279 --> 00:08:51,613
It's from a poem by John Donne.

119
00:08:51,823 --> 00:08:55,951
"Do not ask for whom the beIl tolIs;

120
00:08:56,494 --> 00:08:59,121
it toIls for thee."

121
00:09:02,542 --> 00:09:05,169
No cIues here, Batman. No secret writing.

122
00:09:05,378 --> 00:09:09,882
It's just what it looks Iike,
a perfectIy ordinary asbestos book cover.

123
00:09:10,091 --> 00:09:15,345
Darn it alI. I'm stiIl positive there's some reason
why he chose this particular book.

124
00:09:15,555 --> 00:09:18,140
Maybe it was the only one he had
that was the right size.

125
00:09:18,349 --> 00:09:22,811
No, Robin. No. You see,
I know how this fiend's mind works.

126
00:09:23,021 --> 00:09:27,316
He prepares every super crime
like the frustrated noveIist he is.

127
00:09:27,525 --> 00:09:32,404
Every page, every chapter
is an integral part of one stolen pIot.

128
00:09:32,614 --> 00:09:36,366
Even that charade
at the bridge this morning.

129
00:09:36,910 --> 00:09:39,870
Great heavens. Of course. The bridge.

130
00:09:40,080 --> 00:09:41,205
What, Batman?

131
00:09:41,414 --> 00:09:45,793
<i></i>I<i></i>n<i> For Whom the Bell Tolls,</i>
the hero's mission is to blow up a bridge.

132
00:09:46,002 --> 00:09:48,754
HoIy detonator. Let's go.

133
00:09:49,964 --> 00:09:52,049
What is our super crime, boss?

134
00:09:52,258 --> 00:09:55,260
SiIence. Back to your books.
You'II be toId in good time.

135
00:09:55,470 --> 00:09:58,222
Oh, you're some cIever worm, Bookworm.

136
00:09:58,431 --> 00:10:00,224
Hmm. Oh.

137
00:10:00,433 --> 00:10:02,893
Oh, it's books, my sweet Lydia.

138
00:10:03,103 --> 00:10:05,437
Books. Books.

139
00:10:05,647 --> 00:10:08,565
That's the secret of my success.

140
00:10:09,359 --> 00:10:11,276
Books.

141
00:10:12,362 --> 00:10:15,030
Oh, I read them aII.

142
00:10:15,240 --> 00:10:17,324
I inherit the wisdom of the ages.

143
00:10:17,534 --> 00:10:22,788
Every pIot ever devised
is here inside my head.

144
00:10:22,997 --> 00:10:26,375
Oh, Bookworm, with a mind Iike yours...

145
00:10:26,584 --> 00:10:29,378
...I wonder why
you don't write your own bestseIIer.

146
00:10:29,587 --> 00:10:30,629
Shut up!

147
00:10:31,965 --> 00:10:33,423
Don't you dare say that to me.

148
00:10:33,633 --> 00:10:36,426
-But, Bookworm, I--
-You, you, you're taunting me, aren't you?

149
00:10:36,636 --> 00:10:37,886
-No, Bookworm.
-Yes, you are!

150
00:10:38,096 --> 00:10:40,889
-You're taunting and mocking me! And why?
-No! No!

151
00:10:41,099 --> 00:10:44,560
Why? Because I have no originaIity,
that's why!

152
00:10:44,769 --> 00:10:48,147
Why?
Because I'm only the master of stoIen pIots!

153
00:10:48,356 --> 00:10:49,773
WelI....

154
00:10:49,983 --> 00:10:53,485
-WelI, this, this wiII teach you a lesson!
-No!

155
00:11:18,720 --> 00:11:20,179
Hmm.

156
00:11:20,597 --> 00:11:21,889
[CHUCKLES]

157
00:11:22,265 --> 00:11:23,307
[CLEARS THROAT]

158
00:11:23,516 --> 00:11:24,850
[LAUGHS]

159
00:11:25,059 --> 00:11:26,185
Psst.

160
00:11:26,394 --> 00:11:28,020
What is he doing?

161
00:11:28,229 --> 00:11:29,980
With his fantastic mind...

162
00:11:30,190 --> 00:11:34,318
...he wiII read that entire book
in a matter of seconds.

163
00:11:53,421 --> 00:11:57,299
Now, ahem, what was I saying
before I was interrupted?

164
00:11:59,260 --> 00:12:00,594
<i></i>Aw<i></i>.<i></i>

165
00:12:00,803 --> 00:12:02,429
Dear me.

166
00:12:02,639 --> 00:12:06,141
What feebIe memories you have. Heh.

167
00:12:06,559 --> 00:12:10,729
However, shades of Shakespeare.

168
00:12:11,022 --> 00:12:14,483
Night has faIIen.

169
00:12:14,734 --> 00:12:17,486
It is time for us
to put a little twist into our pIot.

170
00:12:18,529 --> 00:12:20,489
FolIow me.

171
00:12:22,533 --> 00:12:25,118
-There's one thing I don't dig, Batman.
-Oh?

172
00:12:25,328 --> 00:12:27,537
Why does Bookworm wanna bIow up
the new bridge?

173
00:12:27,747 --> 00:12:30,874
-What's he gonna get out of it?
-Perhaps nothing but twisted revenge.

174
00:12:31,084 --> 00:12:34,336
Revenge against a welI-regulated society--

175
00:12:34,545 --> 00:12:36,797
Look. On that cIoud.

176
00:12:37,382 --> 00:12:39,466
ROBIN:
Wow, the Bat-SignaI.

177
00:12:39,676 --> 00:12:41,260
[PHONE BEEPING]

178
00:12:41,803 --> 00:12:42,928
BatmobiIe here.

179
00:12:43,137 --> 00:12:46,723
Oh, thank heavens, Boy Wonder.
A strange occurrence has just been reported.

180
00:12:46,933 --> 00:12:47,975
ROBIN:
<i>Where and what?</i>

181
00:12:48,184 --> 00:12:52,271
Back at that huge oId warehouse
on Harbor Avenue. It involves a bridge.

182
00:12:52,480 --> 00:12:55,232
Say no more, commissioner.
We're on our way.

183
00:12:55,441 --> 00:12:57,192
OId warehouse, Harbor Avenue.

184
00:12:57,402 --> 00:12:59,611
HoId tight. Emergency Bat-turn.

185
00:13:00,697 --> 00:13:02,781
[TIRES SCREECHING]

186
00:13:06,244 --> 00:13:09,246
Robin, aIert Parachute Pickup.

187
00:13:09,789 --> 00:13:10,831
Parachute Pickup.

188
00:13:34,397 --> 00:13:37,524
HoIy magic Iantern.
An immense picture of the new bridge.

189
00:13:37,734 --> 00:13:40,152
Yes, he's bIown it up alI right.

190
00:13:40,361 --> 00:13:42,696
That photograph of the bridge,
it's hugeIy enIarged.

191
00:13:42,905 --> 00:13:44,781
"BIown up" in photographer's lingo.

192
00:13:44,991 --> 00:13:48,243
Gosh, what a tricky pIay on words.

193
00:13:48,453 --> 00:13:50,495
-What's Bookworm's game?
-I don't know, Robin.

194
00:13:50,705 --> 00:13:53,790
The first thing is to find out
where that hidden photo projector is.

195
00:13:54,000 --> 00:13:56,626
Let's cIimb the waII
and get a bird's-eye view.

196
00:13:56,836 --> 00:13:59,463
WalI's too high to use the Bat-Ropes.

197
00:13:59,672 --> 00:14:01,340
Let's use the Batzooka.

198
00:14:04,385 --> 00:14:06,136
PRESSMAN [OVER RADIO]:
<i>Pressman to Bookworm...</i>

199
00:14:06,346 --> 00:14:08,347
<i>...they're getting ready to climb the wall.</i>

200
00:14:08,556 --> 00:14:12,392
Bookworm to Pressman,
return to bookmobiIe.

201
00:14:12,602 --> 00:14:14,227
Fire.

202
00:14:16,522 --> 00:14:17,898
HoIy buII's-eye.

203
00:14:18,107 --> 00:14:19,149
Let's go.

204
00:14:20,526 --> 00:14:25,030
I have the curious feeIing
this is aII some kind of literary plot.

205
00:14:25,239 --> 00:14:27,783
Let's outwit him, Batman.
Let's refuse to bite.

206
00:14:27,992 --> 00:14:30,369
-We must, Robin. It's the only way--
-Are you Batman?

207
00:14:30,578 --> 00:14:32,829
Oh. Oh, you must be because that's Robin.
Hi, Robin.

208
00:14:33,039 --> 00:14:36,625
BATMAN: Yes, citizen. But don't be aIarmed,
we're here on officiaI business.

209
00:14:36,834 --> 00:14:38,627
HoIy human fIies.

210
00:14:45,426 --> 00:14:46,968
This ought to be high enough.

211
00:14:47,178 --> 00:14:48,845
Look, down there in that other aIley.

212
00:14:49,055 --> 00:14:51,348
CarefuI, Robin. Both hands on the Bat-Rope.

213
00:14:51,557 --> 00:14:53,350
Sorry, Batman.

214
00:14:53,559 --> 00:14:56,561
You're right, though.
The source of this giant projected blowup...

215
00:14:56,771 --> 00:14:59,439
...seems to be coming from the roof
of that parked van.

216
00:14:59,649 --> 00:15:01,691
Reverse BatcIimb.

217
00:15:11,536 --> 00:15:14,204
Odd. An abandoned bookmobiIe.

218
00:15:14,414 --> 00:15:17,124
Could it realIy be one
from the Gotham City Public Library?

219
00:15:17,333 --> 00:15:18,458
I doubt it, Robin.

220
00:15:18,668 --> 00:15:21,420
Not with that photo projector
built into the roof.

221
00:15:21,629 --> 00:15:24,172
I doubt whether
it's entireIy abandoned either.

222
00:15:24,382 --> 00:15:27,968
You're right, Batman. There must be
someone inside to tend the projector.

223
00:15:28,177 --> 00:15:29,719
Let's give the worm a turn.

224
00:15:29,929 --> 00:15:32,848
We'II use the ultrasonic Bat-ray.

225
00:15:34,559 --> 00:15:36,601
Bookmobile right in the sights, Batman.

226
00:15:36,811 --> 00:15:40,522
-How many decibels wiIl we give him?
-TweIve thousand dBs ought to be sufficient.

227
00:15:40,731 --> 00:15:43,525
TweIve thousand decibeIs. Here we go.

228
00:15:43,734 --> 00:15:45,861
[BAT-RAY HUMMING LOUDLY]

229
00:15:46,070 --> 00:15:47,404
[MEN SHOUTING]

230
00:15:47,613 --> 00:15:48,780
BATMAN:
That's flushed them out.

231
00:15:48,990 --> 00:15:51,408
ROBIN:
Six of them, two of us. Odds in our favor.

232
00:15:57,748 --> 00:15:59,875
Iwo Jima's <i>A</i><i>rt</i> <i>o</i><i>f</i><i>t</i><i>h</i><i>e</i> <i>A</i><i>tt</i><i>a</i><i>c</i><i>k</i><i>.</i>

233
00:16:00,084 --> 00:16:03,128
Page 14, chapter six, paragraph two.

234
00:16:03,337 --> 00:16:04,421
Into action.

235
00:16:12,472 --> 00:16:14,556
Your glasses.

236
00:16:15,641 --> 00:16:19,269
Remember, never hit a man with gIasses.

237
00:16:22,607 --> 00:16:24,483
[ALL GRUNTING]

238
00:16:28,237 --> 00:16:30,864
Shakespeare, once more unto the breach.

239
00:16:52,428 --> 00:16:53,637
BOOKWORM:
MachiavelIi.

240
00:16:53,846 --> 00:16:56,598
Page three, Iine six.

241
00:16:56,807 --> 00:16:58,266
"Retreat!"

242
00:17:09,820 --> 00:17:12,155
The cowardIy worms. Where are they going?

243
00:17:20,122 --> 00:17:23,291
Where worms aIways go.

244
00:17:23,960 --> 00:17:25,168
Down into the earth.

245
00:17:25,378 --> 00:17:27,546
They've wiggIed through
that secret trapdoor.

246
00:17:27,755 --> 00:17:30,590
-DoubtIess they had it aIl prepared.
-But why, Batman?

247
00:17:30,800 --> 00:17:33,468
-Why Iure us here and then run?
-Good question, Robin.

248
00:17:33,678 --> 00:17:37,722
And one which has baffled us
from the very beginning of this case. Why?

249
00:17:38,766 --> 00:17:42,394
Perhaps there's a cIue to be found
in that bookmobiIe.

250
00:17:44,480 --> 00:17:46,481
[GRUNTING]

251
00:17:48,568 --> 00:17:51,653
HoIy CinderelIa. A beautifuI prisoner.

252
00:17:51,862 --> 00:17:53,530
Just Iike a fairy taIe.

253
00:17:53,739 --> 00:17:54,781
ROBIN:
Let's free her.

254
00:17:54,991 --> 00:17:58,034
No. Wait a minute, Robin.

255
00:17:59,870 --> 00:18:02,122
CriminaIs have tried this trick before.

256
00:18:02,331 --> 00:18:04,165
-Trick?
-Shh, shh.

257
00:18:05,751 --> 00:18:08,211
The girl couId be one of Bookworm's gang...

258
00:18:08,421 --> 00:18:12,257
...disguised as a prisoner
to give us faIse information.

259
00:18:13,217 --> 00:18:17,012
-Gosh, Batman, those Iook Iike honest eyes.
-Ah.

260
00:18:17,221 --> 00:18:20,640
Never trust the old chestnut
that crooks have beady IittIe eyes.

261
00:18:20,850 --> 00:18:22,434
It's faIse.

262
00:18:22,643 --> 00:18:25,979
I say we subject her to the most rigid test.

263
00:18:26,188 --> 00:18:28,898
You mean the Batcave?

264
00:18:29,108 --> 00:18:31,109
Precisely.

265
00:18:33,988 --> 00:18:35,822
[GRUNTING]

266
00:18:37,450 --> 00:18:40,952
I regret this, but it's a precaution I must take.

267
00:18:41,162 --> 00:18:43,705
I'm going to put you to sIeep
for a little whiIe.

268
00:18:43,914 --> 00:18:47,667
I give you my word
there'II be no harmfuI aftereffects.

269
00:18:53,507 --> 00:18:56,801
What is your name?

270
00:18:57,219 --> 00:18:59,387
Lydia Limpet.

271
00:18:59,597 --> 00:19:01,264
[BEEPING]

272
00:19:01,682 --> 00:19:04,142
BATMAN:
Do you know where you are?

273
00:19:04,352 --> 00:19:06,478
Of course.

274
00:19:06,687 --> 00:19:12,317
I'm in back of Bookworm's bookmobiIe.

275
00:19:12,943 --> 00:19:16,613
It rings true, Batman.
She doesn't even reaIize she's in the Batcave.

276
00:19:17,281 --> 00:19:19,658
Get set for the big one.

277
00:19:20,951 --> 00:19:23,495
What is Bookworm's plot?

278
00:19:23,996 --> 00:19:26,873
I don't know.

279
00:19:27,124 --> 00:19:30,752
He hasn't confided it to us.

280
00:19:32,421 --> 00:19:34,673
Darn it alI, another true answer.

281
00:19:35,216 --> 00:19:39,302
I onIy know he can't pulI it off...

282
00:19:39,512 --> 00:19:43,056
...tilI Batman and Robin have perished.

283
00:19:44,141 --> 00:19:45,392
Turn that machine off.

284
00:19:49,980 --> 00:19:51,356
What are we gonna do, Batman?

285
00:19:51,565 --> 00:19:53,858
Only one thing we can do...

286
00:19:54,068 --> 00:19:57,070
...and quickly, before that Bat-gas wears off.

287
00:19:58,364 --> 00:20:00,365
ROBIN:
She's waking up.

288
00:20:04,328 --> 00:20:05,745
Batman.

289
00:20:05,955 --> 00:20:07,288
Oh, thank heavens.

290
00:20:07,498 --> 00:20:10,834
You've rescued me from that sIimy fiend,
the Bookworm.

291
00:20:11,168 --> 00:20:13,128
Any idea what his pIot is, ma'am?

292
00:20:13,337 --> 00:20:16,047
Oh, yes. I overheard it alI.

293
00:20:16,257 --> 00:20:18,758
He pIans to strike at midnight.

294
00:20:18,968 --> 00:20:20,719
Where, ma'am?

295
00:20:21,178 --> 00:20:23,179
It's just awfuI.

296
00:20:23,389 --> 00:20:26,599
You know that perfect repIica
of Independence HalI?

297
00:20:26,809 --> 00:20:28,852
The one buiIt for the exposition?

298
00:20:29,228 --> 00:20:33,732
WelI, he plans to steal
the priceIess document there.

299
00:20:33,941 --> 00:20:35,275
The originaI...

300
00:20:35,484 --> 00:20:41,531
...United States Declaration of Independence.

301
00:20:43,325 --> 00:20:45,577
This poor girI's had a very bad time.

302
00:20:45,786 --> 00:20:48,288
We'd better caII an ambuIance
on the mobiIe Batphone.

303
00:20:48,914 --> 00:20:51,875
Batman, Robin, please don't Ieave me.

304
00:20:54,795 --> 00:20:57,672
-Another trap, of course.
-You can say that again.

305
00:20:57,882 --> 00:21:00,341
Another trap,
and I intend to walk right into it.

306
00:21:00,551 --> 00:21:01,760
What?

307
00:21:01,969 --> 00:21:05,138
It's the onIy way, Robin.
We know the Bookworm's waiting there.

308
00:21:05,347 --> 00:21:08,266
-With a shotgun Ioaded for bats.
-True.

309
00:21:08,476 --> 00:21:12,395
But he doesn't know that I know.
You stay here and guard that crooked girI.

310
00:21:12,605 --> 00:21:15,565
I'II calI Chief O'Hara en route
and have him send reinforcements.

311
00:21:15,775 --> 00:21:18,651
AmbuIance on the way, ma'am.

312
00:21:23,407 --> 00:21:25,784
Won't be Iong, Miss Limpet.

313
00:21:27,077 --> 00:21:28,495
WhiIe we wait...

314
00:21:28,996 --> 00:21:31,664
...why don't you untie me? Hmm?

315
00:21:31,874 --> 00:21:35,168
I don't know if I shouId.
I mean, you might be injured, Miss Limpet.

316
00:21:35,377 --> 00:21:38,713
Better not move
untiI trained personneI arrives.

317
00:21:39,673 --> 00:21:42,050
WelI, then, how about reading me a book?

318
00:21:42,426 --> 00:21:45,303
Say, that fourth one on the end of the sheIf.

319
00:21:45,513 --> 00:21:47,847
Sure thing, Miss Limpet.

320
00:21:48,224 --> 00:21:51,059
-This one?
-No, no, no, the next one.

321
00:21:54,855 --> 00:21:56,940
<i>"A Complete English History"?</i>

322
00:21:57,149 --> 00:22:00,318
This kind of stuff aIways puts me to sleep.

323
00:22:01,028 --> 00:22:03,238
[COUGHING]

324
00:22:17,044 --> 00:22:18,670
Limpet to Bookworm, urgent.

325
00:22:19,046 --> 00:22:22,257
<i>Do you read me? Am I legible?</i>

326
00:22:25,761 --> 00:22:28,471
<i>Repeat, am I legible?</i>

327
00:22:28,681 --> 00:22:30,139
Ahem. I read you.

328
00:22:30,349 --> 00:22:33,268
Warning, Batman knows it's a trap.

329
00:22:33,811 --> 00:22:35,144
How couId he?

330
00:22:35,479 --> 00:22:39,941
I don't know.
But get this, the Boy Wonder knows my name.

331
00:22:40,150 --> 00:22:41,860
He's been caIling me Miss Limpet.

332
00:22:42,778 --> 00:22:44,946
<i>They must've tumbled somehow.</i>

333
00:22:45,155 --> 00:22:46,656
Do you stilI have Boy Wonder?

334
00:22:47,157 --> 00:22:48,741
Oh, yes.

335
00:22:48,951 --> 00:22:52,996
He got a whiff of your sleepy-bye book,
<i>English History.</i>

336
00:22:53,205 --> 00:22:55,707
Stay right there.
I'II be right over to pick you up.

337
00:22:55,916 --> 00:22:57,750
<i>Over and out.</i>

338
00:23:02,965 --> 00:23:07,343
NARRATOR:
<i>A strange destination for a dreadful fate.</i>

339
00:23:07,553 --> 00:23:09,929
<i>The Wayne Memorial Clock Tower...</i>

340
00:23:10,139 --> 00:23:14,893
<i>...presented to Gotham City</i>
<i>in memory of Bruce Wayne's father.</i>

341
00:23:15,102 --> 00:23:16,644
BOOKWORM:
Time.

342
00:23:16,854 --> 00:23:21,566
Time which delivers us aII to the worms
in the end.

343
00:23:21,775 --> 00:23:22,984
[SPEAKS IN FRENCH]

344
00:23:23,193 --> 00:23:24,652
Huh?

345
00:23:25,070 --> 00:23:26,946
-What time is it?
-Oh!

346
00:23:27,156 --> 00:23:30,241
One minute to midnight, Bookworm.

347
00:23:30,451 --> 00:23:34,996
Ah. Sixty tiny seconds. Oh.

348
00:23:35,205 --> 00:23:38,583
FareweII, Boy Wonder. Adieu, Robin.

349
00:23:38,792 --> 00:23:43,671
Oh, this is the Iast time
that you wilI meddIe in affairs of moment.

350
00:23:43,881 --> 00:23:46,716
Oh, I tried to warn you.

351
00:23:46,926 --> 00:23:50,720
"Do not ask for whom this beII tolIs;

352
00:23:50,930 --> 00:23:53,222
it toIls for thee."

353
00:23:53,432 --> 00:23:54,807
[POPS]

354
00:24:04,818 --> 00:24:07,028
HoIy headache.

355
00:24:07,404 --> 00:24:09,572
[NARRATOR READING
ON-SCREEN TEXT]

356
00:25:11,802 --> 00:25:13,803
[EngIish - US - SDH]

