1
00:00:10,385 --> 00:00:14,764
NARRATOR: <i>S</i><i>o</i> <i>fa</i><i>r</i> <i>w</i><i>e</i> <i>h</i><i>a</i><i>v</i><i>e</i> <i>s</i><i>e</i><i>e</i><i>n</i><i>,</i>
<i>at the dedication of a new bridge...</i>

2
00:00:15,307 --> 00:00:17,016
<i>...murder.</i>

3
00:00:17,518 --> 00:00:23,773
<i>And spotted in the crowd,</i>
<i>that sinister crook, The Bookworm.</i>

4
00:00:25,108 --> 00:00:27,193
<i>Great Scott.</i>

5
00:00:27,986 --> 00:00:33,199
<i>A Bookworm ploy,</i>
<i>a ruse to divert the dynamic duo...</i>

6
00:00:33,951 --> 00:00:37,411
<i>...while a bomb was placed in the Batmobile.</i>

7
00:00:37,996 --> 00:00:40,373
<i>Bomb detected...</i>

8
00:00:41,500 --> 00:00:43,626
<i>...ejected.</i>

9
00:00:44,294 --> 00:00:48,130
<i>A clue. He was going to blow up the bridge.</i>

10
00:00:48,799 --> 00:00:54,136
<i>He did.</i>
<i>He blew it up into a giant photograph.</i>

11
00:00:54,846 --> 00:00:58,558
<i>Like moths, our heroes followed the light...</i>

12
00:00:59,184 --> 00:01:01,769
<i>...into a Bat trap.</i>

13
00:01:02,479 --> 00:01:05,022
<i>Was this girl really a prisoner?</i>

14
00:01:05,232 --> 00:01:07,191
<i>Was it a trick?</i>

15
00:01:07,901 --> 00:01:11,862
<i>One way to find out:</i>
<i>Put her gently to sleep...</i>

16
00:01:12,656 --> 00:01:15,324
<i>...spirit her to the Batcave, test her.</i>

17
00:01:17,452 --> 00:01:22,248
<i>Counterplot, pretend we fall for her game.</i>

18
00:01:23,000 --> 00:01:26,377
<i>The tricky girl turned the tables.</i>

19
00:01:27,045 --> 00:01:30,047
<i>And The Bookworm knew</i>
<i>just what to do with him:</i>

20
00:01:30,257 --> 00:01:33,759
<i>Bind him to the clapper of a giant bell.</i>

21
00:01:34,511 --> 00:01:37,680
<i>Do not ask for whom this bell tolls.</i>

22
00:01:37,889 --> 00:01:40,057
<i>It tolls for Robin.</i>

23
00:01:40,267 --> 00:01:45,730
<i>In just one minute,</i>
<i>the stroke of midnight doom.</i>

24
00:02:53,298 --> 00:02:54,715
NARRATOR:
<i>A few minutes earlier...</i>

25
00:02:54,925 --> 00:02:59,178
<i>...even as Bookworm binds Robin</i>
<i>to the clapper of the giant bell...</i>

26
00:02:59,388 --> 00:03:03,724
<i>...Batman races across Gotham City</i>
<i>in the opposite direction...</i>

27
00:03:03,934 --> 00:03:06,769
<i>...hot on a trail that's fatally false.</i>

28
00:03:13,902 --> 00:03:17,613
-What's up, Chief O'Hara?
-We searched that halI, ceIIar to weather vane.

29
00:03:17,823 --> 00:03:20,199
-Not a trace of The Bookworm.
-But how can that be?

30
00:03:20,409 --> 00:03:22,159
Oh, worse news too, Batman.

31
00:03:22,369 --> 00:03:25,329
You know that aIleyway where you said
we'd find the Boy Wonder...

32
00:03:25,539 --> 00:03:28,290
-...guarding Bookworm's moIl?
-Yes, yes, yes.

33
00:03:29,292 --> 00:03:32,253
-Don't telI me.
-You guessed it.

34
00:03:32,546 --> 00:03:33,629
Great heavens.

35
00:03:33,839 --> 00:03:37,174
I'd better try to contact Robin instantIy
on the utility belt waveIength.

36
00:03:37,384 --> 00:03:38,926
Robin?

37
00:03:39,261 --> 00:03:41,721
Robin, do you receive me?

38
00:03:41,930 --> 00:03:44,348
Robin? Over.

39
00:03:45,976 --> 00:03:48,185
The tricky devils.

40
00:03:48,395 --> 00:03:50,521
They've turned the tabIes and caught Robin.

41
00:03:50,731 --> 00:03:52,898
I'II calI headquarters. Throw out the dragnet.

42
00:03:53,108 --> 00:03:55,234
No, wait a minute, Chief O'Hara.

43
00:03:55,444 --> 00:03:58,487
Let me turn my memory back.

44
00:04:01,992 --> 00:04:06,454
"He strikes at midnight," she said.

45
00:04:06,663 --> 00:04:08,831
But we know The Bookworm
has changed his pIan.

46
00:04:09,040 --> 00:04:10,124
Don't interrupt.

47
00:04:10,333 --> 00:04:14,211
I'm trying to fathom the subconscious
of a deadIy criminal.

48
00:04:15,672 --> 00:04:19,258
He strikes at midnight.

49
00:04:21,970 --> 00:04:25,222
A metaphor. Suggests a clock.

50
00:04:25,974 --> 00:04:27,558
A cIock caIIed "he"?

51
00:04:27,768 --> 00:04:29,560
Of course.

52
00:04:29,770 --> 00:04:34,023
And there's onIy one cIock in Gotham City
that is caIIed "he."

53
00:04:35,192 --> 00:04:36,776
Saints alive.

54
00:04:36,985 --> 00:04:40,029
Big Benjamin
in the Wayne MemoriaI Clock Tower.

55
00:04:40,614 --> 00:04:42,656
And it fits in with the plan.

56
00:04:42,866 --> 00:04:46,744
Do not ask for whom the beII toIls.
It toIIs for thee....

57
00:04:47,370 --> 00:04:50,164
-You mean....
-Exactly.

58
00:04:50,373 --> 00:04:52,583
And if my surmise is correct...

59
00:04:52,793 --> 00:04:55,836
...the ghastIy fate
that Bookworm pIanned for me...

60
00:04:56,046 --> 00:04:57,421
...he has twisted to Robin.

61
00:04:57,631 --> 00:05:02,051
Chief O'Hara, we haven't
one Big Benjamin second to Iose.

62
00:05:30,497 --> 00:05:32,873
Mere seconds before he strikes.

63
00:05:33,083 --> 00:05:35,501
I'II shoot out the works.

64
00:05:37,420 --> 00:05:39,755
[GUNSHOTS]

65
00:05:41,216 --> 00:05:44,051
Argh. Didn't even dent it.

66
00:05:44,261 --> 00:05:46,053
No time for a Bat-cIimb.

67
00:05:46,263 --> 00:05:48,556
We have one Iast desperate chance.

68
00:05:48,765 --> 00:05:50,474
HeIp me set up the Bat-zooka.

69
00:05:54,396 --> 00:05:56,897
The Iightning rod on top.

70
00:05:57,107 --> 00:05:58,607
Fire!

71
00:06:02,904 --> 00:06:04,905
BuII's-eye.

72
00:06:05,657 --> 00:06:08,826
Second shot. The hands of that cIock.

73
00:06:09,035 --> 00:06:10,369
Fire!

74
00:06:15,876 --> 00:06:17,835
Mother Machree, done it again.

75
00:06:18,044 --> 00:06:21,547
QuickIy. Now to get the ends
of these two conductive Iines.

76
00:06:30,307 --> 00:06:31,599
What are you doing, Batman?

77
00:06:31,808 --> 00:06:33,934
Attaching lines
to the nucIear power source...

78
00:06:34,144 --> 00:06:36,020
...both Iines to the positive terminaI.

79
00:06:36,229 --> 00:06:41,150
As you may recalI from schooI,
like charges of eIectricity repeI each other.

80
00:06:44,237 --> 00:06:47,656
Now to rev up the power turbines.

81
00:06:47,866 --> 00:06:50,075
I stiII don't get it, Batman.

82
00:06:50,285 --> 00:06:53,996
Pray. Pray, Chief O'Hara...

83
00:06:54,247 --> 00:06:57,791
...that the cIapper and the beIl
wiIl be positively charged...

84
00:06:58,001 --> 00:07:00,461
...and thus repeI each other!

85
00:07:00,670 --> 00:07:02,755
I hope so, Batman. I hope so.

86
00:07:18,104 --> 00:07:20,481
[BIRD CHIRPING]

87
00:07:22,025 --> 00:07:26,111
Funny, aIl I hear is a nightingale.

88
00:07:30,367 --> 00:07:32,368
[SCREAMING]

89
00:07:36,081 --> 00:07:37,957
InconceivabIe but true.

90
00:07:38,166 --> 00:07:42,002
The precocious pest has escaped us.

91
00:07:42,212 --> 00:07:43,420
But how couId he, Bookworm?

92
00:07:43,630 --> 00:07:45,673
HENCHMEN:
How couId he?

93
00:07:45,882 --> 00:07:50,386
I cannot conceive, but from <i>G</i><i>i</i><i>l</i> <i>B</i><i>l</i><i>a</i><i>s</i>
transIated by Tobias SmoIlett...

94
00:07:50,595 --> 00:07:53,347
...Book 1 0, chapter three, quote:

95
00:07:53,556 --> 00:07:57,309
"Facts are stubborn things," unquote.

96
00:07:57,519 --> 00:08:02,731
Now, the fact is that our bats
have fIown the beIfry...

97
00:08:02,941 --> 00:08:05,567
...unaccountably stilI squeaking.

98
00:08:05,777 --> 00:08:09,279
Gee, and us with
our super-crime not pulIed yet.

99
00:08:09,489 --> 00:08:10,531
[HENCHMEN SIGH]

100
00:08:10,740 --> 00:08:12,199
Ah! Ah.

101
00:08:14,452 --> 00:08:16,286
Ah.

102
00:08:17,414 --> 00:08:21,875
Ah. Do not fret, my sweet Lydia.
Oh, do not fret.

103
00:08:22,085 --> 00:08:25,879
My brain-drenched mind has done it again.

104
00:08:26,089 --> 00:08:28,716
Oh! A most deIicious Bat trap.

105
00:08:28,925 --> 00:08:31,135
[HENCHMEN TITTER]

106
00:08:31,344 --> 00:08:33,762
Mwah. Oh!

107
00:08:35,974 --> 00:08:40,310
<i></i>N<i></i>A<i></i>R<i></i>RAT<i></i>O<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> And in Wayne Manor,</i>
<i>stately home of millionaire Bruce Wayne...</i>

108
00:08:40,520 --> 00:08:42,896
<i>...and his youthful ward, Dick Grayson...</i>

109
00:08:43,106 --> 00:08:47,192
<i>...the plot is about to take</i>
<i>a strange new twist.</i>

110
00:08:47,402 --> 00:08:48,444
[CLEARS THROAT]

111
00:08:48,653 --> 00:08:49,862
Oh, what is it, AIfred?

112
00:08:50,071 --> 00:08:52,489
It's a gentIeman from
the bookmobiIe service, madam.

113
00:08:52,699 --> 00:08:55,868
Oh, how nice. Bring him in.

114
00:08:56,077 --> 00:08:57,786
This way, sir.

115
00:09:01,708 --> 00:09:03,500
How do you do?

116
00:09:03,710 --> 00:09:08,839
What do you recommend this week,
something for reading before going to sleep?

117
00:09:09,049 --> 00:09:13,635
Oh, weII, I beIieve that you wiII find this voIume
extremely effective, Mrs. Cooper.

118
00:09:13,845 --> 00:09:15,304
Oh.

119
00:09:17,098 --> 00:09:20,768
<i>"Congressional Record, </i>M<i></i>a<i></i>r<i></i>c<i></i>h<i> </i>1<i></i>9<i></i>1<i></i>9'<i></i>'<i></i>?<i></i>

120
00:09:20,977 --> 00:09:23,645
Oh, it's the iIIustrations, Mrs. Cooper.

121
00:09:23,855 --> 00:09:25,522
They are so piquant.

122
00:09:25,732 --> 00:09:28,942
-Oh, you don't say.
-Mm.

123
00:09:29,152 --> 00:09:31,653
Look, AIfred.

124
00:09:36,993 --> 00:09:38,327
[BOOKWORM CHUCKLES]

125
00:09:43,291 --> 00:09:47,294
Hmm.

126
00:09:47,504 --> 00:09:49,004
Oh, weII.

127
00:09:58,681 --> 00:10:00,349
Subject found to be member of--

128
00:10:00,558 --> 00:10:02,392
[PHONE BEEPS]

129
00:10:02,602 --> 00:10:05,854
-Yes, commissioner?
-Bookworm has struck again, Batman, brazenIy.

130
00:10:06,064 --> 00:10:08,482
-£W<i>h</i><i>e</i><i>r</i><i>e</i><i>?</i>
-The mansion of milIionaire Bruce Wayne.

131
00:10:08,691 --> 00:10:12,861
He stoIe a single volume,
a priceIess first-edition cookbook.

132
00:10:13,530 --> 00:10:16,824
-Was anyone in the Wayne household hurt?
-Fortunately, no one.

133
00:10:17,033 --> 00:10:18,075
Goodbye, commissioner.

134
00:10:18,284 --> 00:10:20,744
I'II be at Wayne Manor
faster than anyone can imagine.

135
00:10:20,954 --> 00:10:23,330
-Batman, wait, that's not the only thing.
<i>-What else?</i>

136
00:10:23,540 --> 00:10:28,210
In the middle of the street, at Cedar and 5th,
there's been a sudden monstrous apparition.

137
00:10:28,545 --> 00:10:31,547
<i>The biggest cookbook anyone ever saw.</i>

138
00:10:31,923 --> 00:10:33,674
Goodbye, commissioner.

139
00:10:33,883 --> 00:10:36,343
-Aunt Harriet and Alfred?
-They're not hurt, he said.

140
00:10:36,553 --> 00:10:39,346
Our duty is to the pubIic. Let's go.

141
00:10:44,185 --> 00:10:46,061
What a twisted skein of events.

142
00:10:46,521 --> 00:10:51,525
TypicaI of the frustrated author
Bookworm is, over-plotting.

143
00:10:51,734 --> 00:10:56,530
Either the robbery or a giant cookbook
would've attracted our attention.

144
00:10:56,739 --> 00:11:00,534
FooIish amateur has to try both.

145
00:11:00,743 --> 00:11:02,744
[CROWD CHATTERING]

146
00:11:17,802 --> 00:11:20,095
HoIy tome!

147
00:11:20,597 --> 00:11:22,556
Back, everybody.

148
00:11:23,600 --> 00:11:24,975
Back, back.

149
00:11:25,185 --> 00:11:28,770
Take cover in the side streets.
Take cover in the side streets.

150
00:11:29,689 --> 00:11:32,816
The recipes in this book couId be expIosive.

151
00:11:33,026 --> 00:11:34,860
Stay back.

152
00:11:35,612 --> 00:11:38,864
-I bet it's hoIlow inside, Batman.
-We'II soon find out.

153
00:11:39,073 --> 00:11:42,201
-Let's probe it with our high-energy radar.
-Roger.

154
00:11:47,790 --> 00:11:49,958
ROBIN: HolIow, aII right.
BATMAN: Yes.

155
00:11:50,168 --> 00:11:53,587
Judging from the rate of reflection,
the cover contains high-tensiIe steeI.

156
00:11:53,796 --> 00:11:56,673
-Let's open it up, Batman.
-Right you are.

157
00:11:56,966 --> 00:11:59,927
If the cover contains steeI,
we can do it from a safe distance...

158
00:12:00,136 --> 00:12:02,971
-...using the super-powered Bat-magnet.
-Great.

159
00:12:06,809 --> 00:12:08,936
-I'II work the power suppIy.
BATMAN: Roger.

160
00:12:09,145 --> 00:12:11,146
[MAGNET HUMMING]

161
00:12:13,024 --> 00:12:15,317
Bat-pulI 1 200 pounds.

162
00:12:18,112 --> 00:12:19,821
BATMAN:
Make it a ton.

163
00:12:32,877 --> 00:12:36,255
Oh, poor puny IittIe bat-brains.

164
00:12:36,464 --> 00:12:38,382
I bet they think they opened that book.

165
00:12:38,967 --> 00:12:40,300
But wiII they go in?

166
00:12:40,510 --> 00:12:42,261
Of course they'lI go in.

167
00:12:42,470 --> 00:12:44,888
In the words of the poet:

168
00:12:45,265 --> 00:12:49,268
"Curiosity kiIled the bat." Heh.

169
00:13:02,365 --> 00:13:04,199
Ordinary paper.

170
00:13:04,867 --> 00:13:06,660
It must cover the hoIIowed-out part.

171
00:13:06,869 --> 00:13:08,954
I wonder what's on the menu inside.

172
00:13:09,163 --> 00:13:11,039
Only one way to find out, Robin.

173
00:13:11,249 --> 00:13:13,250
Let's take a bite.

174
00:13:43,740 --> 00:13:44,906
SmeIIs Iike soup.

175
00:13:45,992 --> 00:13:47,242
Darn good soup.

176
00:13:47,744 --> 00:13:49,077
Right you are.

177
00:13:49,287 --> 00:13:50,704
Bat soup.

178
00:13:50,913 --> 00:13:53,248
And in you go.

179
00:13:57,462 --> 00:13:59,713
No! HoIy stew pot!

180
00:13:59,922 --> 00:14:02,299
BOOKWORM [OVER PA]:
<i>Bookworm to Batman.</i>

181
00:14:02,508 --> 00:14:06,094
He's got this pIace wired.
I'II bet he's watching and Iistening too.

182
00:14:06,304 --> 00:14:07,721
WelI, of course I'm Iistening.

183
00:14:07,930 --> 00:14:10,349
BATMAN [OVER RADIO]:
<i>Bookworm, what are you up to?</i>

184
00:14:10,558 --> 00:14:12,809
It's a curious oId recipe I discovered...

185
00:14:13,019 --> 00:14:17,481
<i></i>.<i></i>.<i></i>.<i></i>i<i></i>n<i> </i>th<i></i>e<i> Alchemist Cookbook,</i>
Vienna, dated 1 534.

186
00:14:17,690 --> 00:14:20,901
<i>How to steam a bat.</i>

187
00:14:21,277 --> 00:14:22,736
I think he means it.

188
00:14:22,945 --> 00:14:25,280
BOOKWORM:
<i>Of course I mean it, Boy Wonder.</i>

189
00:14:25,490 --> 00:14:31,411
<i>Watch now while I turn up</i>
<i>my radio-controlled double boiler.</i>

190
00:14:34,957 --> 00:14:37,167
DoubIe for Dynamic Duo.

191
00:14:37,377 --> 00:14:40,754
<i>Cook well, my bat-eared friends.</i>
<i>While you are stewing down...</i>

192
00:14:40,963 --> 00:14:45,342
<i>...I shall be pulling off the crime of the century</i>
<i>with the aid of your Batmobile.</i>

193
00:14:45,802 --> 00:14:48,261
Happy juices. Heh.

194
00:14:48,471 --> 00:14:50,514
Quick, Iet's fly.

195
00:14:52,225 --> 00:14:55,852
Batman to Gotham City Police,
Batman to Gotham City Police.

196
00:14:56,062 --> 00:14:57,604
Red aIert, red alert.

197
00:14:57,814 --> 00:15:01,441
We are trapped inside a cookbook
at 5th and Cedar.

198
00:15:01,651 --> 00:15:04,653
Red aIert. Do you receive me? Over.

199
00:15:04,862 --> 00:15:06,738
No answer.

200
00:15:07,782 --> 00:15:10,784
These high-tensile steeI waIIs,
they're cutting down our transmission.

201
00:15:10,993 --> 00:15:13,954
-I'II get out my Iaser-beam cutting torch.
-Don't, Robin. No, no.

202
00:15:14,163 --> 00:15:17,541
It wouId superheat the steam
and boil us in a split second.

203
00:15:17,750 --> 00:15:19,626
HoIy pressure cooker.

204
00:15:19,836 --> 00:15:22,838
Only way to crack this
would be the Bat Beam in the BatmobiIe...

205
00:15:23,047 --> 00:15:25,048
...and Bookworm has it.

206
00:15:25,258 --> 00:15:26,883
We even Ieft the engine running.

207
00:15:27,093 --> 00:15:29,094
[BOTH COUGHING]

208
00:15:32,890 --> 00:15:36,893
O'HARA:
With alI your might and main, men, let's go.

209
00:15:40,523 --> 00:15:42,524
[BOTH COUGHING]

210
00:15:46,654 --> 00:15:47,779
[GASPS]

211
00:15:48,865 --> 00:15:50,365
They'lI never get to us in time.

212
00:15:50,575 --> 00:15:51,908
There's only one hope.

213
00:15:52,994 --> 00:15:56,329
OFFICER 1 : Get them under there. Come on.
OFFICER 2: Yeah, we're on it.

214
00:15:56,539 --> 00:15:58,290
-WelI?
-We're getting nowhere, chief.

215
00:15:58,499 --> 00:16:00,500
Oh, harder, feIlas, harder.

216
00:16:00,710 --> 00:16:02,335
Oh, give me that sIedge, here.

217
00:16:02,545 --> 00:16:05,005
Sounds Iike steam in there.

218
00:16:06,757 --> 00:16:07,799
DreadfuI.

219
00:16:08,009 --> 00:16:12,053
That fine pair of crime fighters
boiled in the entraiIs of a monster cookbook.

220
00:16:12,263 --> 00:16:15,765
Who could imagine a more tragic end?

221
00:16:16,684 --> 00:16:17,893
Batman to Batcave.

222
00:16:18,102 --> 00:16:20,353
What's the use, Batman?

223
00:16:20,563 --> 00:16:23,148
It's just possibIe
our own super-sensitive antenna...

224
00:16:23,357 --> 00:16:26,234
...may pick up the signaI
where the poIice receivers could not.

225
00:16:26,444 --> 00:16:30,030
-Do you think AIfred's there?
-He's a creature of weII-discipIined habits.

226
00:16:30,239 --> 00:16:32,782
It's his reguIar time
for dusting the Atomic PiIe.

227
00:16:32,992 --> 00:16:36,912
[OVER RADIO] <i>B</i><i>a</i><i>t</i><i>m</i><i>a</i><i>n</i> <i>t</i><i>o</i> <i>A</i><i>l</i><i>fre</i><i>d</i><i>,</i>
<i>Batman to Alfred. This is an emergency.</i>

228
00:16:42,251 --> 00:16:43,919
Might I be of some assistance, sir?

229
00:16:46,088 --> 00:16:50,217
Quick, AIfred, pIug me into the voice-actuated
circuit of the master anticrime computer.

230
00:16:50,426 --> 00:16:52,219
CertainIy, sir. At once, sir.

231
00:16:52,428 --> 00:16:54,429
[MUTTERING]

232
00:17:04,690 --> 00:17:09,903
Bookworm to bookmobiIe,
Bookworm to bookmobiIe. Do you read me?

233
00:17:10,112 --> 00:17:12,155
DEVIL [OVER RADIO]:
<i>Devil to Bookworm. I read you.</i>

234
00:17:12,365 --> 00:17:16,159
Rendezvous,
the rear of the Morganbilt Library.

235
00:17:16,369 --> 00:17:18,453
Over and out.

236
00:17:20,706 --> 00:17:23,917
The MorganbiIt Library?
But that's uncrackabIe.

237
00:17:24,126 --> 00:17:26,628
It's defied every burgIar in the country.

238
00:17:27,004 --> 00:17:29,172
Yes, yes, my sweet Lydia, yes...

239
00:17:29,382 --> 00:17:32,467
...but they did not have the use
of the Bat Beam.

240
00:17:32,677 --> 00:17:38,181
Plans and Views, foIio 369,
operate cross beam.

241
00:17:47,650 --> 00:17:48,942
I'm weakening, Batman.

242
00:17:49,151 --> 00:17:50,193
HoId on, Robin.

243
00:17:50,403 --> 00:17:51,778
[ROBIN COUGHS]

244
00:17:52,863 --> 00:17:55,240
HoId on, hold on.
I'm getting the answer I expected.

245
00:17:55,449 --> 00:17:56,491
Answer?

246
00:17:56,701 --> 00:17:59,286
About the source of this steam...

247
00:17:59,495 --> 00:18:03,707
...Plans and Views, cut out,
feedback, circuit three, operate.

248
00:18:08,462 --> 00:18:11,881
-Who's the best safecracker in our files?
-Uh, the RiddIer.

249
00:18:12,091 --> 00:18:15,051
Send a heIicopter to the State Penitentiary.
Have him brought here.

250
00:18:15,261 --> 00:18:17,053
-Yes, sir.
SERGEANT: AII right, everybody down.

251
00:18:17,263 --> 00:18:18,346
Come on, get them down.

252
00:18:21,017 --> 00:18:22,058
Ready?

253
00:18:22,268 --> 00:18:24,102
Fire!

254
00:18:26,897 --> 00:18:29,983
ALL:
Yeah!

255
00:18:30,192 --> 00:18:32,193
[ALL COUGHING]

256
00:18:34,614 --> 00:18:36,448
Good grief.

257
00:18:36,657 --> 00:18:38,408
We're too Iate.

258
00:18:38,618 --> 00:18:39,826
Gone.

259
00:18:40,036 --> 00:18:41,953
Consumed, I fear.

260
00:18:42,163 --> 00:18:46,541
TotaIIy consumed
in this diaboIicaI heII's kitchen.

261
00:18:51,380 --> 00:18:56,968
<i></i>N<i></i>A<i></i>R<i></i>RAT<i></i>O<i></i>R<i></i>:<i> The Morganbilt Library,</i>
<i>unparalleled repository of literary treasures.</i>

262
00:18:57,178 --> 00:19:03,016
<i>In an alley at the rear,</i>
<i>there are little foxes in the vines.</i>

263
00:19:03,225 --> 00:19:05,685
DirectIy ahead through that waII...

264
00:19:05,895 --> 00:19:09,356
...the air-conditioned vauIt
containing treasures beyond imagination.

265
00:19:09,565 --> 00:19:11,775
Oh, some hauI, aII right.

266
00:19:11,984 --> 00:19:17,530
Seven Gutenberg Bibles,
1 1 first folios by WiIliam Shakespeare.

267
00:19:17,740 --> 00:19:19,324
Some waII too.

268
00:19:19,533 --> 00:19:22,369
Three feet of cement over 1 8 inches of steeI.

269
00:19:22,578 --> 00:19:24,329
Ah! To the Bat Beam.

270
00:19:28,125 --> 00:19:30,043
But what if something goes wrong,
Bookworm?

271
00:19:30,252 --> 00:19:32,754
Oh, it won't, it won't, it won't.

272
00:19:32,963 --> 00:19:36,383
Best-laid pIans of mice and men.

273
00:19:36,592 --> 00:19:39,427
I don't know where it's from,
but I know it's true.

274
00:19:39,637 --> 00:19:44,057
Schemes, schemes, schemes,
the best-Iaid schemes.

275
00:19:44,266 --> 00:19:47,686
Robert Burns "To a Mouse," stanza seven.

276
00:19:47,895 --> 00:19:49,104
Schemes.

277
00:19:49,313 --> 00:19:51,940
You are graded C-minus.

278
00:19:53,943 --> 00:19:57,112
Now for the Bat Beam.

279
00:20:08,624 --> 00:20:12,293
-Ah. MeIted.
-Fantastic.

280
00:20:12,795 --> 00:20:17,298
My fine twisty worms, folIow me. Ha.

281
00:20:21,512 --> 00:20:22,804
They'lI foIIow you, Bookworm.

282
00:20:23,013 --> 00:20:25,807
Right back into the woodwork
of the prison carpenter shop.

283
00:20:26,016 --> 00:20:28,476
-ImpossibIe.
-How did they escape?

284
00:20:28,853 --> 00:20:30,770
Thought you had us cooked, huh?

285
00:20:30,980 --> 00:20:33,189
We escaped through the manhoIe
under your stove.

286
00:20:33,399 --> 00:20:35,942
The one you used
to introduce your murderous steam pipe.

287
00:20:36,152 --> 00:20:37,527
It's an oId mistake, Bookworm.

288
00:20:37,737 --> 00:20:41,322
Armoring the walIs
but Ieaving the floor unprotected.

289
00:20:41,532 --> 00:20:43,658
How did they discover our objective?

290
00:20:43,868 --> 00:20:46,536
Your taIk in the BatmobiIe
was picked up by a secret mike.

291
00:20:46,746 --> 00:20:49,831
ReIayed to us via the automatic
feedback circuit in our Batcave.

292
00:20:50,291 --> 00:20:51,583
Let's cIean house, Batman.

293
00:20:51,792 --> 00:20:52,834
Now, Robin.

294
00:20:57,339 --> 00:20:58,757
GIasses off.

295
00:21:01,343 --> 00:21:05,847
AlI right, my fine twisty worms, attack!

296
00:21:21,697 --> 00:21:23,239
Charge!

297
00:21:28,662 --> 00:21:29,704
[GASPS]

298
00:21:29,914 --> 00:21:31,206
Ooh!

299
00:21:31,415 --> 00:21:33,416
[ALL GRUNTING]

300
00:21:57,900 --> 00:22:00,193
You shouId have learned
much sooner, Ms. Limpet...

301
00:22:00,402 --> 00:22:03,154
...the oIdest pIot and stiIl the best.

302
00:22:03,864 --> 00:22:05,573
Crime...

303
00:22:06,408 --> 00:22:08,243
...does not pay.

304
00:22:13,332 --> 00:22:17,502
A check for $5000
for the state-prison Iibrary.

305
00:22:17,711 --> 00:22:21,339
-This is very generous of you, Bruce.
-I thought it was the Ieast I couId do...

306
00:22:21,549 --> 00:22:26,928
...after reading about that dreadfuI business
in the newspapers of the Bookworm affair.

307
00:22:27,137 --> 00:22:30,849
And I feeI our prison libraries
couId use some new upIifting titIes.

308
00:22:31,058 --> 00:22:33,059
Yes, yes, shocking.

309
00:22:33,269 --> 00:22:35,478
A man of Bookworm's education.

310
00:22:35,688 --> 00:22:38,314
How couId such a feIlow turn
to a life of crime?

311
00:22:40,150 --> 00:22:44,654
I'd say it's an exampIe of the old precept
"a IittIe knowledge is a dangerous thing."

312
00:22:44,864 --> 00:22:48,408
A wise observation, Bruce.
I'II remember that.

313
00:22:48,617 --> 00:22:50,994
-By the way, would you like to see him?
-Bookworm?

314
00:22:51,203 --> 00:22:53,580
He's outside, awaiting conveyance
to the penitentiary.

315
00:22:53,789 --> 00:22:57,166
Gosh, Bruce, I'd sure like
to see a reaI crook in the flesh.

316
00:22:57,376 --> 00:23:01,504
WelI, I don't see any harm in it, Dick,
as long as he's under sound restraint.

317
00:23:02,464 --> 00:23:04,173
-Get them, Chief O'Hara.
O'HARA: Yes, sir.

318
00:23:05,801 --> 00:23:09,012
-"Them"?
-His femaIe accompIice too, a Ms. Limpet.

319
00:23:09,221 --> 00:23:11,639
Hmm. Very sad case, that one.

320
00:23:11,849 --> 00:23:13,474
O'HARA:
AlI right, bring them in.

321
00:23:13,684 --> 00:23:15,476
Come on, boys.

322
00:23:20,274 --> 00:23:24,360
AlI right, you crooks, and remember,
be poIite to Mr. Bruce Wayne too.

323
00:23:28,824 --> 00:23:30,992
<i>"The World's Hundred Greatest Crimes."</i>

324
00:23:32,703 --> 00:23:34,996
You abandoned chiId.

325
00:23:35,372 --> 00:23:37,707
Is there no hope for you?

326
00:23:38,000 --> 00:23:42,170
As you can see, Bruce,
your gift was soreIy needed.

327
00:23:42,671 --> 00:23:44,672
May I keep that
as a souvenir, commissioner?

328
00:23:45,466 --> 00:23:46,925
-Oh, yes, certainIy.
BRUCE: Thank you.

329
00:23:50,012 --> 00:23:51,304
What are you smiling at?

330
00:23:51,513 --> 00:23:55,016
Oh, I am so much cIeverer
than alI of you, you see. Heh.

331
00:23:55,225 --> 00:24:00,647
Oh, as the poet says,
"They who Iose today may win tomorrow."

332
00:24:00,856 --> 00:24:04,025
Wrong, Bookworm, not the poet.

333
00:24:04,234 --> 00:24:09,656
That line's from Cervantes' <i>D</i><i>o</i><i>n</i> <i>Q</i><i>u</i><i>i</i><i>x</i><i>o</i><i>t</i><i>e</i><i>,</i>
part one, Book 1 , chapter seven.

334
00:24:09,865 --> 00:24:12,158
Pfft. The deviI.

335
00:24:12,368 --> 00:24:16,204
I think this felIow,
he is almost as obnoxious as Batman.

336
00:24:16,413 --> 00:24:19,874
O'HARA:
AlI right, alI right. Out, out, out. Come on.

337
00:25:08,340 --> 00:25:09,340
[EngIish - US - SDH]

